大家好，欢迎收看全新的系列节目
Hello and welcome to a brand-new series
《烘焙大赛:专业人士》
of Bake Off: The Professionals.
第一组预赛就要开始了。
Our first set of heats are about to begin.
我都等不及了。希望我们的前六支队伍全力以赴，
I can't wait. And let's hope our first six teams go all out,
因为在两次测试挑战之后，
because after two testing challenges,
有人要回家了。
somebody will be going home.
要回家了吗?别担心，利亚姆，这次不会是你了。
Going home? Oh, don't worry, Liam - it's not going to be you this time.
你现在有新角色要扮演了。
You've got a new role to play now.
这是不是意味着我能进入决赛了?
So does that mean that I make it all the way to the final?
是的，利亚姆，绝对的!
Yes, Liam, absolutely!
哦,很酷。因为上次我被抢了。
Oh, cool. Cos last time, I was robbed, you know.
哦，我知道。
Oh, I know.
12组才华横溢的糕点师
12 teams of incredibly talented pastry chefs
即将参加的是最壮观的
are about to take part in the most spectacular
最专业的烘焙大赛
professional bake off Britain has ever seen.
感觉很神奇，不是吗?可怕的!
It feels amazing, doesn't it? Terrifying!
每周，他们都要制作数百个精美的蛋糕
Each week, they will have to create hundreds of exquisite cakes and
糕点，然后是建筑
pastries and then construct
令人难以置信的高耸展品完全建成
incredible towering showpieces made entirely
精心雕刻的糖和巧克力。
of delicately-sculpted sugar and chocolate.
这是千载难逢的机会。
It's a once-in-a-lifetime opportunity.
希望我们能走得更远。
Hopefully, we get to go further.
是吗?是吗?
Yeah? Yeah?
他们创造的一切都将受到评判
Everything they create will be judged
由两位世界上最受尊敬的糕点师Benoit Blin…
by two of the world's most respected patissiers - Benoit Blin...
我要失去那个孩子咬你牙齿的乐趣了。
I am losing that kid's pleasure of snapping your teeth into this.
. .还有珍爱·芬登。
..and Cherish Finden.
这太耸人听闻了。
It is so sensational.
我要跳恰恰恰恰。
I've got to cha-cha-cha.
哦，真漂亮。
Ooh, it's beautiful.
走，走，走，走，走。
Go, go, go, go, go.
无处可逃。糕点是一门艺术。
There is no hiding away. Patisserie is an art.
前卫吗?
Avant-garde?
他们把任何错误放在盘子里，
Any mistake that they put on the plate,
我马上就能发现。
I will spot it immediately.
在每个紧张的一周结束时，一个团队…
At the end of each demanding week, one team...
哦,哔哔声!. .会被送回家。
Oh, BLEEP! ..will be sent home.
我为他们感到害怕。
I am scared for them.
但我们的12支队伍中哪一支能保持冷静?
But which of our 12 teams can hold their nerve?
够强烈吗?谁会把自己推到最远?
That intense enough? And who will push themselves furthest?
别哭了。当他们为加冕冠军而战时…
Don't cry. As they fight to be crowned champions...
你认为它会坚持下去吗?
Do you think it is going to hold?
我对你有信心。他们笑了
I've got faith in you. THEY LAUGH
哔哔声。
BLEEP.
. .《烘焙大赛:专业人士》
..of Bake Off: The Professionals.
呻吟
GROANING
在接下来的两天里
Over the next two days,
我们的前六组专业糕点师
our first six teams of professional pastry chefs
将面临两大挑战……
will face two challenges...
祝你好运。
Good luck.
你准备好了吗?
Are you ready?
. .之后将对他们进行排名，
..after which they will be ranked,
谁最后到，谁就得离开。
and whoever comes last will have to leave.
我知道他们会说"开始"
I know they say, like, "Go."
我们不需要，跑掉。我们只需要把食谱拿出来，
We don't need to, like, run off. We just need to get our recipe out and,
喜欢……是的。. .我想讨论一下。
like... Yeah. ..discuss for a second, I think.
早上好，厨师们，欢迎来到《专业烘焙大赛》。
Good morning, chefs, and welcome to Bake Off: The Professionals.
根据评委的说法，
Which, according to the judges,
是英国最激烈的糕点大赛
is Britain's toughest patisserie competition.
今天我们从微型经典开始，
We start today with miniature classics,
两种标准糕点的大批量测试。
a high-volume test of two standards of pastry.
法官们告诉我，如果你不能兑现承诺，
And the judges have told me if you cannot deliver on this,
他们会非常失望的。
they will be sorely disappointed.
不是生气，只是失望。
Not angry, just disappointed.
好吧，珍惜会生气的，但那只是珍惜。
Well, Cherish will be angry, but that's just Cherish.
评委们，能告诉我们你们选出了哪支队伍吗?
So, judges, can you tell us what you have chosen for the teams?
我选了水果馅饼。
I have chosen tarte aux fruits.
你可以用任何你喜欢的水果，
You may use any fruit you like, however,
你的24个蛋挞必须是美味的，而且做得很好。
your 24 tarts must be delicious and highly finished.
伯努瓦，你能告诉我们你选了什么吗?
Benoit, can you tell us what you've chosen?
是的，汤姆，我选了一个……法语发音:对话。
Yes, Tom, I've chosen a... FRENCH PRONUNCIATION: ..conversation.
你是说“谈话”吗?不，不，我是说谈话。
Do you mean "conversation"? No, no, I mean conversation.
它在英语中是什么意思?
What does it mean in English?
英语发音:会话。
ENGISH PRONUNCIATION: Conversation.
嗯，那真是太棒了……法语发音:对话。
Well, that was a wonderful... FRENCH PRONUNCIATION: ..conversation.
这是一种法式小馅饼，由酥皮组成，
This is a little French tart consisting of puff pastry,
奶油，果酱，最后淋上皇家糖霜。
frangipane or almond cream, jam and finished off with royal icing.
我需要每队24人。
I need to see 24 from each team.
大厨们，你们有三个半小时的时间，现在开始计时。
Chefs, you have three-and-a-half hours, and your time starts now.
哦,哔哔声!
Oh, BLEEP!
我们开始吧。
Let's do it.
至关重要的是，团队首先要做好这一点
It is crucial that the team do well with this first
挑战。珍惜和我的关系随着时间的流逝而变得紧密。
challenge. Cherish and I have made it tight with time.
我们想知道这些专业人士是如何
We want to find out how those professionals
可以用自己推吗
can be pushed with their
时间管理，提供令人难以置信的味道
time management to deliver incredible flavours
在大量的微缩模型中完美的呈现。
and flawless presentation across large batches of miniatures.
我想在水果馅饼上看到的是漂亮的天鹅绒酥皮
What I want to see on a tarte aux fruits is a beautiful velvet pastry
光滑的充气法式奶油。
of smooth, aerated creme patissiere.
水果必须精美地呈现。
The fruit has to be beautifully presented.
我们希望团队能够自由发挥他们的想象力。
We want the team to run free with their imagination.
早上好，玛塔，早上好，朱莉。
Morning, Marta, morning, Julie.
早....早上好,厨师。
Morning. Morning, chef.
你做这件事就好像你想快点做完一样。
You are going at it like you want it done very quickly.
那么我们现在准备什么呢?
So what are we preparing now?
我在准备做水果挞的酱汁。
So I am preparing the pate sucree for the fruit tarts.
脑袋往下……?
Pate suc...?
脑袋sucree。脑袋sucree。我的法语不太好——我向你道歉。
Pate sucree. Pate sucree. My French isn't great - I do apologise.
不，没关系。在英语中，你可以说sweet pastry。
No, that is fine. In English, you could say sweet pastry.
很好，这样更快。
It's fine, that's quicker.
拉夫堡邦邦糕点店的朱莉和玛尔塔
Julie and Marta from the independent Bom Bom Patisserie in Loughborough
他们是在餐饮学院认识的，朱莉是玛尔塔的导师。
met at catering college, where Julie was Marta's tutor.
巴西出生的玛尔塔正在混合一种经典的英国大黄和蛋奶冻
Brazilian-born Marta is blending a classic British rhubarb and custard
草莓,
with strawberries,
被耗时的酸奶慕斯包围着。
surrounded by a time-consuming glaze dome of yoghurt mousse.
我需要把蛋挞烤好，这样我才能开始组装。
I will need the tarts baked so I can start assembling it.
什么都不会耽误的，玛尔塔。
Nothing is going to be delayed, Marta.
什么都不会耽搁!我们让他们继续干好吗?
Nothing is going to be delayed! Shall we let them crack on?
你不想试一试，是吗?
You do not want a go, then?
哦，不，不，不!我要试试，我要试试。
Oh, no, no, no! I want a go, I want a go.
伯努瓦:现在是三人组了!
BENOIT: A team of three now!
不，波浪太多了。谢谢你！
No, too many waves. Thank you.
走了。
Get going.
这就是我输掉另一届烘焙大赛的原因吗?
Is that why I lost the other Bake Off?
他们笑了
THEY LAUGH
#进入最佳状态
# Get into the groove
男孩，你得走了…＃
# Boy, you gotta move... #
丽贝卡和米迦勒的水果馅饼
Rebekah and Michael's tarte aux fruits
灵感来自于他们对一首歌的热爱。再喝一两杯。
has been inspired by their love of a song. And one or two drinks.
我们喜欢喝一杯果汁朗姆酒放松一下。
We like to relax with a pina colada.
如果你想喝点酒，我们这张桌子是不错的选择。
If you are after a tipple, our table's the one.
#抱紧我，不要放手…＃
# Hold me close and don't let go... #
迈克尔和丽贝卡的天赋
Michael and Rebekah's combined talent
帮助了卡迪夫的圣大卫医院
has helped St David's in Cardiff
成为全市唯一的五星级酒店。
become the city's only five-star hotel.
他们的椰林朗姆酒果馅饼有椰子和朗姆酒慕斯，
Their pina colada tartes aux fruits will have a coconut and rum mousse,
酸橙鱼子酱和一小瓶朗姆酒焦糖糖浆。
lime caviar and a pipette of rum caramel syrup.
卡迪夫最好的糕点师，对吗?
The best pastry chefs in Cardiff - is that correct?
脑袋有点大，不过，继续吧。如果是你说的，不是我们…
Well, slightly big-headed, but, yeah, go on. If you have said it, not us...
嗯，我就是这么听说的。坊间传言……我喜欢你的声音，丽贝卡。
Well, that is what I heard. Word on the street is... I like your voice, Rebekah.
她是一个山谷女孩。我来自朗达谷的托尼潘迪。
She is a Valleys girl. So I'm from Tonypandy, the Rhondda Valley.
Tonypandy吗?Tonypandy。听起来你应该把这个放进蛋挞里。
Tonypandy? Tonypandy. That sounds like something you should be putting in this tart.
你从哪里来，迈克尔?
And where are you from, Michael?
我来自一个叫Bargoed的小镇，那是…Bargoed吗?
I am from a little town called Bargoed, which is... Bargoed?
是的。听起来不像是应该放在甜点里。
Yeah. That doesn't sound like it should be in a dessert.
绝对不是，相信我。
Definitely not - trust me.
对于Hideko和Theo的水果馅饼，
For Hideko and Theo's tarte aux fruits,
灵感来自比卡迪夫的一家夜总会更遥远的地方。
inspiration has come from a little further afield than a nightclub in Cardiff.
对不起,爱。
Sorry, love.
Hideko经营着自己的定制糕点公司SweetArt Lab，
Hideko runs her own bespoke pastry business, the SweetArt Lab,
西奥帮助她将不可思议的创作变为现实。
where Theo helps bring her incredible creations to life.
她设计了一个彩虹水果馅饼
She has designed a rainbow tarte aux fruits
其中还包括另一种日本食材
that includes another Japanese ingredient.
Shiso。这是一种日本的绿色草本植物。
Shiso. It's a Japanese green herb.
它不像罗勒，也不像薄荷……它介于两者之间。
It is not like a basil, it's not like a mint... It's in between.
你知道我在家里种大麻吗?
Do you know that I grow shiso at home?
我把它放在我的窗边，真是太棒了。
I put it by my window and it is amazing.
我们就着米饭吃，不是吗?
We eat it with rice, don't we?
是的,完全正确!
Yeah, exactly!
你不抽，对吧?
You don't smoke it, no?
不。
No.
为了填满他们的水果馅饼，Chris和BJ做了更大的尝试。
To fill their tartes aux fruits, Chris and BJ are going even further.
我们用沙棘做奶油蛋糕。
We are using sea buckthorn in our creme patissiere.
这是一种生长在海边的浆果。
It's a berry that grows by the sea.
它非常锋利。它几乎像果子露。
It is very sharp. It is almost like sherbet.
通常情况下，它是有毒的，但一旦煮熟，
Ordinarily, it is poisonous, but once it is cooked up,
它有一种非常棒的味道。
it's got a really amazing flavour.
没有一点危险的生活是什么?
What is life without a little bit of danger?
看看还能找到什么，然后我们就可以回去了。是的。
See what else we can find and then we can head back. Yeah.
BJ和Chris经常寻找食材
BJ and Chris often forage for ingredients
带回到备受好评的厨房
to take back to the kitchen at the critically-acclaimed
在坦布里奇韦尔斯的沃伦餐厅。
Warren restaurant in Tunbridge Wells.
贝尔·格里尔斯是我最崇拜的人之一。
Bear Grylls is one of my biggest heroes.
我爱他。他不会看这个的。
I love him. He's not going to watch this.
我也不在乎
I don't care.
他们的水果蛋挞以芒果为特色，
Their tartes aux fruits will feature mango,
椰子蛋白霜和沙棘凝胶。
coconut meringue and a sea buckthorn gel.
它们潜在的有毒成分已经有了致命的
And their potentially poisonous ingredient has already had a lethal
对法式奶油的影响。
effect on their creme patissiere.
这很快就分裂了。
That has immediately split.
我想泥已经和奶油分开了。
I think the puree has split with the cream.
感觉正好。我感觉出奇的平静
Okey dokey. I am feeling weirdly calm,
但我相信这种情况会改变的。
but I'm sure that's going to change.
沃伦河的男孩们并不是唯一一支开始探索的队伍
The boys from the Warren aren't the only team beginning to discover
第一次挑战有多难。
just how difficult this first challenge is.
一个小时。快一个小时了，Hideko。
One hour. Nearly an hour gone, Hideko.
现在得用力了。
Have to push now.
是的。茱莉亚，蛋挞已经在烤箱里了。
Yeah. Julia, the tart in the oven already.
他们正要进去。
There are about to go in.
烘蛋挞饼，
With tart cases baking,
剩下的每一分钟都需要仔细安排。
every remaining minute will need to be carefully scheduled.
他们需要足够的时间让箱子冷却，然后才能装进去……
They need enough time for the cases to cool before they can fill them...
这事得快点了。
This needs to hurry up, like.
. .而且它们的馅料需要尽早凝固……
..and their fillings need to set early enough...
做我的酸奶慕斯。
Doing my yoghurt mousse.
. .留出足够的时间装饰。
..to leave enough time for decoration.
我们还没到那一步。我想我们快没时间了。
We are not there yet. I think we're going to run out of time.
如果我开始跑来跑去哭，那就是信号了。
If I start running around and crying, that'll be the telltale sign.
这里越来越暖和了，不是吗?
It's getting warmer in here, isn't it?
时间可能是达瑞尔和巴拉特最不担心的事情。
Time could be the least of Darryl and Bharat's worries.
我们有了德国甜酱。
So we have a German sweet paste.
它是无蛋的。这是一种很棒的糕点。
It's an eggless. It's a great pastry.
你们通常不喜欢在食谱中使用鸡蛋吗?
Do you guys normally go against using eggs in your recipes?
我对鸡蛋过敏。
I'm a actually allergic to egg.
啊!你对鸡蛋过敏?
Ah! You're allergic to eggs?
是的，我是。你负责品酒吗?
I am, yes. Do you do the tasting?
我负责品酒。啊，好了。
I do the tasting. Ah, there we go.
Darryl和他的家人住在康沃尔，
Darryl lives with his family in Cornwall,
但每天通勤去伯明翰
but commutes to Birmingham
在那里，他和巴拉特在名胜世界制作高端甜点。
where he and Bharat create high-end desserts at Resorts World.
他们的蛋挞会有香草奶油蛋糕和白蛋糕
Their tart will have a vanilla creme patissiere and a white
巧克力芒果慕斯，
chocolate-glazed mango mousse,
这两种达里尔都没尝过
neither of which Darryl has ever tasted.
错误发生了，我最后住进了医院。
Mistakes have happened and I have ended up in hospital.
医生确实说过"放弃吧，你可能会害死自己"
The doctors did say, "Give it up, you could end up killing yourself."
我确实走开了，想了一会儿。
I did go away and think about it for a minute..
. .然后决定继续
..then just decided to carry on
因为这是我喜欢做的事。
cos it's something I love doing.
山姆和伊曼纽尔还面临着一个死敌……
Sam and Emmanuel are also facing a mortal enemy...
我们决定走一条完全不同的路，
We have decided to go a totally different way,
重新思考我们呈现它的方式。
rethinking the way we are presenting it.
. .。
..themselves.
我们要做芒果和激情慕斯。
We are going to do a mango and passion mousse.
然后我要做一个草莓酸橙果冻放在中间。
Then I am going to make a strawberry and lime jelly to go in the middle.
冻好后，把它们切出来，
And once that is frozen, cut them out,
把它们浸在百香果可可脂里。
dip them in a passion fruit cocoa butter.
前决赛选手，
A former finalist,
山姆和他的老板伊曼纽尔，
Sam is returning to the competition with his boss, Emmanuel,
伦敦五星级希尔顿公园巷酒店的首席糕点师。
head pastry chef of the five-star Hilton Park Lane in London.
除了三层慕斯，他们还制作了六种水果，
As well as a triple-layered mousse, they are heading six types of fruit,
草莓巧克力羽毛和金箔做竖形蛋挞。
strawberry chocolate feathers and gold leaf for a vertical tart.
我们试着把你通常能找到的所有味道都放进去，但是
We try and take all the flavours that you would normally find but
把它们改造成相当现代的东西。
transform them into something quite modern.
感觉有点压力，但仍然很自信。
Feeling a bit under pressure but still confident.
大厨们，你们已经完成一半了。
Chefs, you are halfway through.
哔哔声!我们在后面。
BLEEP! We're behind.
如果制作24个完美无瑕的水果蛋挞还不够苛刻的话……
If creating 24 flawless tartes aux fruits wasn't demanding enough...
把它们冻起来……两队还要完成另一个甜点——
Freeze them. ..the teams have another pastry to complete -
Benoit的……
Benoit's...
我记得，当我还小的时候，走进那些面包店
I remember, when I was little, going into those bakeries
爱上了那些美丽的金色圆挞。
and falling in love with those beautiful, golden, round tarts.
传统上，谈话中有一个酥皮饼盒
Traditionally, a conversation has a puff pastry case
里面有覆盆子果酱、杏仁奶油或香槟酒，
filled with raspberry jam, almond cream, or frangipane,
上面撒上酥皮，
topped with puff pastry,
皇家糖霜和酥皮钻石装饰。
royal icing and a puff pastry diamond decoration.
如果哪支队伍有足够的勇气加入他们自己的创意，
If any of the teams are brave enough to add their own twist,
它会让我小时候喜欢的糕点更加美味。
it has to enhance the pastry I loved as a boy.
克里斯。即使他们已经毁了他们的行程…
Chris. Even though they have already ruined their schedule...
我估计沙棘还要多一点。
I reckon even slightly more sea buckthorn.
对，放进去。
Yeah, put it in.
. .Chris和BJ现在可能会毁了Benoit童年的梦想。
..Chris and BJ could now ruin Benoit's childhood dreams.
现代的对话……
The modern conversation...
现代对话?!
A modern conversation?!
. .是用甜酥皮而不是酥皮做的。
..is made with sweet pastry and not puff pastry.
丧钟敲响
FUNEREAL BELL TOLLS
我们用的是粗糙的酥皮基底
We are using a rough puff pastry base
然后我们在上面撒上甜面酱。为什么?
and then we have capped that with the sweet paste. Why?
因为我们做酥皮的时候遇到了很多麻烦
Because we were having so much trouble with the puff pastry
没有按照我们想要的方式上升。
not rising the way we wanted it.
冲击。
Shock it.
嘿，让我们学习和生活。
Hey, let's learn and live.
我希望如此。或者活到老学到老。是啊!
I hope so. Or live and learn. Yeah!
学习然后离开?
Learn and leave?
学习后离开。
Learn and leave.
练习重现这一经典并不适合西奥和英子
Practising recreating this classic hasn't suited Theo and Hideko's
艺术的一面。
artistic side.
我试了一个快的。祝你好运——一切顺利。
I tried a fast one. Good luck - it went well.
第二个坍塌了!
The second collapsed!
真是一场灾难!
It was a disaster!
煮，煮，煮，煮。
Boil, boil, boil, boil.
你想尝尝这个吗?
Do you want to just taste this?
而且已经在对付达里尔的鸡蛋过敏了…
And already coping with Daryll's egg allergy...
里面有香草吗?它还需要更多吗?
Have you got vanilla in there? Does it need more?
它需要更多的香草，是的……巴拉特现在面临着另一个障碍。
It needs more vanilla, yeah. ..Bharat now faces another obstacle.
你觉得和别人聊天怎么样?
How do you feel about making conversation?
你现在做得很好。这是一个伟大的…法语发音:对话。
You're doing great now. This is a great... FRENCH PRONUNCIATION: ..conversation.
我以前没做过。这是一件好事吗?不是为了比赛，不是。
I haven't really made before. Is that a good thing? Not for a competition, no.
我是说，这基本上就是贝克维尔馅饼，不是吗?
I mean, it's basically a Bakewell tart, isn't it?
这是一个奇特的名字…是的，我想是的。
It's a fancy name for... Yeah, I think so.
这就是当Benoit谈论这件事时我的感受。
That's how I felt about it when Benoit was going ON about it.
芒果慕斯冻好了。
The passion and mango mousse has been frozen.
还有一个令人担忧的雄心勃勃的水果馅饼……
As well as a worryingly ambitious tarte aux fruits...
我做了一个aga果冻。
I made an aga jelly.
阿迦设定得很快，所以这样的比赛很有意义。
Aga sets fast, so makes sense for a competition like this.
. .山姆和伊曼纽尔找到了一种方式来进行对话。”
..Sam and Emmanuel have found a way to make the conversations'
简单漂亮的馅料有点复杂。
beautifully simple fillings a bit more complicated.
在果酱里，我们加了一点菖蒲……
To the jam, we have added a little bit of calamansi...
哦……这是一种柑橘。
Ooh... ..which is a citrus.
我是伴随着这种酸橙长大的。这是一个很小很小的酸橙。
I grew up with this lime. It's a small, little, tiny lime.
味道很浓。
Very intense, its flavour.
希望它不会取代覆盆子，这是有风险的。
Hopefully, it won't take over the raspberry, which is a risk.
即使团队对他们的谈话内容都很满意……
Even if the teams are happy with both their conversation fillings...
这是很多法国奶酪。
It is a lot of French beurre.
我们做一半吧。是吗?是的。
Let's do half. Yeah? Yeah.
. .在第一个挑战中多任务处理
..multitasking in this first challenge
会变得更加困难。
is about to get much harder.
你的慕斯冻坏了。甜蜜的!
Your mousses are frozen. Sweet!
除了确保他们所有的水果挞元素都在轨道上…
As well as ensuring all their tarte aux fruits elements are on track...
越快进入爆炸，效果越好。
The quicker it gets in the blast, the better it is.
我要试着把它切下来，如果太软了，
I need to try and cut out of this, and if it is too soft,
这将是一场噩梦。
it's going to be a nightmare.
. .对话必须充实和建立起来……
..the conversations have to be filled and built...
#哦，你得搬家了…＃
# Oh, you've got to move... #
. .还有足够的时间烤好。
..with enough time remaining for them to bake correctly.
我们能做到的，宝贝。我们可以把这段时间追回来。
We can do this, babes. We can claw this time back now.
这里有一个!
Vous avez une heure!
一个heure !
Une heure!
我甚至不知道那是否…你是这么说的吗?
I don't even know if that... Is that how you say it?
可能不是这个意思。
Probably doesn't mean that.
意思可能是“你把东西落在餐具柜上了。”
Probably means, "You have left something on the sideboard."
我们有一个小时的时间把所有事情做完。
We have an hour to have everything done.
肯定会很紧。
Definitely going to be tight.
现在出了很多汗。
Perspiring a lot now.
好了。
Nice.
她用葡萄牙语数数
SHE COUNTS IN PORTUGUESE
对话的结局是我最担心的，
The finish on the conversations is what I'm most worried about,
确保它们看起来干净整洁。
to make sure they all look neat and tidy.
太小了。它们必须在接下来的15分钟内放进烤箱。
Too small. They have got to go in the oven in the next 15 minutes.
我们得把这些放进烤箱。
We need to get these in the oven.
我们还剩多久?
How long have we got left?
46分钟。
46 minutes.
我的眼镜上全是香槟酒。
Got frangipane all over my glasses.
我不喜欢谈话。
I don't like conversations.
你保持的越简单，你需要的就越完美。
The simpler you keep it, the more perfect you need to have it.
只是用皇家糖衣覆盖对话。
Just covering the conversations with royal icing.
煮25分钟，所以…
They take 25 minutes to cook, so...
他们得在六分钟内进去。
They need to be going in in the next six minutes.
我觉得你野心太大了。好的。
I think you're being a bit overambitious. OK.
然后，伊曼纽尔，把非常薄的酥皮放在上面。
And then, Emmanuel, put very thin strips of puff pastry on the top.
这会在糖霜烹饪时产生裂缝。
That will create the cracks in the icing when it cooks.
帮我一下。我们得结束这一切。
Give me a hand. We need to finish this.
43分钟。否则，它出不来。
43 minutes. Otherwise, it won't get out.
沸腾了，伙计，沸腾了。对不起，对不起，对不起。
It's boiling, man, it is boiling. Sorry, sorry, sorry.
把它放在上面，防止染色过多。
Putting it on top to stop the colouring too much.
否则，就会很黑。
Otherwise, it's going to be very dark.
伯努瓦希望在上面放些糕点，
Benoit did expect some pastry on top,
但我们只是在上面涂上黄油。
but we just score over them with butter.
一定快到了。
Must be almost there.
当Chris和BJ开始弥补时间的时候…
While Chris and BJ are beginning to make up time...
是的。
Yeah.
. .Hideko和Theo开始挣扎……
..Hideko and Theo are starting to struggle...
半小时……他们并不孤单。
Half an hour. ..and they are not alone.
哔哔声!
BLEEP!
慕斯比我们想要的稍微厚一点。
The mousse is slightly thicker than we wanted it.
现在有点汗流浃背。
Bit of a sweaty mess at the moment.
Hideko，现在就放，否则他们不会…是的。
Hideko, put them now or they won't be... Yeah.
这些要放进烤箱了。
These are going in the oven.
对，对，对。按钮的哔哔声
Yeah, yeah, yeah. BUTTONS BEEP
好吧，芭芭丝，接下来是什么?
Right then, babs, what's next?
水果馅饼。
The fruit tart.
一，二，三。
One, two, three.
搅拌机开始震动
MIXER WHIRS
釉。我们要加一点红色。来吧!
Glaze. We'll add a bit of red to it. Come on!
萨姆的摩丝现在需要手工定型了。
Sam's mousses will now need to be shaped by hand...
我们需要调整。修剪指挥棒。
We need to adjust. Trim the baton.
. .这需要时间。
..which will take time.
有点乱。
It's a little messy.
我在做酸橙鱼子酱来配水果馅饼。
I'm making the lime caviar to go on the fruit tart.
酸橙汁，糖，琼脂的混合物。
A mixture of lime juice, sugar, agar-agar.
把它放进冷油里。
Just drop it into cold oil.
当我还是个孩子的时候，我总是喝五活果汁。
As a child, I was always given the juice drink Five Alive.
这就是它让我想起的。
That's what it reminds me of.
可以说，你只剩下小酸橙球了。
You are left with little lime balls, so to speak.
这让我想起了格罗巴格。
And then, reminds me a little bit of Grotbags.
回到爆炸现场。
Back to the blast.
他重塑了他的摩丝……
He has reshaped his mousses...
哦,哔哔声!
Oh, BLEEP!
. .但现在山姆把它们放在托盘上，托盘太大了，放不回去
..but now Sam's put them on a tray that is too big to go back into the
爆炸冷却器。有什么问题，托盘吗?
blast chiller. What's the problem, the tray?
我变得非常非常紧张。
I'm getting very, very tense.
18分钟。持续推动。是的。
18 minutes. Last push. Yeah.
我汗流浃背。
I'm sweating my BLEEP off.
他们还好吗?
Are they all right?
那么这个蛋挞还需要做什么呢?构建!
So what else is left to do for that tart? Build!
我给它上了一层橙色的釉，
I am glazing it with an orange glaze,
这让它更有一点柑橘的味道。
which gives it a bit more citrus flavour.
我们还有多少时间?
How long we got?
大厨们，你们有15分钟。
Chefs, you have 15 minutes.
我们在鲍比球上。是的。
We're on the Bobby Ball. Yeah.
继续，汤米，过来。
Rock on, Tommy, over here.
他们看起来有点邋遢。
They look a little bit sort of scruffy.
我要做35根羽毛。
I'm going to do 35 feathers.
超级好。
Super nice.
我在给沙棘糕点奶油倒汁。
I'm just piping our sea buckthorn pastry cream.
那是六分钟。
That's six minutes.
我们会准时到达的。
We are going to be just on time.
可可脂很好切。
Cocoa butter's cutting well.
当你蘸着冷冻的东西时，巧克力会立即反应。
When you're dipping something that's frozen, chocolate reacts instantly.
我们还有多少分钟?
How many minutes do we have?
大厨们，你们还有五分钟。
Chefs, you have five minutes left.
你喜欢朗姆酒吗?＃
# Do you like pina coladas...? #
哦,他妈的!他们是不是很热?
Oh, bugger! Are they hot, by any chance?
我想继续我的谈话。
I want to jump on to my conversations.
其中一些刚刚爆发。
Some of them have just exploded.
他们看起来有点粗糙。
They are looking a bit rough.
混合淹没了语音
MIXING DROWNS SPEECH
这是科米特生孩子时的样子。
This is what it looks like when Kermit has babies.
冗长的。
Overstuffed.
我不在乎，只要我们把他们救出来就行。
I don't care, as long as we get them out.
一些朗姆酒从移液管里漏出来了。百香果。
Some of the rum has leaked out of these pippettes. Passion fruit.
大厨们，你们还有一分钟就要开始迷你经典了
Chefs, you have one minute until your miniature classics
必须上桌。
must be served.
现在每一秒都很重要。
Every second's important now.
哦，别这样，别这样。我们还有时间，不是吗?
Oh, come on, come on, come on. We've got time, haven't we?
是的。别涂太多金色的，伙计。
Yeah. Try not to put too much gold on, mate.
哦，哔哔哔的东西，伙计。
Oh, BLEEP things man.
来吧，你这个小混蛋。
Come on, you little bugger.
她很重要
SHE COUNTS
好了，厨师们，时间到了。
OK, chefs, time's up.
请离你的蛋挞远点。
Please, step away from your tarts.
时间过得比你想象的要快得多。
The time goes a lot quicker than you think.
最好的是……我不需要尿尿。
Best thing is...didn't need to pee.
不，我也不太想尿尿。
No, I don't really need to pee either.
这两支球队现在将面临伯努瓦和珍爱的审判
The teams will now face the judgment of Benoit and Cherish
这是第一次。
for the very first time.
这太可怕了，不是吗?
This is terrifying, init?
哔哔声!
BLEEP!
希尔顿公园巷，请到审判桌来。
Hilton Park Lane, please come up to the table to be judged.
它们看起来和我记忆中的很接近。
They look pretty close to what I remember.
这是一个漂亮的，完整的挞。
It's a nice, full tart.
四季橘…他吹覆盆子
The calamondin... HE BLOWS RASPBERRY
我想要覆盆子酱。
I would have rather raspberry on it.
我们试试水果馅饼吧。它们看起来很性感。
Let's try the fruit tart. They look very sexy.
你还在上面撒了一点金粉。
You've dusted a little bit of gold dust on it as well.
它会提升整件事。
It just lifts up the whole thing.
干得好，大厨。谢谢你！
Well done, chef. Thank you.
调味方面，我放了很多酸，
Flavour-wise, I've got a lot of acid,
没有什么真正有趣的东西出来。
nothing really interesting coming out of it.
这里太沉了，琼脂太多了。
It's so heavy over here, it's just too much agar.
非常感谢。谢谢你！
Thank you very much. Thank you.
谈话，就结尾而言，
Conversation - as far as the finishing is concerned,
因为你没有在上面放任何糕点，我们看到了杏仁奶油。
because you didn't put any pastry on the top, we see the almond cream.
好的部分是杏仁奶油，很明显，烤得很好。
The good part is the almond cream, obviously, is baked nicely.
然而，执行力很差。
However, the execution is poor.
水果馅饼怎么样?
What about the fruit tart?
你的釉很漂亮，很光滑。
Your glaze is beautiful, it's smooth.
我们有草莓，菠萝，芒果，
We've got the strawberry, pineapple, mango,
但它不会去任何特别的地方。
but it doesn't go anywhere special.
有点平。好的。
It's a bit flat. OK.
它让我兴奋吗?不是真的。
Does it excite me? Not really.
这酥皮摸起来很厚，不容易碎。
The pastry feels thick and it's not flaky.
但你把水果挞提升到了另一个层次。
But you've moved the fruit tart to a different level.
哦!
Oops!
我对酸奶慕斯不感兴趣。它尝起来像酸奶。
Yoghurt mousse doesn't excite me. It tastes of yoghurt.
再放一点大黄，但要放得很轻。
And I get a little bit of rhubarb, but very light.
所以我认为这不是水果挞，我认为这是酸奶挞。
So I don't think it's a fruit tart, I think it's a yoghurt tart.
这次谈话，是王室的锦上添花
The conversation - the royal icing on the top
看起来不太吸引人，所以…他吹覆盆子
doesn't look very appealing, so... HE BLOWS RASPBERRY
我不吃糕点。如你所见，这是生的
I will not eat the pastry. As you can see, that's raw -
今晚会让我肚子疼的。
that will give me tummy ache tonight.
我的心碎了……
My heart was broken...
. .因为我们刚才在说琉璃和琉璃。
..because we were talking about the glaze with the shisho.
但是当我看到水果的时候，它太干了。
But when I look at the fruit, it's just so dry.
你完全失去了控制。是的。
You lost control completely. Yeah.
这就是我要找的十字形图案。
This is the little crisscross pattern I'm looking for.
但很明显，我们有一些自负。
But obviously we've got a few puffed up.
谈话不一定要夸夸其谈。
A conversation doesn't have to puff up.
啊!它看起来是满的——这很重要!
Ah! It looks full - and that's important!
上面的糖霜有点少了。
The amount of icing you've got on the top, which is a bit short.
我失去了那孩子咬你牙齿的乐趣。
I'm losing that kid's pleasure of snapping your teeth into this.
还有烘焙，虽然不完美，但很好吃。
And the baking, not perfect, but pleasant.
我非常高兴与愉快!
I'm very happy with pleasant!
笑声
LAUGHTER
看看你的水果馅饼，
Looking at your fruit tartlets,
我需要墨镜才能看到你的鱼子酱。
I need sunglasses to look at your caviar.
我不能忍受这么多颜色的样子。
I can't bear the look of so much colour.
他猛地呼了一口气
HE EXHALES SHARPLY
我该怎么处理这个瓶子?
What do I do with the bottle?
过了头。这是椰子朗姆酒焦糖。
Over the top. It's a coconut rum caramel.
我不确定这是好是坏。
I'm not sure if that's good or bad.
我喜欢它。
I like it.
我说了，我说了，我喜欢!
I said it, I said it - I like it!
我喜欢菠萝，所以你是我的最爱。
I love pineapples, so you got my sweet spot there.
好的。
OK.
我不喜欢……
I don't like it...
. .我喜欢!
..I love it!
太好吃了，我的天啊。
It's so tasty, oh, my goodness.
现在你的膝盖变软了。我得到…!
Now your knees are going soft. I'm getting...!
好吧，我告诉你，鱼子酱真的非常非常酸，
Well, I tell you what, the caviar is really, really acidic,
它和各种元素都融合得很好。
and it blends very well with every element.
还有你洒在上面的，太棒了。
And this that you drizzle on - sensational.
谢谢，非常感谢。
Thank you, thank you very much.
这很好。哦,是的。
That's nice. Oh, yeah.
我没想到会这样。这是一半一半。
I wasn't expecting that. It was half and half.
我真没想到会这样。
I really wasn't expecting that.
沃伦，请过来。
The Warren, please come forward.
这就像一场婚礼，不是吗?
It's like a wedding, isn't it?
我们有24个吗?你没有。你有18个。
Have we got 24? You do not. you've got 18.
哦，他们只做了18件!
Oh, they only did 18!
我不认为你特别着急，
I don't believe you were particularly rushing,
或者你表现得不像。是的。
or you didn't behave like you were. Yeah.
你只是站在那里无所事事。
You were standing around doing nothing.
首先，肠衣是生的。我不能吃那个。
Firstly, the casing is uncooked. I can't eat that.
奶油很无趣，很无趣，我不喜欢。
And the cream is dull, it's boring, it's not to my liking.
对不起，我不能吃。
Sorry, can't eat it.
大多数人都说过，
Well, most of it has been said,
不过沙棘的味道是我喜欢的。
except the sea buckthorn flavour is one I like.
就谈话而言，它已经爆发了。
As far as the conversation is concerned, it has exploded.
是的。但是,是的…是烤好的吗?是的。
Yeah. But, yeah...is it baked? Yep.
不!它不是。
Nope! It isn't.
杏仁奶油在哪里?它烤得不对。
Where is the almond cream? It hasn't baked correctly.
我有点失望。
I'm a bit disappointed.
如果我是一个专业厨师，你把这个带到比赛中，
If I'm a professional chef, you bring this up into the competition,
我会很尴尬的。
I'll be so embarrassed.
哇……
Wow...
什么也说不出来。我们被毁了。
Can't really say anything. We just got destroyed.
也许我们有点太放松了。
Maybe we have been a bit too relaxed.
有点破坏灵魂，但不会破坏气氛。
Slightly soul-destroying, but not going to let it kill the vibe.
明天的第二项挑战规模巨大，以至于各队
Tomorrow's second challenge is on such a grand scale that the teams
有黄金时间准备需要的元素吗
have been given a golden hour to prepare any elements that need
一夜之间设置。
setting overnight.
到目前为止，谁印象深刻?我来自威尔士的同事们
Who's impressed so far? My little colleagues from Wales
在圣大卫酒店。
from St David's Hotel.
他们准备，排练，
They prepared, they rehearsed,
所以他们没有低估竞争。
so they didn't underestimate the competition.
谁有麻烦了?
Who is in trouble?
甜馅饼俱乐部。它的野心太大了。
The SweetArt Club. It's just too ambitious.
名胜世界…?
Resorts World...?
我觉得他这么做很保险。
I think he's playing it very safe.
没有什么令人兴奋的。
There's nothing that is exciting.
但你还有，沃伦团队。
But you've got, also, The Warren team.
如果你是来参加比赛的，你必须做好心理准备。
If you come for a competition, you have to be mentally prepared.
少一点谈话，多一点行动。
A little less conversation, a little bit more action.
在我们的六支队伍参加之前还有一个挑战
There's one challenge remaining before one of our six teams will
不得不退出竞争。
have to leave the competition.
欢迎回来，大厨们。我们都希望你们都休息好了
Welcome back, chefs. We all hope you're all well rested
为今天的表演挑战赛做准备
and prepared for today's Showpiece Challenge.
现在，这是关于一个普通的甜点
Now, this is all about taking an ordinary dessert
并把它变成一些非凡的东西。
and transforming it into something extraordinary.
今天，评委们希望你们喜欢自己
And today, the judges would like you to like you
来改造黑森林蛋糕
to transform Black Forest gateau.
评委们，你们在找什么?
So, judges, what are you looking for?
传统上，这道甜点的特色是巧克力，
Well, traditionally, the dessert features chocolate,
奶油和樱桃白兰地，叫樱桃酒。
cream and a cherry brandy called kirsch.
我想要那些味道。我也想在你的展品中感受大自然。
I want those flavours. I want also to feel nature in your showpieces.
基本上，伯努瓦希望你在蛋糕里放足够的樱桃酒
Basically, Benoit wants you to put enough kirsch in the gateau that
他产生幻觉，以为自己真的在森林里。
he hallucinates that he's actually in a forest.
做大点，不然你就得回家。
Go big, or you will go home.
大厨们，你们还有四个小时
Chefs, you have four hours left
来完成今天的Showpiece挑战。
to complete today's Showpiece Challenge.
你的时间从现在开始。
Your time starts...now.
的焦点。我们开始吧。
Focus. Let's do this.
果冻，海绵，香蒂伊。
Jelly, sponge, Chantilly.
当我还是个孩子的时候，我们经常
When I was a little kid, we always used to get
黑森林是我们的生日礼物。
a Black Forest for our birthdays.
是莎拉·李冻住了。
It was Sara Lee frozen.
它得解冻两天左右
It had to defrost for about two days
在你真正熬过去之前。
before you could actually get through it.
很复古。
Very retro.
向这个日耳曼经典致敬需要
Paying tribute to this Germanic classic will require
足够24人享用的令人垂涎的甜点
enough mouthwatering desserts to serve 24
还有一个令人瞠目结舌的可食用雕塑。
and an eye-popping edible sculptural centrepiece.
我在找一件艺术品，
I'm looking for a work of art here,
炫耀各种各样的技术。
showing off a whole range of techniques.
大量的创新和表演技巧。
Plenty of innovation and a sense of showmanship.
质地和味道很重要。
It's very important to get texture and flavour right.
每个组成部分之间都必须保持良好的平衡。
Every component has to balance very well with each other.
如果味道达不到我的标准，我是不会接受的。
If the taste is not up to my standard, it will not be acceptable.
我去过黑森林的时候，
When I've been to the Black Forest,
它是美丽的。
it was beautiful.
这就是我们的灵感来源。
That is the inspiration we got it from.
朱莉会专注于那棵树，
Julie is going to be concentrating on the tree,
我来做开胃菜
and I'll be doing the entremets.
由蛋白霜慕斯，樱桃果盘，松糕，
Comprised of meringue mousse, cherry compote, joconde sponge,
还有巧克力黑貂饼干底座，这是玛尔塔的主菜分享甜点
and a chocolate sable biscuit base, Marta's entremets sharing dessert
会坐在朱莉精致的糖树下
will sit at the foot of Julie's delicate sugar tree.
模具是有弹性的PVC，周围有很多透明胶带。
By mould is flexible PVC with lots of Sellotape around it.
蓝彼得，吃你的心吧!
Blue Peter, eat your heart out!
我们把地产附在了餐厅上，
We've got the estate attached to the restaurant,
我自己也喜欢在森林里度过时光。
and I also love spending time in the forest myself.
对于热爱大自然的Chris和BJ来说，
For nature lovers Chris and BJ,
这一挑战似乎提供了一个完美的救赎机会。
this challenge would appear to offer the perfect chance for redemption.
比贾尼，你在搞什么鬼?呃,我…擦一根棍子?
Bjarni, what the hell are you doing? Er, I'm... Polishing a stick?
我的斧柄已经做了一半了。
I'm partway through an axe handle.
我们要让藤蔓沿着斧头向下延伸
We're going to have vines coming sort of down and around the axe,
几乎就像它在回收……杂草丛生。杂草丛生。
almost like it's reclaiming... Overgrown. Overgrown.
我有点糊涂了。那么你的展示品是什么?只是斧头吗?
I'm a bit confused. So what is your showpiece? It's just the axe?
那将是藤蔓缠绕的斧头
It'll be the axe with the vines coming around
往下走到大理石上。
and going down onto the marble.
BJ的巧克力斧头会被
BJ's chocolate axe will be surrounded by
单独的樱桃形甜点
individual cherry-shaped desserts in
这是他们拯救自己的最后一搏。
their final bid to save themselves from the chop.
这就够特别了吗?
Is that going to be extraordinary enough?
如果结果和我们想象的一样，
If it comes out the way that our vision of it is,
我觉得它会让人印象深刻。
I think it's going to look pretty impressive.
你通常不会用斧头砍樱桃，对吧?
You don't normally harvests cherries with an axe, do you?
不。我不知道，我从来没做过。
No. I don't know - I've never done it.
我们都是关于森林砍伐的!
We're all about deforestation!
自从我们在一起…＃
# Since we've been together... #
迈克尔和丽贝卡正在森林深处冒险。
Michael and Rebekah are venturing even deeper into the forest.
我们走到森林的地面上，
We sort of went like the forest floor,
有点怪异，但也很漂亮。
sort of eerie but also pretty.
我要把它刮下来，像树根一样。
I am going to shave it all down so it's like a tree root.
我们有巧克力土，巧克力蘑菇。
We have chocolate soil, chocolate mushrooms.
我们做过一次样板。有一次，在凌晨一点。
We've made the showpiece once. Once, at one o'clock in the morning.
吃披萨的时候。非常迷人。
While eating pizza. It was very glamorous.
在迈克尔扭曲的巧克力树枝下，
Beneath Michael's twisted chocolate branch,
他们的森林地面将点缀着樱桃形状的甜点
their forest floor will be dotted with cherry-shaped desserts
特色一套插入樱桃巴伐利亚酒和酸樱桃凝胶。
featuring a set insert of kirsch bavarois and a sour cherry gel.
确保结构稳定，能承受
Making sure the structure's stable and will hold -
这是最重要的部分。
that's kind of the biggest part.
没人希望它倒下!
Nobody wants it to fall over!
事实证明，野心过大导致了伊曼纽尔和萨姆的失败
Over-ambition proved to be Emmanuel and Sam's downfall
在第一个挑战中——一个他们似乎没有学到的教训。
in the first challenge - a lesson they don't seem to have learned.
因为有这么多的组成部分，我们真的必须全力以赴。
Because of so many components, we really have to go for it.
我们在做一个布谷鸟钟。
We're making a cuckoo clock.
这些会变成一个分支。
These turn into a branch.
那边那些小东西，会变成鸟的。
Those little things over there, they will turn into birds.
他们的布谷鸟钟将安放在巧克力树的树枝上。
Their cuckoo clock will nestle in the branches of a chocolate tree.
在它的下面会放上香蒂伊酱，
Beneath it will sit individual desserts filled with Chantilly,
樱桃果冻和巧克力软糖海绵蛋糕。
cherry jelly and a chocolate fudge sponge.
让事情更复杂的是，
And just to make things even more complicated,
他们的目标是让巧克力布谷鸟唱歌。
they are aiming to make their chocolate cuckoo sing.
这是一个小的机制
This is a little mechanism which is
要重现鸟叫的声音。
going to reproduce the sound of a bird.
如果不成功，就由萨姆来唱歌，
If it doesn't work, Sam will be doing the singing,
因为他的歌声比我的好。
because his singing is better than mine.
希望避免在比赛中过早出局
Hoping to avoid an early exit from the competition...
把这部分刮干净，让边缘光滑。
Just shaving that piece just to get a nice, smooth edge.
. .Darryl和Bharat正在避免任何传统的联系
..Darryl and Bharat are avoiding any conventional connection
和黑森林一起。
with the Black Forest.
我们会得到一个倾斜的长方形。
We're going to have a oblong shape, tilted.
在它上面，我们有一个圆
On the top of that, we'll have a circle
这也是一个角度。
which will also be at an angle.
非常抽象的作品，有点不同。
Very abstract piece, a bit different.
他们大胆的几何塔将提供
Their bold geometric tower will provide
背景是三个分享主菜甜点
the backdrop for three sharing entremets desserts
特色是达里尔的无蛋巧克力慕斯。
featuring Darryl's eggless chocolate mousse.
最重要的是一定要搅拌
The most important thing is to make sure you whisk it
否则你会做出颗粒状的慕斯。
otherwise you end up with a really grainy mousse.
希望它能让他们惊叹。
It should hopefully wow them.
昨天，我们以为我们会让他们大吃一惊……
Yesterday, we though we was going to wow them...
. .显然没有!
..and obviously didn't!
如果Darryl的抽象设计感觉像是
If Darryl's abstract design feels like the result of
一晚上喝樱桃酒……
a night on the kirsch...
老实说，这是相当高的风险!
It's quite a high risk, to be honest!
. .Hideko的声音听起来像是她失去理智了。
..Hideko's sounds like she may have lost her marbles.
这是孩子们非常喜欢的玩具。
It's a very popular toy for kids.
好的。在哪里，黑森林吗?
OK. Where, in the Black Forest?
在这个世界上。在这个世界上。
In the world. In the world.
两组可食用的大理石将从糖的工作滑梯上滑下来
Careering down a sugar work slide will be two sets of edible marbles
两者结合起来，
which, when combined,
将经典的黑森林风味融合在一起
should bring the classic Black Forest flavours together.
先咬一口，再咬一口。
One bite and then the other bite.
我们不应该同时吸收两个弹珠。
We are not supposed to absorb both marbles at the same time.
啊，如果你有一个大嘴巴，这是可能的。
Ah, if you have a big mouth, it's possible.
你会像仓鼠一样…!
You'll be like hamster...!
不是我说的，是你说的。
I didn't say that, you did.
还剩三小时找个地方
Three hours left to secure a place
在下一轮比赛中。
in the next round of the competition.
请小心。
Watch your backs, please.
我要开始做慕斯，然后把它冻起来。
I'm going to start building the entremets and then get it frozen.
选择大的共享甜点……
Opting for large sharing desserts...
试着把它放平。
Try and lay it on flat.
. .可以节省Darryl和Marta宝贵的时间。
..should save Darryl and Marta precious minutes.
大量的酒精会抑制你的味蕾。
Loads of alcohol, muffle those taste buds.
我希望他们不是在开车回家。
I hope they're not driving home.
但对于其他团队来说，有几十个精致的，
But for the other teams, there are dozens of delicate,
单独的甜点被组装和设置。
individual desserts to be assembled and set.
这是慕斯，这是巧克力樱桃饼干。
This is our mousse, and this is our chocolate and cherry biscuit.
我们要把它粘在一起，然后塑形。
And we're just going to stick it together and then mould it.
它就像一个大理石形状。
It's going to be like a marble shape.
我们今天会准时到的。今天，我们会准时到达。
We'll be on time today. Today, we'll be on time.
我认为我们今天取得了很好的进展。
I think we're making good progress today.
你有冷冻樱桃酱和香蒂伊奶油
You've got a frozen cherry coulis and Chantilly cream
我们要把它放进巧克力慕斯里。
that we are pushing into the chocolate mousse.
但是当西奥和克里斯的甜点准备好了…
But while Theo's and Chris' desserts are ready to begin setting...
嗯…
Hmm...
. .迈克尔和丽贝卡的都还没准备好。
..Michael and Rebekah's aren't even ready to be constructed.
他们的樱桃巴伐利亚樱桃酒的插片没能定型。
Their kirsch bavarois inserts have failed to set.
你想让我怎么做?我毁了他们。
What do you want me to do? I'm ruining them.
尽管在迷你挑战赛中表现出色…
Despite doing well in the miniature's challenge...
里面是樱桃慕斯。
So this was a kirsch mousse inside.
当我们想把它们吹胀时，有些已经碎了。
When we were trying to puff them, some were breaking.
. .米迦勒和丽贝卡的甜点秀是不会成功的。
..Michael and Rebekah's showpiece desserts aren't going to plan.
我能看出来丽贝卡很紧张
I can see that Rebekah is nervous.
像风一样奔跑。
Run like the wind.
他们正在做一个所谓的树干。
They are making a so-called tree trunk.
这可能有点极简主义。
It could be a bit minimalist.
向诸神祈祷吧。向众神祈祷，祈求好运。
Pray to the gods. Pray to the gods and hope for the best.
我们正在寻找一个宏伟的样板。
We are looking for a magnificent showpiece.
对此，我不太确定。
With this, I'm not too sure.
这种简单性也有可能发挥作用。
There is potential for that simplicity to work also.
你觉得Darryl和Bharat怎么样?
What do you think about Darryl and Bharat?
我主要担心的是无蛋慕斯。
My concern is mainly the eggless mousse.
它可能会很粘稠。
It could be very gummy and sticky.
我期待的是Hideko和Theo的组合。
The team I am looking forward to is team Hideko and Theo.
他们冒了很大的风险，
They are taking quite a bit of risk here,
但如果它成功了，那可能是令人惊叹的因素。
but if it works that may be the wow factor.
如果成功了，我就去接甜点。
If it works I will be catching the dessert.
我会帮你把它卷下来。
And I will be rolling it down for you.
你能在我检查插入时帮我换一下工作吗?
Are you free to swap jobs me a second while I check the inserts?
这就是它出错的地方。
This is the bit where it goes wrong.
大厨们，你们只剩下一个小时了。
Chefs, you have just one hour left.
今天时间过得真快。
Time is flying today.
我需要把所有的东西都喷上，然后建造。
I need to spray everything and then build.
我们把它们冻住了，我们正在处理。
We froze them, we are on it.
希望都煮熟了。
Hopefully it will all be cooked.
我把小弹珠浸在白巧克力和可可脂里。
I'm dipping the little marbles in white chocolate and cocoa butter.
把它举起来，拧成大理石的样子。
Lift it up and twist it for the marble effect.
之后我们可以玩弹珠吗?
So we can play marbles after?
是的，我会打败你的。不，你不会的。我要出发了。
Yeah, I'll beat you. No, you won't. I'm going to roll out.
我得赶紧去把这些东西冷却一下。
I've just got to go quickly blast-chill these.
这是直的吗?
Is that straight?
直吗?
Straight?
每添加一个元素…它是直的吗?
Every element added... Is it straight?
是的。
Yes.
. .给本已脆弱的关节增加了额外的压力。
..puts additional strain on already fragile joints.
现在这里真的很热
At the moment it is really hot in here
所以我不能百分之百地相信这种情况会持续下去。
so I am not 100% confident that is going to hold.
冻结。
Freeze.
我们需要把斧头装上。
We need to attach the axe.
小心,小心。
Carefully, carefully.
我们只在边缘涂巧克力吗?
Do we just chocolate the edges?
我想是的。
I think so.
填满底部。
And just fill the bottom.
天气太热了。
It's too hot.
这里太热了。
It's so BLEEP hot in here.
只剩下45分钟了……在压力下。
Just 45 minutes left... Under pressure.
. .现在，当他们试图完成他们的建筑时……
..and now while they try to complete their constructions...
我要开始上釉了。
I'm going to start glazing.
. .制作团队没有多少时间来脱模和装饰甜点了。
..the teams are running out of time to de-mould and decorate the desserts.
这些是我们的樱桃。
These are our cherries.
我们要把它们浸入深色的釉中。好的。
We're going to dip them in that dark glaze. OK.
蜘蛛釉是釉上釉，
The spider glaze is a glaze on a glaze,
创造一种网络效应。
to create a sort of web effect.
这工作。
That worked.
这里确实很暖和。
It is definitely warm in here.
还没定下来，对吧?
It's not even set yet, is it?
来吧，小家伙。集合,集合。
Come on, little one. Set, set.
哔哔声。你没意见吧?
BLEEP. Are you all right with that?
你需要帮忙吗?我需要一个帮手。
Do you need a hand? I will need a hand.
还有半小时，大厨们。最好快点。
Half an hour left, chefs. Better get a hurry on.
正确的。开始吧。
Right. Here we go.
时间飞逝，所以你必须非常专注。
Time is just flying so you have to be really focused.
你会没事的。我们开始吃甜点吧。
You will be OK. Let's get on with the dessert.
下面有点乱，他会给我们做记号的。
A bit untidy down there, he's going to mark us off on that.
这只是巧克力釉。我要加一些有光泽的粉末
This is just chocolate glaze. I'm going to add some shiny powders
在上面。你能帮我看看有没有遗漏什么吗?
on top. Can you have a look to see if I've missed anything?
这里是1和2。
One and two there.
这个很重。
This one is quite heavy.
哦,不。它不是直立的。
Oh, no. It's not stood up.
一旦我上了闪亮的釉，它们就会完全变了。
Once I put the shiny glaze on, it will change them completely.
我需要把它推进去。是的。
I need to push it in. Yes.
小心,小心。
Carefully, carefully.
对，我们得把它捡起来。
Right, we need to pick it up.
保持这种状态。你明白了吗?是的。
Keep it that way. Have you got it? Yes.
等一下，我的手指被卡住了。
Hold on, I've got my finger stuck.
就像手套一样。
Like a glove.
我要把它移到桌子上。
I'm going to move it onto the table.
滑下去一定很有趣。
It's going to be fun to slide.
它让它变成了一米。
It made it all of one metre.
正如席琳·迪翁曾经说过的，“这是认真的。”
As Celine Dion once said, "This is getting serious."
这里真的很热。
It's really hot in here.
你掉下去了。哔哔声。
You've fallen off. BLEEP.
这里太热了。
It's far too hot for this.
我现在就去试试。
I'm just going to go for it now.
更多信息在这里。
More up here.
漂亮的一个。
Nice one.
等等，等等，等等，等等。
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
好的,冻结。
OK, freeze.
好的。
OK.
我的眼镜掉下来了。
My glasses are falling off.
你还有五分钟。
You have five minutes left.
我们得在上面放点东西。
We need to start putting things on it.
你觉得你还能做更多的樱桃吗?
Do you reckon you could do more cherries?
我觉得这样更好看。
I think it actually looks better like this.
我的手太热了，巧克力都要化了。
My hands are too hot, the chocolate is just melting.
我觉得它们太重了。
I think they are too heavy.
现在把这些放在这里。
Put these on here now.
确保它们面朝同一方向。
Make sure they are facing the same way.
说下去，对，说下去。
Go on, yes, on.
迈克尔。
Michael.
天气非常热。
It's extremely hot.
大厨们，你们的时间到了。
Chefs, that is your time up.
请离开你的展品。
Please step away from your showpieces.
短短五个小时就完成了六个令人惊叹的黑森林展示。
Six breathtaking Black Forest showpieces made in just five hours.
哇。我喜欢上面的樱桃。
Wow. I love the cherry on the top.
这蛋糕太棒了。
That is an amazing cake.
这太疯狂了。
That is insane.
哔哔声。
BLEEP.
鸟推
BIRD TWEETS
他们惊奇地笑了起来
THEY LAUGH WITH AMAZEMENT
伯努瓦:他还活着吗?这太疯狂了!
BENOIT: Is he alive? That is mad!
伯努瓦:肯定有一些漂亮的小雕刻，漂亮的小触摸。
BENOIT: Definitely some nice little carving, nice little touches.
我唯一的一点遗憾是它不够明亮。
My only little regret is this is lacking brightness.
珍惜:你所有的甜点都装在一个可食用的盘子里。
CHERISH: All your dessert is plated in an edible plate.
爱死它了。而且看起来也很开胃。
Love it. And also it looks really appetising.
你考虑过我吃东西的方式，所以当我切入的时候，
You thought about how I eat so, when I cut through,
我有一个樱桃和一个果冻。
I have a cherry and I have the jelly.
巧克力慕斯在我的味蕾上融化。
The chocolate mousse just melts on my palate.
我希望你能有更多的香蒂伊。
I wish you could have just a little bit more Chantilly.
我缺少樱桃酒的元素。
I'm lacking the kirsch element.
缺乏，而不是喜欢。
Lacking, not liking.
不过，这个海绵有一种未煮熟的面粉味，
The thing with this sponge, though, there is an undercooked flour taste,
因为它很笨重，所以感觉有点干。
which, because it's clunky, it feels a bit dry.
比起味道，我更喜欢它的视觉效果。
I prefer the visual than the way it tastes like.
你知道这让我想起了什么吗?
Do you know what it reminds me of?
鱼钩。到处都是虫子，看!
A fishing hook. There's worms everywhere, look!
未完成的业务。两种:是的。
Unfinished business. BOTH: Yeah.
你的樱桃慕斯，我尝不出樱桃味。
Your cherry mousse, I can't really taste cherry.
我还觉得海绵浸透了。
And I also think that the sponge is over soaked.
只是有点湿。你有慕斯和非常柔软的巴瓦鲁丝。
It's just soggy. You've got mousse and a very soft bavaroise.
它缺少一点质感。
It's lacking a little bit of texture.
我真的很喜欢你使用的3D模具。
I really like the fact that you've used the 3D mould.
光线以不同的方式穿透
The light penetrates in different ways
这样就得到了不同的阴影。
and that gives you those different shades.
哦，你喜欢摇摆摇摆。
Oh, you like the wobbly wobbly.
是的。说明你的明胶是有控制的。
Yeah. That tells me your gelatine is controlled.
如果我移动，没有抖动，
If I move and there's no wobble,
那就说明你的蛋糕很硬。
that would tell me that your cake is solid hard.
感谢上帝赐予我黑貂，因为黑貂带来了一点
Thank God for the sable because the sable brings a little bit
还有一些更有趣的东西。
of crunch and something a little bit more interesting to play with.
这很简单，但有时少即是多。
It's very simplistic but sometimes less is more.
你肯定利用了这一点。
You've definitely used that to your advantage.
我真的很喜欢你的樱桃。
I really like your cherry.
它看起来很真实。它看起来好像很甜。
It looks so real. It looks as though it is so sweet.
我真想大吃一顿。
I really want to tuck in.
我很喜欢巧克力慕斯。
I quite like the chocolate mousse.
我觉得樱桃对我来说太酸了。
I think the cherry is so acidic for me.
樱桃元素占据了一切。
The cherry element takes over everything.
我们没有黑森林的味道。
We don't have the flavour profile of the Black Forest.
看起来不错，但当你吃的时候，
Looks good, but when you get to eat it,
你的甜点不均衡。
there is no balance in your dessert.
哔哔声。
BLEEP.
我很期待你们的互动。
I'm looking forward to the interaction.
我要把它放在这里
I'm going to place it in there
它应该一直向下，然后得到
and it should go all the way down and get
放进盘子里。是的,我希望。
into the plate. Yes, hopefully.
笑声
LAUGHTER
各就各位，准备，开始!
On your marks, get set, go!
哇!
Wow!
让我们看看吃和玩是否一样有趣。
Let's see if it is as fun to eat as it is to play.
我喜欢它。很明显，问题是，
I like it. The thing is, obviously,
你必须一次吃一点
you have to have little bits at a time
但我可以把两块碎片拼在一起
but I can put two little pieces together.
樱桃酒的元素将黑森林凝聚在一起，所以它成功了。
The kirsch element brings the Black Forest together so it works.
我认为这真的很有趣。
I think it's really fun.
我还会再来一次吗?
Would I come back for another?
也许是为了好玩，但不是为了味道。
Perhaps for the fun but not for the taste.
酒太多了，我不喜欢。
The alcohol is just too much for my liking.
两半场比赛。
A game of two halves.
干得好，谢谢。谢谢你！
Well done, thank you. Thank you.
它是可以修复的，对吗?
It can be repaired, right?
它是圆的，它是方的，它是圆的……
It's round, it's Square, it's round...
. .它仍然是方的。
..and it's still square.
一切都是实实在在的，这对我来说很苛刻。
Everything is really solid, it's very harsh for me.
如果这是对几何形状的挑战，
If it would have been a challenge on geometrical shapes,
是的，我明白了。
yes, I got that.
好的。我有很浓的酒味。
OK. I've got a strong alcohol flavour.
海绵浸透了，所以质地很软，糊状。
The sponge has over soaked, so a very soft, mushy texture.
我想再咬一口。
I would love a little bit more bite.
巧克力慕斯有点紧，感觉不太顺滑，
And the chocolate mousse is kind of tight, it doesn't feel smooth,
就味道而言，它…
and, flavour wise, it's...
. .不够强。
..not strong enough.
我还希望你只用纯食材呢。
I was wishing that you just used pure ingredients.
简单的事情有时也可以如此美好。
Simple things sometimes can be so beautiful.
你做什么都加太多明胶了。
You add in too much gelatine in everything.
当我这样做的时候，这对我不好。
When I do this, this is bad for me.
那里的一切都不对。我很抱歉。
Everything is just not right in there. I'm so sorry.
哦,男人。哦,不。
Oh, man. Oh, no.
没关系。
It's OK.
他抽泣
HE SOBS
根据他们在两项挑战中的表现，
Based on their performance on both challenges,
Benoit和珍惜现在将对球队进行排名，最后一名的球队将进行排名
Benoit and Cherish will now rank the teams and those in last place will
不得不退出竞争。
have to leave the competition.
这也是对展品的影响。
It's the impact as well on the showpiece.
我们热爱我们的工作。事实上，我们非常有激情。
We love what we do. In fact, we're extremely passionate.
就像挨了一枪。
It was like taking a bullet.
现在，有很多工作要做吗?也许不是。
Now, is there a lot of work in it? Maybe not.
我们昨天过得很糟糕。
We had a really bad day yesterday.
今天还不错。
Today wasn't so bad.
其他球队的情况正好相反，所以……
Other teams have had the reverse of that, so...
这很难说。
It's difficult to say.
Benoit和珍惜已经做出了决定。
Benoit and Cherish have made their decision.
评委们认为第一名的队伍是最稳定的
The judges thought the team in first place were the most consistent
跨越这两个挑战。
across both challenges.
恭喜你……
Congratulations...
. .希尔顿公园巷的伊曼纽尔和山姆。
..Emmanuel and Sam from Hilton Park Lane.
掌声
APPLAUSE
并列第二的是玛尔塔和朱莉，迈克尔和丽贝卡。
In joint second place were Marta and Julie, and Michael and Rebekah.
和他们一起进入下一轮比赛的，是第四名的Hideko和Theo。
And, joining them in the next round, are Hideko and Theo in fourth place.
这样一来，名胜世界的达里尔和巴拉特，
Which leaves Darryl and Bharat from Resorts World,
还有沃伦酒店的克里斯和比贾尼。
and Chris and Bjarni from The Warren.
经过深思熟虑，今晚离开我们的队伍是……
After much deliberation, the team leaving us tonight are...
. .Chris和Bjarni。
..Chris and Bjarni.
恭喜你们，我们下周见。
Congratulations to the rest of you, we'll see you next week.
看到别人离开会很难受。
It would have been hard to see someone else go.
在某种程度上，我很高兴是我们，但同时也很糟糕。
In a way, I am pleased it's us but it also sucks at the same time.
BENOIT: Darryl !
BENOIT: Darryl!
他吹口哨
HE WHISTLES
他们必须看到我们有更多的东西可以提供。
They must see that we've got a little bit more to offer.
能让我流泪的东西，你知道，只是说明它意义重大。
For something to reduce me to tears, you know, just shows it means a lot.
伊曼纽尔,拥抱。
Emmanuel, cuddles.
干得好，伙计。下周，新的挑战。
Well done, man. Next week, new challenge.
我想我们将从明天开始做这件事。
We will work on it from tomorrow, I suppose.
或周一。我们至少休息一天吧。休息半天。
Or Monday. Let's have a day off at least. Half a day off.
我来找你们了，山姆和伊曼纽尔。小心点，好吗?
I'm coming for you, Sam and Emanuel. Look out, yeah?
下次……派对时间!
Next time... Party time!
. .竞争越来越激烈……
..the competition gets hotter...
噢!噢!噢!
Ooh! Ooh! Ooh!
. .用两个看似简单的微缩模型。
..with two deceptively simple miniatures.
它了!和一个经典的法国样板…
It cracked! And a classic French showpiece...
这是新的、现代的款式。
It's the new, modern style.
. .适合最隆重的场合。
..Fit for the grandest occasion.
但哪四支球队能存活下来呢?
But which four teams will survive?
哇，哇，哇!还有她的法式蛋糕梦……
Whoa, whoa, whoa! And whose patisserie dreams...
它有一吨重!. .会崩溃吗?
It weighs a tonne! ..will come crashing down?
她声称
SHE EXCLAIMS
我感到很兴奋。谢谢你！
I'm excited. Thank you.
字幕由红蜂传媒制作
Subtitles by Red Bee Media
利亚姆，我喜欢我们在乡下的新生活。
Oh, Liam, I just love our new life in the countryside.
那肯定不是哈克尼，对吧?
Well, it's definitely not Hackney, is it?
新鲜的空气，小羊在田野里奔跑，在花园里喝茶!
Fresh air, lambs running through the fields, taking tea in the garden!
只是这里的生活节奏不一样。
Oh, it's just a different pace of life down here.
手表发出哔哔声哦，汤姆。看看时间，
WATCH BEEPS Oh, Tom. Look at the time,
我们第一个挑战要迟到了。
we're gonna be late for the first challenge.
哦,不!哦，不，我们不能让那些法官等着!
Oh, no! Oh, no, we mustn't keep those judges waiting!
哦，他们太可怕了。
Oh, they're so terrifying.
加油，汤姆!是的…
Come on, Tom! Yeah...
汤姆!耶，我来了，耶!
Tom! Yeah, I'm coming, yeah!
我来了，我来了!是啊!
I'm coming, I'm coming! Yeah!
汤姆!对不起，利亚姆!
Tom! Sorry, Liam, yeah!
塞满东西:是的，我们不能让他们等。
MOUTH FULL: Yeah, we mustn't keep them waiting.
在这场最艰难的烘焙大赛中，有12支才华横溢的蛋糕师队伍
In this toughest of Bake-Offs, 12 talented teams of patissiers
正在竞争英国最佳专业糕点师的称号。
are vying to be named Britain's best professional pastry chefs.
后退，后退，后退，后退!我现在觉得自己像毕加索。
Back, back, back, back! I feel like Picasso now, you know.
最后一次……
Last time...
哇!. .我们的前六支球队……这太可怕了。
Wow! ..our first six teams... This is terrifying.
. .突然惊醒。
..got a rude awakening.
哔哔声。现在，孩子们，我们落后了。
BLEEP. Now, boys, we're behind.
我们需要调整。
We need to adjust.
伊曼纽尔和萨姆表现出色。
Emmanuel and Sam excelled.
干得好，大厨。我惊呆了。
Well done, chef. I'm blown away.
达瑞尔和巴拉特的信心受到了打击。
Darryl and Bharat's confidence took a knock.
哔哔声。它没有什么特别的地方。
BLEEP. It doesn't go anywhere special.
有点平。他抽泣
It's a bit flat. HE SOBS
没关系的。
It's all right.
但是Chris和Bjarni的轻松方法…
But Chris and Bjarni's relaxed approach...
我感觉出奇的平静。
I'm feeling weirdly calm.
. .让他们被淘汰了。
..got them axed from the competition.
太无聊了，太无聊了，我不喜欢。
It's dull, it's boring, it's not to my liking.
现在…快，快，快，快，快!
Now... Go, go, go, go, go!
. .团队必须重新发明两种经典布丁
..the teams must reinvent two classic puddings...
啊!我把它卷起来的时候它裂开了一点。
Ah! It cracked a little bit as I was rolling it.
. .作为尖端的微缩模型。
..as cutting-edge miniatures.
它们有毒吗?如果你有太多。
Are they poisonous? If you have it too much.
改变传统的法国婚礼中心…
And transform a traditional French wedding centrepiece...
它们有那么大吗?
They're meant to be that big?
我不知道正确答案是什么!
I don't know what the right answer is!
变成了21世纪的展示品
..into a 21st century showpiece...
哔哔声。重达一吨……规模巨大。
BLEEP. Weighs a ton. ..on a monumental scale.
我们开始吧。顶，顶，顶。
Let's do this. Top, top, top.
哪四个队能坚持到底?
Which four teams will stick it out?
哔哔声。
BLEEP.
谁会崩溃?
And who will fall apart?
一点压力都没有。
No pressure at all.
别哭了。
Don't cry.
准备好了吗?
Ready?
我永远都是!
As I'll ever be!
当我们收到像上周这样的评论时，我们很伤心。确实很疼。
When we get comments like last week, it hurts. It does hurt, yeah.
这确实让你有点吃不消，但你已经
It does knock you back a bit, but you've just got
回来战斗。
to come back fighting.
显然，我们是并列第二，所以我们一定做对了什么。
Obviously, we came joint second, so we must have done something right.
所以希望我们这周也能做得更好。
So hopefully we can do the same, if not better, this week.
回到游戏中。
Back in the game.
我们今天要试一下诱惑。
We're gonna try seduction today.
带珍爱去吃饭，她带伯努瓦去喝酒，
Take Cherish for dinner, she take Benoit for a drink,
这就是我们今天的策略!
and then that's our strategy today!
需要进入状态。
Need to get in the zone.
早上好，厨师们，欢迎回到厨房。
Good morning, chefs, and welcome back to the kitchen.
我们今天五岁了。
We are five today.
但到明天结束时，只剩下4只。
But by the end of tomorrow, only four will remain.
没错，你们中的一个会被淘汰。
That's right - one of you will be eliminated.
像最弱小的羚羊一样被干掉
Picked off like the weakest gazelle
被两只非常饥饿，爱吃糕点的狼。
by two very hungry, pastry loving wolves.
其中一个碰巧带着一把尺子。
One of whom happens to be carrying a ruler.
今天，我们从多层切片开始。
Today, we begin with multiple layered slices.
评委想让你做两种分层切片，
And the judges would like you to make two types of layered slice,
每种24个。
24 of each.
你选了什么?
So what have you chosen?
我选了提拉米苏切片。
I've chosen tiramisu slice.
它必须展示经典的咖啡风味，包括手指松糕。
It must showcase classic coffee flavour, including ladyfinger.
我选了果仁卷，
Well, I've chosen the roulade praline slice,
哪个必须至少有两种不同的馅料
which must have at least two different filling
还有坚果的味道。
and feature a nutty flavour.
要有创意，但不要忘记
Be creative, but don't forget -
我们希望看到所有切片上整齐干净的层。
we want to see neat, clean layers across all your slices.
大厨们，你们有3.5小时的时间
So, chefs, you have 3.5 hours
完成48个完美的分层切片。
to complete 48 perfectly layered slices.
你的时间开始了……
And your time starts...
现在. . !
..now!
我先把榛子烤一下，好吗?
I'm gonna put the hazelnuts to roast first, OK?
在分层切片中，每个元素都是可见的。
In a layered slice, every single element is visible.
因此，要想取得成功，两支球队必须结合各自的天赋
So to succeed, the teams must combine flair
将风味和质地完美结合
in marrying flavours and textures with precision
将它们的组件分层。
in layering their components.
伯努瓦选择用经典的，
And Benoit has chosen to try the teams with a classic,
以法语单词“滚”命名，也就是roulade。
named after the French word "to roll" - the roulade.
法国人的经典卷饼
The classical roulade for a French person
是传统的圣诞原木。
is the traditional Christmas log.
当我还是学徒的时候，我们一起度过了最后一周
When I was an apprentice, we were spending the last week
在圣诞节前每天都这样做。
before Christmas doing these every single day.
哦，我非常喜欢。
Oh, I like it very much.
你可以使用很多海绵，
There are many sponges you can use,
任何能给你一点弹性的海绵。
any sponge which will give you a little bit of elasticity.
但是滚球的技术性在于能否滚球
But the technicality of the roulade is being able to roll it
漂亮的圆形。你不会想要卷成方形的。
nice and circular. You don't want the roulade to go squarish.
这在国内可能会被接受，但这是一场比赛。
It may be accepted at home, but this is a competition.
你将无处可藏。
There will be nowhere to hide.
山姆和伊曼纽尔，你们好吗?
Sam and Emmanuel, how are you doing?
早上好,先生们。早上好。
Morning, gentlemen. Good morning.
上周的获奖者们，你们感到压力了吗?
Last week's winners, are you feeling the pressure?
是的，我们有。你能跟我们谈谈你的行程吗?
Yes, we do. Would you be able to talk to us about your roulade?
我们保留了基本的成分。
We kept the basic ingredients.
我们把它保留了下来，差不多就是这样了。
We kept it round, and that's more or less everything.
所以你在某种程度上解构了它?
So you deconstruct it in a way?
是的，我们做到了。
Yeah, we did.
利亚姆:在伦敦的希尔顿公园巷酒店，
LIAM: At the Hilton Park Lane Hotel in London,
突破糕点界的界限是一种基本的精神
pushing the boundaries of patisserie is an essential ethos
伊曼纽尔和山姆的作品
of Emmanuel and Sam's work.
他们的前卫之旅，伊曼纽尔和山姆将
For their avant-garde roulade, Emmanuel and Sam will be
包裹着一层又一层的榛子蛋糕，
encasing layers of hazelnut dacquoise,
牛轧糖和国语果冻，
nougatine and Mandarin jelly,
榛子巧克力慕斯。
in a hazelnut chocolate mousse.
然而，他们遗漏了
However, they're omitting
一个值得注意的因素
one notable element
正常的卷饼。
of a normal roulade.
我们不要拐弯抹角了。
Let's not beat around the bush.
在你的旋转中有任何漩涡运动吗?
Is there any swirl movement within your roulade?
不像卷饼，是一圈一圈又一圈的。
It's not like the roulade, which is round and round and round.
所以我们让你做旋转，但你说，“你知道吗，
So we ask you to do roulade, but you say, "You know what,
“真该死……”不，不，不。“不要再跳了，我们不跳了。”
"sod it..." No, no, no, no. "No more roulade, we're not doing a roulade."
我们保留了层的概念。所以没有漩涡?
We kept the idea of the layers. So there is no swirl?
伯努瓦，求你放手吧!
Benoit, please let it go!
哦，天哪，天哪。
Oh, dear, dear.
很明显，对法官来说，我们的动作有点过了。
Our touch is a bit too much, obviously, for the judge.
这是……好的。
That's... OK.
我觉得他们觉得我们有点太冒险了。
I'm under the impression they think we're a bit too adventurous.
他们现在说什么都不会影响我们。
Whatever they say now doesn't really affect us.
我们必须尝试做一些与众不同的事情。
We've got to try and do something different from everybody else.
这是你赢的唯一办法。
It's the only way you're gonna win.
勉强通过最后一轮后……
After scraping through the last round...
你想尝尝这个吗?
Do you wanna just taste this?
更多的果仁糖。是的。
More praline. Yeah.
. .达里尔和巴拉特决定见面
..Darryl and Bharat are determined to meet
评委们的批评是正面的。
the judges' criticisms head on.
上周，我们认为他们会喜欢这些味道，
Last week, we thought they would have loved the flavours,
但显然他们没有。我们今天要给他们留下深刻印象。
but obviously they didn't. We're here to impress them today.
我们只是在执行任务。
We're just on a mission, basically.
我们会做到的。我们能行的，我们能行的!
We will do it. We can do it, we can do it!
跆拳道黑带，
A black belt in tae kwon do,
队长达里尔对被击倒并不陌生
team captain Darryl is no stranger to getting knocked down
然后回来战斗。
and coming back fighting.
他会用白巧克力榛子酱
He'll use a white chocolate hazelnut whip
再来一杯牛奶巧克力奶油
and a milk chocolate cream
创建一个双色填充
to create a two-tone filling
对于他的joconde海绵，
to his joconde sponge,
他会用香草和榛子调味。
which he'll flavour with vanilla and hazelnut.
因为坚果里的油，
Because of the oils in the nut,
它使它在滚动时很有弹性，不应该开裂。
it makes it quite elastic when it comes to rolling, shouldn't crack.
弹性可以帮助厨师做出想要的卷形。
Elasticity will help the chefs to achieve the desired roulade shape.
好吗?我很好，你呢?
OK? Yeah, I'm good, you?
是的,很好。但说到口感，
Yeah, good. But when it comes to texture,
Hideko和Theo希望他们的海绵能更上一层楼。
Hideko and Theo are hoping to take their sponge to the next level.
蛋糕部分是蛋奶酥底，就像松软的海绵蛋糕。
The cake part is a souffle base, like a fluffy, soft sponge cake.
这听起来像我以前做的日本海绵…
This sounds like the Japanese sponge I used to make...
完全正确!啊，我也这么想!
Exactly! Ah, I thought so!
英子15年前从日本来到英国
Hideko came to the UK from Japan 15 years ago
成为一名糕点师，她和一些
to become a pastry chef, and she's worked with some of the
英国烹饪界的大腕。
biggest names in British cuisine.
戈登·拉姆齐的第一副厨，
First sous-chef to Gordon Ramsay,
之后是赫斯顿·布卢门撒尔
and after this, Heston Blumenthal.
哔哔声。
BLEEP.
Hideko的日式蛋奶酥海绵
Hideko's Japanese souffle sponge
会用榛子奶油分层吗
will be layered with hazelnut cream
还有切碎的焦糖榛子。
and chopped caramelised hazelnuts.
她还加了香蒂伊奶油
She's also adding a Chantilly cream
沉浸在小说里
infused with a novel
甜点的味道。
dessert flavour.
因为这显然是一个插入，我需要冻结它
Cos this is obviously an insert, I need this to be frozen
然后尽快放入慕斯。
as soon as possible to then go inside the mousse.
这些会直接进入爆炸。
These are gonna go straight in the blast.
当山姆和伊曼纽尔的卷饼被放入冷冻机时…
While Sam and Emmanuel's roulade goes in the blast chiller...
快，快，快!
Go, go, go!
朱莉，我们准备好了…剩下的就可以放进烤箱了。
Julie, we're ready. ..the rest are ready to go in the oven.
我要做八层，看看效果如何。
I'll do eight layers and see how it comes out.
烤海绵卷的时间很关键。
The bake time for the roulade sponge is crucial.
我的是10。
I'm putting mine ten.
记得关上门的时候还有七分钟吗?
Remember it's on seven minutes when you close the door, yeah?
在烤箱里烤太久，海绵卷起来就会破裂，
Too long in the oven and the sponge will crack when it's rolled,
这样就不可能得到最重要的螺旋了。
making it impossible to get the all-important spiral.
祈祷!
Fingers crossed!
用海绵烤……
With sponges baking...
40分钟了。
40 minutes in.
. .是时候填馅了。
..it's on to fillings.
哔哔声。
BLEEP.
玛尔塔和朱莉在他们的节目中加入了危险的暗示。
And Marta and Julie are spicing theirs with a hint of danger.
我准备了汤卡豆泡奶油，
I've got my Tonka bean infused cream in there,
然后我就可以把它加到巧克力酱里了。
so then I can add it to the ganache.
唐卡豆有毒吗?
Tonka beans, are they poisonous?
如果你吃太多，它们是有毒的。
If you have it too much, they are poisonous.
杀人需要多少钱?
How much would you need to kill somebody?
我在找一个朋友。我不知道。
I'm asking for a friend. I don't know.
球队队长玛尔塔在拉夫堡开了一家糕点店
Team captain Marta opened Bom Bom Patisserie in Loughborough
两年前，
two years ago,
从生物学家转到面包师之后。
following a career switch from biologist to baker.
她的榛子松糕
Her hazelnut joconde sponge will be
装满了两个甘纳许
filled with two ganaches -
一个是榛子鞭子，
one, a hazelnut whip,
另一个是她的巧克力和唐卡豆。
the other, her chocolate and tonka bean.
这是你看到的质地吗?
Is this the texture that you're looking at?
看，那部分不光滑。
See, that bit is not smooth.
好的。我要让你自己纠正。
OK. I'm gonna let you rectify it yourself.
嗯，没什么压力。
Mm, nothing stressful about that.
Michael和Rebekah唯一感受到的压力是…
The only stress Michael and Rebekah are feeling...
他们唱
THEY SING
. .在他们的声带上。
..is on their vocal cords.
我们更像是一对老夫老妻，你不觉得吗?
We're definitely more like an old married couple, do you not think?
对，分床睡。是啊，就是这样一对夫妻!
Yeah, separate beds. Yeah, that kind of a married couple!
迈克尔和丽贝卡做了九年的朋友
Friends for nine years, Michael and Rebekah have spent
最后两个人在圣大卫酒店并肩工作
the last two working side-by-side at the St David's Hotel
在卡迪夫。
in Cardiff.
服务,请。
Service, please.
迈克尔的榛子巧克力海绵蛋糕
Michael's hazelnut Pain de Genes sponge
会被黑巧克力釉覆盖吗
will be covered with a dark chocolate glaze
里面装满了果仁巧克力酱
and filled with praline ganache
还有香蕉慕斯。
and a banana mousse.
我们做了香蕉慕斯，用保鲜膜包起来
We've made the banana mousse, rolled it in clingfilm
来制造又长又细的管子……会有一点点
to make really long, thin tubes... There'll be a little bit of
当你切开它的时候，里面会有惊喜。
a surprise inside when you slice it open.
所以这可能是获胜的板凳?
So this could be the winning bench?
联合第二。你唯一能走的路是更高……
Joint second. The only way you can go is higher...
我们要第一!就是这样。
We want first! That's it.
所以插入物被摩丝包围
So the insert's surrounded by the mousse
然后我要在它的底部放一个底。
and then I'm gonna have a base to go on the bottom of it.
那得剪小一点。
That'll need to be cut a little bit smaller.
大厨们，你们还有两个小时。
Chefs, you have two hours left.
两个小时。
Two hours.
希望我们在轨道上!
We are on track, hopefully!
不会比上周更糟了。
Can't be worse than last week.
还有两个小时，对吧?是的,是的。
Two hours to go, yeah? Yeah, yeah.
在爆炸中度过一个半小时是很好的。
It's good to get a good hour and a half in the blast.
希尔顿的游行队伍可能已经组装好了……
The Hilton's roulade may already be assembled...
定时器哔哔声对，就是我们。
TIMER BEEPS Right, that's us.
. .但对其他人来说，他们的首要任务是得到
..but for everyone else, their priority is getting
他们的海绵刚出炉…
their sponges is out of the oven...
热托盘在这里。是的。
Hot tray here. Yeah.
热，热，热。
Hot, hot, hot.
. .冷却到可以填充和卷起来。
..and cool enough to fill and roll.
进去吧，姑娘!
Get in there, girl!
照这样下去，我们有时间喝杯茶了!
We'll have time for a cuppa at this rate!
也就是说，如果这批完美的面包卷要求不够高，
That is, if the batch of perfect roulades wasn't demanding enough,
团队还需要创建他们的第二层切片。
the teams also need to create their second layered slice.
嗯，你可能认为提拉米苏很容易做
Well, you might think that tiramisu is easy to make
因为它随处可见。
because you can see it everywhere.
然而，要做到这一点太难了。
However, it is just so difficult to get right.
松糕海绵蛋糕必须烤得完美，
The ladyfinger sponge must be baked to perfection,
这样它们就能吸收所有美丽浓郁的咖啡糖浆。
so that they can soak up all the beautiful, intense coffee syrup.
我不想看到没有泡过的海绵，那样会很干。
I do not want to see an unsoaked sponge, it would be so dry.
然后是漂亮柔滑的马斯卡彭奶酪。
Then a beautiful, silky mascarpone cream.
用适量的明胶保持它的形状。
Use just enough gelatine to hold its form.
太多明胶了，你能想象吗?
Too much gelatine, can you imagine?
这可能看起来很简单，但它需要完美。
It might seem simple, but it needs to be perfect.
西奥正在为甜蜜艺术实验室制作提拉米苏。
Theo is creating the tiramisu for Sweet Art Lab.
希望我们能继续看到那些山脉，
We're gonna hopefully keep seeing all those, like, mountains,
所以我们要把形状弄直。
so we have to be really straight with our shaping.
厨房里的人，
Word round the kitchen,
你从来没做过提拉米苏。
you've actually never made a tiramisu before.
不完全是。如果我祖父母听到了，他们会杀了我的，
Not exactly. If my grandparents hear me, they'll kill me,
因为他们是意大利人，喜欢提拉米苏。
because they're Italian and love tiramisu.
那是什么?
What's that?
它对你有用吗?
Does it work with you?
你真性感。
You're pretty hot.
他们笑了
THEY LAUGH
如果你要做提拉米苏，你首先要做的就是
If you're making a tiramisu, the first thing you want
被咖啡击中。
to be hit with is coffee.
但厨师们如何引入咖啡的味道可能是关键。
But how the chefs introduce the coffee flavour could prove key.
那是你能找到的最好的咖啡。
That is the finest coffee you can find.
这是雀巢速溶咖啡。
It's Nescafe instant coffee.
咖啡利口酒给你咖啡，
Coffee liqueur to give you that coffee,
但只要喝一点酒，就会有很大的刺激。
but a little bit of alcohol, plenty of alcohol kick.
那将是一个……
That'll be one...
基本上，我们会把它们都放进去。
Basically, we'll put it all in.
一瓶半。
Bottle and a half.
派对时间!
Party time!
小手指准备好了。
Ladyfinger is ready.
我对我的手指松饼很满意。
I'm pretty happy with my ladyfingers.
又脆又干，能吸收咖啡利口酒的味道。
They're crisp, they're dry, so it actually absorbs the coffee liqueur.
我觉得海绵干的时候会很不舒服。
I think the sponge when it's dry, it can be quite unpleasant.
也不能浸泡太久，
You can't soak it too much as well,
否则你的酒吧就不能正常运作了?
otherwise your bar is not going to hold straight, you know?
很难找到适量的糖浆。
It's quite hard to find the right amount of syrup to put.
这都是我第三次灌满这瓶了，
This is like the third time I've refilled this bottle,
所以它占据了相当多的空间。
so it has taken up quite a lot.
我在准备马斯卡朋慕斯的原料。
I'm preparing the ingredients for the mascarpone mousse.
250.
往马斯卡彭奶酪里加明胶
Adding gelatine to the mascarpone
会帮助他们的切片保持形状。
will help their slices keep their shape.
你的马斯卡彭鞭子怎么样了?
How's your mascarpone whip coming out, nice?
哦，是的，很好。
Oh, yeah, it's good.
但太多的话，厨师就会失去奶油味
But too much and the chefs will lose the creaminess Cherish
正在寻找。
is looking for.
我要用迷你秤，这样更精确。
I've got to use a mini scale, which is a touch more precise.
不满足于解构面包卷……
Not content with deconstructing the roulade...
不，我也没见过这样的卷饼。
No, I don't think I've ever seen a roulade like this either.
. .伊曼纽尔和山姆也在改造提拉米苏
..Emmanuel and Sam are also reinventing the tiramisu
通过添加一个不寻常的元素。
by adding an unusual element.
咖啡果冻。
Coffee jelly.
把它放在海绵的顶部，然后我们就有了这一层
It's got to go on the top of the sponge, then we have the layer
马斯。
of mascarpone.
萨姆，我们还能准时吗?不知道。这很好。
Sam, how are we doing on time? No idea. That's good.
每一层都需要在放置下一层之前设置好。
Each layer needs to be set before you put the next thing.
如果没有很好地定型，你就不能切得很干净，
If it's not set nicely, you can't get a clean cut,
我们都知道珍爱喜欢漂亮干净的发型。
and we all know Cherish loves a nice, clean cut.
这是马斯卡朋奶酪的第一层。
This is the first layer of the mascarpone.
又平又漂亮，是吧?第二层小手指饼干。
Nice and flat, eh? Second layer of ladyfinger biscuit.
需要尽快把它放进冰箱。
Need to have it as as soon as possible in the freezer.
现在有点吃力，我得把这些塞进去。
Bit of a push now, I need to get these in.
我现在要去冷冻机那里。
I'm going to the blast chiller now.
是的,是的。
Yeah, yeah.
朱莉，朱莉，我们有麻烦了。
Julie, Julie, we're gonna have a problem.
这个大托盘放不下。
That big tray doesn't fit in here.
没关系，我把它放在冰箱里。
That's fine, I'll put it in the freezer.
选择模具的时间太长了，
Having chosen moulds too long for the blast freezer,
朱莉把它们放在普通的冰箱里。
Julie puts them in a normal freezer.
但现在她的提拉米苏需要更长的时间来定型。
But now her tiramisu will take longer to set.
哦,好吧。我们现在也无能为力了，对吧?
Oh, well. Not a lot we could do about it now, is there?
大厨们，你们还有半小时。
Chefs, you have half an hour left.
半小时，Hideko。是的。
Half an hour, Hideko. Yeah.
我在准备卷饼。
Just getting the roulades ready to roll.
那又回来了!它回来了，宝贝。
That is back! It's back baby.
巧克力酱又回来了!
Ganache is back!
要把图层分开，因为擀面的时候，
Just gonna get my layers separated, because when you roll it,
不管怎样，它会推动整个过程。
it's gonna push it altogether, anyway.
关键时刻。
Pivotal moment.
Crucial moment.
开始滚动。
Start rolling.
这是香蕉慕斯。
This is the banana mousse.
它会粘在中间。
It'll stick in the centre.
这样，当你滚动的时候，你可以保持它很好很紧。
That way, when you're rolling, you can keep it nice and tight.
啊。
Ah.
他们看到我在打滚，他们就恨我。
They see me rollin', they hatin'.
他们看到我在翻滚……＃
# They see me rollin'... #
对不起,厨师。
Sorry, chef.
哦，啦，啦。
Oh, la, la.
在烤箱里烤太久了，太干了。
It stayed too long in the oven, it's too dry.
我卷的时候它有点裂，但螺旋还是有的。
It cracked a little bit as I was rolling it, but the spiral's there.
你想把它冷却到哪里?冰箱。
Where do you want this chilling to? Freezer.
完美。在冷风机里很快就会熟了。
Perfection. It's gonna go quickly in the blast chiller.
可以切片，但如果温度再低一点，效果会更好。
It's sliceable, but you'll get a better finish if it's cooler.
试着把下一层硅去掉。
Try and take the next layer of silicon off.
现在冻得更快了。
It's gonna freeze even quicker now.
我们的时间不多了。
We haven't got that much longer.
提拉米苏刚从冰箱里拿出来。
The tiramisu has just come out of the chiller.
我们要在上面撒点可可粉。
We're just gonna dust it with a bit of cocoa powder.
它们已经凝固在上面，准备上釉了。
They've set on top, ready for the glaze.
加热一下，这样我就可以把提拉米苏从模具里拿出来了。
Just heating it up, so I can take the tiramisu out of the mould.
你可别把它烧过了头
Got to make sure you don't over blowtorch it
因为它可以融化侧面。
cos it can actually melt the sides.
哦,哦!朱莉，朱莉，朱莉!哦。
Oh, oh! Julie, Julie, Julie! Oh.
洞里有火!
Fire in the hole!
这是关键时刻。
This is the crucial moment.
看看这一层是不是直的。
See all the layer and if it's straight or not.
哦，别这样。
Oh, come on.
请不要那样做。
Don't do that, please.
压力。评委们肯定会很严厉，
Pressure on. Judges are gonna be tough for sure,
所以一定要做到完美。
so have to be perfect.
完成了。快乐吗?
Done. Happy?
我想是的。完美的。
I think so. Perfect.
看起来不错。这就是我想要的，清晰可见的图层。
It looks all right. That's what I wanted, the layer I can clearly see.
说实话，我对此很满意。
I'm pretty happy with this, to be honest.
分层很好，不是吗?
Layers are good, eh?
还是软的吗?是的。
Is that still soft? Yeah.
我想把它从模子里拿出来，这样我就可以把它放回去了
I want to get it out of the mould so I can get it back in
冷冻室。好，你就这么做了。
the blast freezer. OK, so you do that.
大厨们，你们还有十分钟。
Chefs, you have ten minutes left.
我们还有十分钟。
We've got ten minutes.
要开始分装了。
Gonna start to portion up.
尽量让它保持干净。
Try to keep it as clean as you can.
把它翻转过来，把它折起来，
By turning it on its side and having it doubled up,
现在只用一半的时间就做好了六层。
you've now got six layers in half the time.
这是一块很厚的海绵。
It's quite a thick sponge.
可能有点涨得太大了。
It's risen maybe a little bit too much.
看起来有点方。
It's looking a bit square.
哦，我明白你的意思了。它是替代。
Oh, I see what you mean. It's alternative.
我们只希望它尝起来好吃。
We just hope that it'll taste good.
我正在为舞会做装饰。
Just making the decor for the roulade now.
我需要稍微冷却一下。
I need to cool it down a little bit.
如果太热，它就不会像这样掉下来。
If it's too hot, it's not gonna do the drop like that.
你还好吗，Darryl?有个麻烦的切片。
Are you all right, Darryl? Got a troublesome slice.
我在想它们会不会待在温暖的地方。
Just wondering if they're gonna stay where they are in the warmth.
它很软。
It's very soft.
还是软的吗?
Is that still soft?
继续切，我来把它切完，好吗?
Keep on cutting it and I'll finish this off, OK?
我们还有多长时间?
How long do we have?
大厨们，你们还有五分钟，五分钟。
Chefs, you have five minutes, five minutes left.
哎呀，这一拳打中了指关节。
Crikey, this one's to the knuckle.
坚持到最后，最后一分钟。是的。
Go to the end, last minute. Yeah.
不过它下得真快。
It's really setting quick, though.
小心你的背。热,热。
Mind your back. Hot, hot.
我在用马斯卡彭奶酪做罗谢尔奶酪。
I'm doing some rochelles with some mascarpone.
我的收尾还可以再好一点，但现在就是这样。
My finishing could be a bit better, but it is where it is right now.
啊,啊。
Ah, ah.
你还好吗?
You OK there?
我们在噼啪作响吗?继续，汤米。
Are we crackalackin'? Rock on, Tommy.
需要加快工作速度。
Need to work faster.
4,8,12,16,20。
4, 8, 12, 16, 20.
我们需要再加四个。
We need to get another four on.
我们会及时完成的，总会有结果的。
We'll get it done in time, something will come out.
大厨们，你们还有一分钟!
Chefs, you have one minute left!
哔哔声。一分钟。
BLEEP. One minute.
我可能需要点推动力，达瑞尔。
I might need a bit of a push, Darryl.
我一穿上巧克力，就来找你。
Soon as I get my chocolate on, I'll be with you.
你在做巧克力吗?我在做巧克力。
Are you doing the chocolate? I'm doing the chocolate.
先把饼干拿过来。
Just get the biscuit first.
我们开始吧。
Let's do this.
时间到了，大厨们!
Time's up, chefs!
离你的手指远点。
Step away from your ladyfingers.
哦!谢天谢地总算结束了。我们只希望他们能熬夜。
Oh! Thank God that's over. Let's just hope they stay up.
也许把它放下。
Maybe lay it down, yeah.
太可怕了。
That was horrendous.
参赛队伍现在必须展示他们的48层切片
The teams must now present their 48 layered slices
有请评委Benoit和珍惜
to judges Benoit and Cherish.
名胜世界的Darryl和Bharat，
Darryl and Bharat from Resorts World,
你能过来一下吗?
could you please come forward?
所以，你的面包卷。
So, your roulade.
我喜欢你的努力
I like the fact that you have tried
用你的两种馅料做一个图案。
to do a pattern with your two fillings.
总的来说，我认为这看起来有点粗暴。
As a whole, I think it looks a little bit heavy-handed.
最大的错误是海绵的厚度。
The biggest mistake is the thickness of your sponge.
但我喜欢你的馅料。
But I like the texture of your filling.
我得到了对比，这实际上是令人愉快的。
I've got contrast, and it's actually pleasant.
来看看你的提拉米苏切片。
Well, let's look at your tiramisu slice.
我真的很喜欢那种小小的心灵抚摸。
I really like the small touch of the heart.
这有什么意义吗?
Is there any meaning to it?
只是纯粹的爱。
Just pure love.
你一个，你一个。
Aw, one from you and one from you.
嗯…我觉得它尝起来确实像提拉米苏。
Well...I think it does taste like a tiramisu.
唷!
Phew!
我很喜欢你放进去的咖啡糖浆，
And I really like your coffee syrup that you put in,
我觉得它很美。
I think it's beautiful.
海绵的第一层，在这里，完全浸透了。
The first layer of your sponge, over here, is just perfectly soaked.
和上次相比，你想说的是，
Compared to the last heat, you're trying really to say,
“等一下，我们有条件。”
"Hang on a minute, we have what it takes."
非常感谢，先生们。谢谢你！
Thank you very much, gentlemen. Thank you.
嗯。一些积极的方面。是的。
Mmm. Some positives. Yeah.
没关系的。
It's all right.
请糕点师邦邦过来好吗?
Can Bom Bom Patisserie please come forward?
来吧，老板。
Come on then, boss.
从视觉上看，我们看到的更像是方形的卷饼。
On the visual, we've got more of a squarish roulade.
谁能给我来杯建筑工人茶?
Can somebody bring me a cup of builder tea?
我要把这个泡进去。
I need to dunk this in.
天气太干燥了。
It was just so dry.
我觉得你所创造的一切，
I think what you've managed to create,
因为加入了汤卡豆，实际上是令人愉快的。
because of the addition of the tonka bean, is actually pleasant.
但它是干燥的。
But it is dry.
我们继续，
So, moving on swiftly,
你把马斯卡彭奶酪的顶部露出来了
you are exposing the top of your mascarpone
而且看起来不太吸引人。
and it doesn't look very appealing.
我试图寻找提拉米苏的美丽侧面，
I was trying to search for the beautiful profile of a tiramisu,
我在这里找不到
and I could not find it in here.
所有的东西都干巴巴的。
Everything is dry and claggy.
谢谢你！谢谢你！
Thank you. Thank you.
有什么原因让你躺下吗?
Is there any reason why you lie down your roulade?
我们试着让它站起来，然后它倒了一点。
We tried to make it stand and then it fell down a bit.
从视觉上看，它并不是最吸引人的。
Visually, it's not the most attractive.
我觉得很好。谢谢你！
I think it's nice. Thank you.
海绵是……
The sponge is...
榛子随处可见，我很喜欢。
I find the hazelnut everywhere, and I love that.
但我觉得你放了迷迭香。
But I think you put in rosemary.
是的，非常微妙。
Yeah, it's very subtle.
啐。一去不复返了。
Pfft. Gone.
现在来点提拉米苏。
Now, the tiramisu.
我喜欢海绵被管起来的想法。
I like the idea of the sponge being piped.
旁边……
Beside that...
. .它真的很厚。
..it's really a slab.
我喜欢你马斯卡彭奶酪的口感。
I like the texture of your mascarpone cream.
不过，底部的部分我不太喜欢，太干了。
The bottom part, though, I did not enjoy, too dry.
我只是很想吃提拉米苏的味道，我就是尝不出。
I was just craving for the tiramisu flavour, I just could not taste it.
非常感谢。再见。谢谢你！
Thank you very much. See you later. Thank you.
做得很好。谢谢。
Well done. Thanks.
希尔顿公园巷，请上前。
Hilton Park Lane, please come forward.
哦,啦啦啦啦啦啦啦啦。
Oh, la-la-la-la-la.
好的。那么，这个卷饼。
OK. So, the roulade.
我本希望看到一块烤好的海绵卷起来。
I would have hoped to see a sheet of baked sponge rolled on itself.
这是卷饼吗?我不太确定。
Is this a roulade? I'm not too sure.
你是不是太过分了?
Did you take it too far?
让我们试一试。让我们试一试。
Let's try. Let's have a go.
你做了很多工作。
You've done a lot of work.
你会把所有这些都滚在一起吗?
Would you have done all those rolled on each other...
. .你的味道混合得很好。
..you had a fantastic flavour combination there.
爱它，爱它，爱它。
Love it, love it, love it.
然而，我要炒蛋，你给我煎蛋卷。
However, I asked for scrambled egg, you give me omelette.
现在来点提拉米苏。
Now, the tiramisu.
就演示而言，我很高兴。
Presentation-wise, I'm happy.
我试图捕捉吃提拉米苏的感觉，
I was trying to capture the sensation of eating a tiramisu,
柔滑的马斯卡彭奶酪。
the creamy, silky mascarpone cream.
嗯。
Hmm.
我没有。
I didn't have that.
切片里的明胶太多了。
It's too much gelatine in the slice.
谢谢你！再见。
Thank you. See you later.
哔哔声。
BLEEP.
圣大卫酒店的迈克尔和丽贝卡，请站出来。
Michael and Rebekah from St David's Hotel, please come forward.
这就是我说的。
This is what I'm talking about.
一个漂亮的漩涡运动。
A nice swirl movement.
看起来很有吸引力。
It looks appealing.
我只是觉得香蕉
I just felt that the banana actually
盖过了卷的味道。
overtakes the flavour of the roulade.
提拉米苏。
The tiramisu.
作为一个整体，切片，有点基本。
As a whole, the slice, a little bit basic.
我们来尝尝吧?
Shall we taste?
这部分是完全干燥的。
This part here is completely dry.
我只是希望你能多加点糖浆。
I was just hoping that you use syrup a little bit more.
不是“a little bit more”，而是“更多”。
Not "a little bit more", more.
因为它根本没有浸泡过。
Because it's not been soaked at all.
我不太喜欢吃你的提拉米苏，抱歉，伙计们。
I did not really enjoy eating your tiramisu, sorry, guys.
非常感谢。谢谢你！我们一会儿见。
Thank you very much. Thank you. We'll see you later.
它们看起来和我的感觉一样。
They look how I feel.
我觉得是因为你全身心投入了。
I think it's because you put your heart into it.
我忍不住笑了。
REBEKAH LAUGHS I can't help laughing.
对着蛋糕哭，就像。
BLEEP crying over a cake, like.
这只是蛋糕而已，亲爱的。
It's only cake, love.
这只是一块蛋糕。
It's only cake.
这太残忍了。
That was brutal.
现在回想起来，事情会简单得多
Looking back on it, it would have been a lot easier
像转圈圈一样转圈圈那样会有帮助的。是的。
to do the roulade as a roulade. That would have helped. Yep.
哦,上帝。
Oh, God.
我知道会有很多镜头。
I knew a lot of shooting was going to come.
是的。从珍爱开始。
Yeah. And it did from Cherish.
对每个人来说都有点复杂。所以我认为一切都是开放的
THEO: A bit mixed for everyone. So I think everything is still open
我认为明天将是至关重要的一天。
and I think tomorrow is going to be a crucial day.
从一到十，我打七分。
On a scale of one to ten, I'm a seven.
我不打算再高了，因为它可能
I'm not going to go any higher than that, because it might all
明天退学，我就只剩1分了。
drop out tomorrow and I'll be down to a one.
各队今晚有一个黄金时间
The teams have been given a golden hour this evening
为了在明天的巨大挑战中领先一步。
to get ahead for tomorrow's monumental challenge.
那么，在所有的团队中，谁做得最好?
So, out of all the teams, who's done the best?
度假村世界为自己感到骄傲。
Resort World have done themselves proud.
上次有眼泪，
There was tears last time,
但他们今天带来了两个强大的微型挑战。
but they have delivered two strong miniature challenge today.
这周你担心的是哪支球队?
And what teams are you worried about this week?
我在圣大卫酒店的同事们。
My little colleagues from the St David's Hotel.
这是一场两半场的比赛，
It's a game of two halves with them,
因为只有它们才能呈现出可爱的漩涡。
because they are the only roulade which presents that lovely swirl.
然而，切片里没有提拉米苏的味道。
However, there's no sensation of the tiramisu in the slice.
对我来说，我真的很担心邦邦，
For me, I'm really worried about the Bom Bom,
因为对他们来说，今天并没有走到一起。
because it didn't quite come together today for them.
真令人失望。
What a disappointment.
那么，你想在明天的展览中看到什么呢?
So, what do you want to see in tomorrow's showpiece?
它必须是巨大的，它必须是惊人的。
It needs to be huge, it needs to be amazing.
我们只希望球队明天能彻底摧毁它，
Let's just hope the teams absolutely wreck it tomorrow,
我想看到厨房里的疯狂。
I want to see madness in the kitchen.
什么是“毁掉它”?“wreck”的意思是，砸了它，把它做好。
What is "wreck it"? Like, wreck it means, like, smash it, do it well.
早....早....早....早....
Morning. Morning. Morning. Morning.
早上好，厨师们。
Good morning, chefs.
今天，评委们想让你做一个表演，
Today, the judges would like you to make an occasion showpiece,
大到足以养活至少36个人，
big enough to feed at least 36 people,
以松饼的形式。一厢情愿。
in the form of a croquembouche. Gesundheit.
传统上，松饼是做成圆锥形的。
Traditionally, a croquembouche is constructed in the shape of a cone.
但我们今天不想在厨房里看到传统。
But we do not want to see tradition in this kitchen today.
让它更现代，围绕一个主题。
Make it modern and build it around a theme.
我想被你的味道所打动。
I want to be impressed and excited by your flavour.
厨师们，你们昨晚只有一个小时准备，
Chefs, you had one hour last night to prepare,
你只剩下四个小时了
and you have four hours remaining
来完成今天的Showpiece挑战。
to complete today's Showpiece Challenge.
各就各位，准备好……
On your marks, get set...
. .烤。不!
..bake. No!
这是另一个节目。
That's the other show.
哦,是的。UN-professionals。
Oh, yeah. The UN-professionals.
厨师们，各就各位，准备……
Chefs, on your marks, get set...
. .法式蛋糕店。
..patisserie.
祝你好运。祝你好运。
Good luck. Good luck.
我们开始吧。
Let's do this.
松饼是一种精心装饰的
A croquembouche is an elaborately decorated,
圆锥形的塔是用法式泡芙包做成的，
cone-shaped tower made with creme-patissiere-filled choux buns,
用焦糖粘在一起。
glued together with caramel.
在法国，它们传统上被用作婚礼蛋糕。
In France, they are traditionally served as wedding cakes.
我妻子仍然对我怀恨在心
My wife still holds a little grudge on me
我们的婚礼上还没做蛋糕。
not having done a croquembouche for our own wedding.
当然，很多事情都可能出错，比如烤松饼。
Many things can go wrong, of course, with the croquembouche.
我要脸红了。
I'm going to blush, here.
如果配料的比例不对
If you've got the wrong ratio of ingredients
在你的糕点奶油里，你可能会有一些东西
within your pastry cream, you may end up having something
块状或软软的，除了奶油味。
lumpy or gummy, everything but very creamy.
小心你的头。
Mind your head.
泡芙要烤到完美，
The choux needs to be baked to perfection,
否则整个结构就会坍塌。
or the structure will collapse.
我希望厨师能在这个挑战中发挥创意。
I would like the chef to be very creative with this challenge.
技能是至关重要的。
Technical skill is crucial.
这都是关于惊喜因素。
It's all about the wow factor.
我想说，“为什么我之前没有想到这一点?”
I want to be saying, "Why didn't I think of that before?"
你是怎么定定时器的?四个小时，对吧?是的。
What did you set the timer? Four hours, yeah? Yep.
这两支球队的当代风格是法式松饼
The teams' contemporary take on a croquembouche
必须有一个创新的形状。
must have an innovative shape.
所以除了他们在泡芙和糖方面的天赋…
So as well as their talent with choux and sugar work...
爆炸。这就是我们需要的。
Bang. That's what we needed.
. .这也将是一项艰巨的考验
..it will also be a daunting test
他们在设计和工程方面的技能。
of their skills in design and engineering.
HIDEKO:
我昨晚睡不着。
I couldn't sleep last night.
我通常在任何地方、任何情况下睡觉。
I normally sleep anywhere, any condition.
我做过的最高的蛋糕是松糕，
Tallest cake I ever made was a croquembouche,
但那是很多年前的事了。
but that's years and years ago.
经过昨天的事，我想这次我们需要挽回一下自己。
After yesterday, I think we need to redeem ourselves on this one.
伊曼纽尔和萨姆的展品将放在一个漂亮的牛格力底座上，
Emmanuel and Sam's showpiece will sit on a beautiful nougatine plinth,
用覆盆子和开心果调味
and be flavoured with raspberry and pistachio
还有桔子甜酒和橘子酒。
and orange liqueur and mandarin.
对于它的形状，他们雄心勃勃地选择了一个球体。
For its shape, they have ambitiously chosen a sphere.
你选择的结构并不容易。
The structure you have chosen is not an easy one.
你舒服吗?我们不舒服。
You are comfortable? We're not comfortable.
好。我们肯定会再一次把自己置于这样的境地，
Good. We definitely put ourselves, again, in a situation,
我们想要挑战自我。
where we want to challenge ourselves.
你练过多少次了?三次，我想说。
How many times have you practised? Three times, I would say.
说实话，有两次，牛轧糖都崩溃了。
To be honest, two times, the nougatine collapsed.
崩溃了吗?哦,不。
It collapsed? Oh, no.
他们的设计，Hideko和Theo
For their design, Hideko and Theo
与其说是跳出框框思考，不如说是创造框框。
aren't so much thinking outside boxes as making them.
它看起来像一个立方体塔。
It's going to look like a cube tower.
三层。
Three layers.
英子和西奥正在为他们的松饼做三种馅料。
Hideko and Theo are making three fillings for their croquembouche.
抹茶、芝麻
Matcha, sesame
还有黑醋栗和栗子。
and cassis and chestnut.
每个极简的泡芙盒都有不同的味道。
A different flavour for each of their minimalist choux boxes.
但是主题是什么呢?
But what is the theme?
这是一种新的现代风格。
It's a new, modern style.
但是，新的现代风格是一个主题吗?
But is new, modern style a theme?
你准备好了吗?是的，请把它传给我。好了。
Are you ready? Yeah, pass it on to me, please. There you go.
谢谢你！我们不觉得昨天做得太好，
Thank you. We didn't feel as though we did too great yesterday,
有了评委们的评论，所以，是的，我们需要把它从袋子里拿出来。
with the judges' comments, so, yeah, we need to pull it out the bag.
玛尔塔和朱莉打算挽回自己
Marta and Julie are aiming to redeem themselves
带着异国情调的展品。
with an exotic showpiece.
我们来自巴西，决定以热带为主题。
Coming from Brazil, we decided to go for a tropical theme.
它看起来像什么，一个巨大的菠萝还是
What is it going to look like, a giant pineapple or
类似的东西?它的结构是菠萝。
something like that? The structure is going to be a pineapple.
一个大菠萝?!
A giant pineapple?!
我只是猜测而已!
I was guessing!
他们的椰子酸橙焦糖菠萝泡芙包
Their coconut, lime and caramelised pineapple choux buns
会坐在一个高耸的八层看台上，
will sit on a towering, eight-tier stand,
由牛轧糖制成。
constructed from nougatine.
所以会有很多牛轧糖要处理，对吧?
So, there will be a lot of nougatine to be worked with, yeah?
你以前经常用牛轧糖吗?是的。
Have you worked with nougatine a lot before? Yeah.
好吧，你很自信。是的，我很有信心。
OK, so you're confident. Yes, I'm quite confident.
祝你好运，大厨。谢谢你！我想我们应该跳桑巴舞出去。
Good luck, chef. Thank you. I think we should samba out.
Samba。
Samba out.
Darryl和Bharat选择了一个更贴近家庭的主题。
Darryl and Bharat have chosen a theme a bit closer to home.
今天的主题是爱尔兰人的运气。
The theme for today is luck of the Irish.
你是爱尔兰人吗?不,
Are you Irish? No,
我的根其实是特立尼达人。
my roots are actually Trinidadian.
我们需要一点运气，所以我们想利用他们的运气。
We need a bit of luck, so we thought we'd use their luck.
希望他们的设计能像魅力一样发挥作用，
Hoping their design will work like a charm,
男孩子们要用小圆面包做底座
the boys will build a base of buns
里面装满了白巧克力和
filled with white chocolate and
树莓，小妖精的帽子
raspberry, a leprechaun's hat
涂上爱尔兰奶油
covered with Irish cream
还有牛奶巧克力泡芙，
and milk chocolate choux,
还有一个巨大的糖三叶草。
and a giant sugar shamrock.
巴拉特:我们昨晚在黄金时段做了三叶草。
BHARAT: We made the shamrock during the golden hour last night.
我们把所有的东西都剥掉，你就得到了一个美丽的镜面效果。
We peel everything off and you get a beautiful mirror finish.
哦，那里有条裂缝。
Oh, there's a crack, there.
我要解决这个问题。
I'm going to fix that.
迈克尔和丽贝卡的设计灵感…
For their design, Michael and Rebecca's inspiration...
呃，啪……就在他们家门口。
Ugh, splat. ..was right on their doorstep.
我们经常在酒店喝下午茶什么的，
We do a lot of afternoon teas and stuff at the hotel,
所以我们的主题是下午茶。
so our theme is afternoon tea.
两个巨大的牛轧糖轮子，
Featuring two giant nougatine wheels,
装饰着手工制作的糖茶具，
adorned with a handcrafted sugar tea set,
里面塞满了伯爵茶和凝块奶油口味的面包，
and filled with their Earl Grey and clotted cream flavoured buns,
他们气势恢宏的作品将被放在一个展台上
their imposing creation will sit on a stand
由七层泡芙制成。
made from seven layers of choux.
大概会有这么高。
Roughly, it'll probably be about that high.
完全没有压力，一点都没有。
No pressure at all, none whatsoever.
大厨们，你们还有三个小时，三个小时。
Chefs, you have three hours left, three hours.
我在做牛轧糖。
HIDEKO: I am cooking nougatine.
它的基础是糖和葡萄糖，还有杏仁。
It's based on sugar and glucose, as well as almond.
牛轧糖是一个关键的结构元素，
Nougatine is a key structural element,
但塑造它可能很棘手。
but moulding it can be tricky.
伊曼纽尔:你需要知道什么时候使用它。
EMMANUEL: You need to know when to use it.
当它太热的时候，试着用它是没有意义的。
There's no point to try to use it when it's too hot.
因为它粘在任何东西上。
Because it sticks to everything.
它冷却下来，焦糖凝固，你不能做任何事情。
It cools down and caramel sets and you can't do anything out of it.
牛轧糖冷却后迅速硬化
With the nougatine hardening rapidly as it cools...
哔哔声。
BLEEP.
. .速度是最重要的。
..speed is of the essence.
朱莉，快点。
Julie, get a move on.
他们吃的牛轧糖越多，速度就越快。
And the more nougatine they have, the quicker they have to be.
我们的展台大概有十层楼高，
Our stand is going to be about ten levels high,
所以我们需要很多牛轧糖。
so we need a lot of nougatine.
我的问题是，我有点慢，所以在我塑造它们之前它们就凝固了。
My problem is, I'm a bit slow so they set before I can shape them.
哦，该死的。
Oh, bloody hell.
正确的,那么。回到烤箱里。
Right, then. Back in the oven.
哦,朱莉。
Oh, Julie.
重新融化牛轧糖需要时间。
Re-melting the nougatine will take time.
我得抓紧时间了。他们没有时间。
I'm going to have to get a move on. Time they don't have.
把我的车底打开。
Get me bottom into gear.
还有一个半小时，大厨们。还有90分钟。
An hour and a half left, chefs. 90 minutes left.
离集合还有一个小时。好吗?是的。
Got an hour until assembly. OK? Yeah.
当朱莉与她的牛轧糖搏斗时……
While Julie wrestles with her nougatine...
两个搞定了，还有十个。
Two done, ten to go.
. .其他队……看看打蛋器的大小。
..the other teams... Look at the size of your whisk.
. .转向泡芙的馅料。
..turn to fillings for their choux.
我们要把开心果酱加到糕点奶油里。
We are going to add the pistachio paste to the pastry cream.
一个是黑醋栗和栗子，一个是抹茶，
One's going to be cassis and chestnut, one is going to be matcha,
一种是黑白调味料。
and one is going to be white and dark seasoning.
你切泡芙的方式，我想看到颜色上的惊喜。
The way you cut choux, I want to see a little surprise in the colour.
这是爱尔兰奶油。上周，珍爱觉得这里有点太醉了，
This is the Irish cream. Last week, Cherish found it a bit too boozy,
所以希望这周不会那么糟糕。
so hopefully, it's not as bad this week.
它们真的有那么大吗?我不知道什么尺寸合适!
Are they meant to be that big? I don't know what the right size is!
如果你切开，希望你能看到我在中间搅拌的橘子胶。
If you cut through, hopefully, you'll see the mandarin gel that I'm piping in the middle.
你只是想要一点点，不是吗?一团，这样他们就能尝到了。
You just want a little dollop in there, don't you? A blob, so they can taste it.
加油，伙计，加油，加油!我得把这些弄清楚。
Come on, mate, come on, chop, chop! I've got to get these ones right.
这是我的菠萝凝胶，我把它放进去，
That's my pineapple gel, so I'll insert it in,
然后我把椰子和酸橙蛋奶冻放上去。
and then I put the coconut and lime custard on.
来吧。还有一小时，大厨们。你有一个小时。
Come on. One hour left, chefs. You have one hour.
正确的,那么。继续，汤米。开始做松饼的外壳，
Right, then. Rock on, Tommy. Starting to build the croquembouche shell,
用焦糖粘在一起。
just stick it together with caramel.
这是很关键的一步，因为其他一切都在这一步之上。
Kind of a crucial stage, cos everything else will be sat on top of this.
设计越复杂……朱莉的集中注意力。
The more complex the design... Julie's concentrating.
她现在不能说话。
She can't talk right now.
. .组装的风险就越大。
..the riskier it will be to assemble.
你得到的太多了。去容易。
You've got way too much. Go easy.
哪一个是第一个?
Which one's first?
这条是最直的。
This one is the straightest one.
对的,好吧。准备好了吗?
Right, OK. Ready?
玛尔塔和朱莉，我很喜欢这个结构
Marta and Julie, I quite like the structure
他们会为我们提供住宿。
they're going to put up for us.
这是一个菠萝。这很有趣。
It's a pineapple. It's quite intriguing.
他们会成功吗?我们不知道。
Will they manage to pull it off? We don't know.
别动，别动。一旦开了，就开了。
Don't move, don't move. Once it's on, it's on.
像这样把它们粘起来。扫描。
Stick those like this. Sweep up.
我不相信。它是三个立方体堆叠在一起。
I'm not convinced. It's three cubes stacked on each other.
这是个简单的设计。那么，希尔顿公园巷怎么样?
It's a simple design. So, what about the Hilton Park Lane?
他们做的松饼有点冒险。
Their croquembouche is kind of a risky business.
他们成功了三次，却坍塌了两次!哇!哦吼!
They've made it three times and it collapsed twice! Wow! Woohoo!
我快没时间了。
I'm running out of time.
我应该已经在第二个半球上了。
I should already be on the second half-sphere.
放松。我去喝杯啤酒，好吗?
Relax. I go for a beer, yeah?
大厨们，你们还有30分钟。
Chefs, you have 30 minutes left.
从糖开始。是的。
Starting on sugar. Yeah.
我在试着拉一个糖丝带。
I'm attempting to pull a sugar ribbon.
我在YouTube上看到有人这么做。
I see people on YouTube doing it.
我参加了英国糖业锦标赛，得了第二名，
I did the UK Sugar Championships and came second,
所以，加点糖。
so, done a bit of sugar.
我在做我的菠萝。这必须是直的。
I am building my pineapple. This needs to be straight.
对反对派虎视眈眈
Eyeing up the opposition.
他们在做玫瑰。它们很棘手。
They're doing some roses. They're quite tricky.
这看起来很漂亮。现在，我们快赶上了。
This looks beautiful. Right now, we're getting close on time.
所以我要更深入地了解它。
So I'm going to have to be more de-board it.
我不想在大家面前这么做。
I don't want to do this in front of everybody else.
为什么?这是非常私人的事情?这是非常脆弱和困难的。
Why? It's a very private thing? It's very fragile and difficult.
像我这样。糖粉碎了
Like myself. SUGAR SHATTERS
哔哔声!
BLEEP!
我想把事情弄清楚。我把它压得太紧了。
I was trying to get it really straight. I've pressed it too hard.
它就这样……
It just sort of went...
这很好。我可以重新开始。是的，去吧。走,走。
That's fine. I can start building it again. Yeah, go for it. Go, go.
希望它是稳定的。
Hopefully, it's going to be stable.
如果你听到噼啪声，我就不高兴了。
If you hear a crack, I won't be happy.
它看起来是朝这边来的。我需要这里的水平仪，拜托。
It looks like it's coming this way. I need the spirit level in here, please.
这很好。它很好。别再说“没事”了!它很好。
That's fine. It's fine. Stop saying, "It's fine"! It's fine.
你必须要快。只会一点点。就是这样。哇，哇，哇，哇!
You have to be quick. Only a little bit. That's it. Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa!
迈克，你看后面，滴水。我刚注意到。
Mike, just watch at the back, the dripping. I just noticed that.
第二轮。我们把这个放到桌子上好吗?
Round two. Shall we move this to the table?
一、二、三……
One, two, three...
电梯,电梯……。不要电击，不要电击，不要电击。
Lift, lift...lift. No shock, no shock, no shock.
小心别把它弄得太乱。
Careful you don't make too much of a mess with it.
就是这样，就是这样。上帝保佑我们。
That's it, that's it. God help us.
心就像……他捶打着胸膛
Heart is like... HE THUMPS HIS CHEST
魔法。
Magic.
那条路?不，这边走。面朝那边。我的天啊。
That way? No, this way. Facing that way. Oh, my God.
哔哔声!那有一吨重。
BLEEP! That weighs a tonne.
我看不见实物。我去拿。我在走下坡路吗?
I can't see an actual thing. I'll get it. Am I going down?
对，下去。趴下，趴下，趴下!
Yeah, go down. Go down, go down, go down!
噢!五分钟，大厨们。还有五分钟。
Ooh! Five minutes, chefs. Five minutes to go.
哦，我现在感觉压力很大。
Oh, I feel really pressured now.
做壳。我得先把它造出来。
Doing the shell. I need to build it first.
我们走吧。糖凝固得太快了，我们得继续。
Let's go. The sugar is setting so quickly, we need to keep going.
一个小的，如果你有的话。下面有一个晃动。
One small one, if you got it. There's a wobble under there.
哦,哔哔声!
Oh, BLEEP!
这必须继续下去。这些是我们的幸运硬币。
This has to go on. These are our lucky coins.
我差不多做完了。
I'm pretty much almost done.
有人知道我们还剩多少时间吗?
Anyone know what time we've got left?
大厨们，你们还有一分钟。
Chefs, you have one minute left.
这种方式吗?是的。是的。
This way? Yeah. Yeah.
这需要继续下去。还得在上面撒点叶子。
This needs to go on. Still got to pipe some leaves on it.
哦，不，不，不，不!
Oh, no, no, no, no!
我只要把彩带粘上就行了。
I've just got to stick the ribbons on.
快走，快走!拿些绿色蔬菜。把绿色蔬菜拿出来。
Move it, move it! Get the greens. Get the greens going.
我认为它需要稍微扭转一下。
I think it needs to turn around a little bit.
快，快，快，快，快!
Go, go, go, go, go!
时间到了。
Time's up.
离你的展示品远点。
Step away from your showpieces.
让我们收拾一下，姑娘。
Let's tidy up, girl.
好了，我们走吧
Right, let's go
然后被摧毁!是啊!
and get destroyed! Yeah!
五个令人敬畏的展示
Five awe-inspiring showpieces
只用了五个小时。
made in just five hours.
我就是忘不了公园巷。
I just can't get over Park Lane's.
我都不知道他们是怎么画出这个形状的。
I don't even know how they did that shape.
伙计们，你们的作品非常视觉化。
Guys, you've produced something extremely visual.
真的很喜欢这些台词。
Really like the lines.
看你们俩的作品真是太开心了。
What a joy to watch both of your work.
很高兴看到你拉花的样子。
And so pleased to see the way you pull your flower.
我们尝尝泡芙好吗?
Shall we taste the choux?
你应该要一杯橘子利口酒配橘子果酱。
You should have an orange liqueur with a mandarin jam.
这泡芙很好吃。
The choux is quite pleasant to eat.
我真的很喜欢橘子的味道。
I really enjoy the mandarin flavour.
话虽如此，我们已经完全失去了橙色利口酒
Having said that, we've lost the orange liqueur altogether
因为你的橘子香。
because of the fragrance of your mandarin.
这个是开心果和覆盆子。
And this one will be pistachio and raspberry.
总的来说，馅料的质地还不错。
Overall, the texture of the filling is good.
然而，我几乎尝不出开心果的味道。
However, I hardly can taste the pistachio.
我完全失去了覆盆子味。
And I've lost the raspberry altogether.
我不喜欢这样。
I'm not enjoying this.
那很好。
That was good.
真的,各位,
Really, guys,
我不会想到要做那样的事
I would not have thought of doing something like that
在一百万英里之外。
in a million miles.
我真的很喜欢。
I really like it.
那是香草，白巧克力和覆盆子泥。
That is vanilla, white chocolate and raspberry puree.
很香，有覆盆子的味道。
It's fragrant, raspberry is present.
我很喜欢你做的蛋奶冻，因为它很滑。
I really like your custard because it's really smooth.
和覆盆子酱很配。
It goes so well with the raspberry jam.
我们来做爱尔兰利口酒……
So we do the Irish liqueur...
我有爱尔兰利口酒。
I've got the Irish liqueur.
就我个人而言，我觉得它有点太浓了。
Personally, I find it a bit too strong.
我喜欢它。
I love it.
这是个人喜好的问题。我还以为会太甜蜜了。
A matter of taste. I thought it was going to be too sweet.
我错了。我喜欢它的味道。
I was wrong. I love the taste.
谢谢你！谢谢你！
Thank you. Thank you.
我觉得你做的很漂亮。
I think it's a beautiful showpiece that you've done.
这是一道优雅的法式奶油布丁。
It's an elegant croque-en-bouche.
但你已经不仅仅是简单化了，你变得简单了。
But you've gone, not just simplistic, you've got simple.
我们现在有三个泡芙了。
We've got now three choux.
这个是……两种:抹茶。
This one is... BOTH: Matcha.
我觉得味道很好。
I think the taste is perfect.
然而，法式奶油，我不喜欢吃。
However, the creme patissiere, I didn't enjoy eating it.
有点黏。
It is a bit gummy.
黑醋栗。黑加仑子和栗子。
Blackcurrant. Blackcurrant and chestnut.
试着尝尝栗子的味道。
Trying to taste the chestnut.
但是，如果我不知道里面有栗子就吃了，
However, if I eat it without knowing there is chestnut in there,
我不会注意到的。黑芝麻。
I wouldn't notice it. Black sesame.
我爱吃黑芝麻。
I love my black sesame.
对我来说，这个，我喜欢。
For me, this, I like.
再多一点奶油，泡芙就完美了。
A little bit creamier, and that choux would be perfection.
没关系的。没关系的。他还挺喜欢的。
It's all right. It's all right. He kind of liked it.
我们来谈谈房间里的大象吧。
Let's talk about the elephant in the room.
它有点倾斜。
It's tilting slightly.
是的。是的。
Yeah. Yeah.
我们还得提一下，你的工作还需要改进。
We also have to mention the neatness of your work needs to improve.
十分钟前，你还在坚持。
It was ten minutes before, you were still sticking.
是的。你太匆忙了。确实很匆忙。
Yeah. You were rushing. Certainly was rushing.
泡芙的馅料是椰子和酸橙蛋奶冻
The filling of the choux has got a coconut and lime custard
然后在里面放上菠萝凝胶。
and then a pineapple gel inside.
泡芙面皮烤得很好。
The choux pastry is baked nicely.
脆皮的口感很好。
The crackling has got a nice texture.
对不起,珍惜。你的不是菠萝吗?
Sorry, Cherish. Is it not pineapple on yours?
空了!不能接受的。
Empty again! Not acceptable.
对不起，我不会为你的甜点买单。
Sorry, I would not pay for your dessert.
在这个底部有一点点。
There is a little bit at the bottom of this one.
好吧，说实话，反正也没什么味道。
Well, to be honest with you, it didn't taste much anyway.
你有吗?
You get some?
不。
No.
Ho-ho-ho-ho !
Ho-ho-ho-ho!
它就在那儿，雄伟，高大。
There it is, majestuous, tall.
它有点粗，
It's a little bit chunky,
而且，作为一种风格，它有点过时了。
and also, as a style, it is a little bit dated.
好的。看着你的茶壶，
OK. And, looking at your teapot,
我还希望你最后的点睛之笔能更细致一些。
I was hoping that you were more delicate with your finishing touch.
我们以下午茶为主题，
We've gone with an afternoon tea theme,
我们有一个凝块奶油泡芙包还有一个草莓凝胶。
so we have a clotted cream choux bun and there's a strawberry gel.
我想谈谈这个泡芙糕点。
I would like to talk about this choux pastry.
我觉得这太粗暴了，
I think it's very heavy-handed,
而且，我也没有尝到凝固的奶油。
and also, I didn't taste the clotted cream.
然后是伯爵茶柠檬泡芙包。
And then an Earl Grey and lemon choux bun.
伯爵格雷奶油的质地比凝块奶油好。
The texture of the Earl Grey cream is better than the clotted cream.
之后，味道组合就很无趣了。
After, the flavour combination was pretty uninteresting.
它不是很好。
It wasn't great.
第一次喝的时候，我说，“哦，我能尝出伯爵茶的味道，”
On the first taste, I said, "Oh, I can taste the Earl Grey,"
然后酸进来了
and then the acid comes in
我不太喜欢，所以，抱歉
and I didn't really enjoy, so, sorry,
我一点也不喜欢这样。好的。
I didn't like this at all. OK.
她抽泣
SHE SOBS
来了,来了。
Come, come.
来吧，别哭了。
CHERISH: Come on, don't cry.
太尴尬了。
That was so embarrassing.
有点尴尬。
Like, proper embarrassing.
你哭什么?我不知道。
What you crying for? I don't know.
根据他们在两项挑战中的表现，
Based on their performance across both challenges,
评委们将对参赛队伍进行排名，
the judges will now rank the teams,
最后一名的队伍
and the team in last place
将不得不退出比赛。
will have to leave the competition.
昨天的失望过后，
After yesterday's disappointment,
我们制作了我们想要的东西，达到了我们想要的水平。
we produced exactly what we wanted to, to the level we wanted to.
不管现在发生什么，我觉得我们已经为自己感到骄傲了。
Whatever happens now, I feel we've done ourselves proud.
很有趣，你不觉得吗?
Very interesting, don't you think?
我喜欢那里的配色。
I like the colour scheme there.
我们在比赛一开始就很低，
We started off the competition on a quite low peg,
但这周我们把它砸了。
but this week we smashed it, I think.
有点胖。
A bit chunky.
说到底，这些都是建设性的批评。
It's all constructive criticism, at the end of the day.
是啊，回去学习吧。
Yeah, go back and learn.
他们这么说不是为了冒犯你，而是为了让你进步。
They don't say it to offend you, they say it to make you improve.
听起来还是很难受。是的。
It's still hard to hear. Yeah.
伯努瓦和珍爱已经做出了决定。
Benoit and Cherish have reached their decision.
第一名的团队在口味和展示方面表现出色
The team in first place excelled in their flavours and presentation
跨越两个艰难的挑战。
across two tough challenges.
恭喜你……
Congratulations...
度假村世界的Darryl和Bharat。
Darryl and Bharat from Resorts World.
你晋级下一轮了。
You are through to the next round.
第二名是希尔顿公园巷的伊曼纽尔和山姆。
In second place are Emmanuel and Sam from the Hilton Park Lane...
Sweet Art Lab的Hideko和Theo获得第三名。
And Sweet Art Lab's Hideko and Theo have come third.
那就只剩下圣大卫酒店的迈克尔和丽贝卡了
Which leaves Michael and Rebekah from the St David's Hotel
还有邦邦糕点店的玛尔塔和朱莉。
and Marta and Julie from Bom Bom Patisserie.
经过深思熟虑，今晚回家的队伍将是……
After much deliberation, the team going home tonight will be...
. .邦邦糕点店的玛尔塔和朱莉。
..Marta and Julie from Bom Bom Patisserie.
祝贺你们其他人。
Congratulations to the rest of you.
我们下周见。
We'll see you next week.
哦，我感觉有点不舒服。
Oh, I'm feeling a bit upset.
是的,很失望。
Yeah, disappointed.
这是你的第一次比赛，对吗?是的。
It's your first competition, right? Yes.
我为我们所做的一切感到骄傲。不是吗?
I'm proud of what we've done. Aren't you?
这让我重拾了对职业的热情。
It's given me my passion back for my trade.
哦，你们把它砸了。
Oh, you lot smashed it.
辉煌。是的,太棒了。
Brilliant. Yeah, fantastic.
是的，我非常非常高兴。
Yeah, really, really happy about it.
它让你想呆在那里。
It makes you want to stay there.
你知道吗?这会让你更加挣扎。
You know? It makes you fight even more.
哔哔声。
BLEEP.
嗯，是的，很震惊。
Um, yeah, shocked.
我简直不敢相信!我以为我们已经走了!
I can't believe it! I thought we were gone!
我想我们必须努力，否则下周就回家。
I think we've got to go hard or go home next week.
下一次，竞争只会更加激烈……
Next time, the competition only gets tougher...
哔哔声。
BLEEP.
. .评委们设置了有史以来第一个秘密食谱挑战…
..as the judges set the first ever Secret Recipe Challenge...
我不知道它长什么样。
I have no idea how it looks like.
. .一个颓废的展示品……
..and a decadent showpiece...
哔哔声。戏剧!
BLEEP. Drama!
. .完全由巧克力制成。别再这样了。
..made entirely of chocolate. Not doing this again.
哪三支球队能进入六强?
Which three teams will make it through to the final six?
我很害怕!
I'm scared!
谁会崩溃……这将是一个有趣的谜题。
And who will crack... It's going to be a fun puzzle.
. .在压力之下?
..under the pressure?
这可不是什么好消息。
Well, it's not great news.
我还以为他们心情很好呢。
Just when I thought they were in a good mood.
字幕由红蜂传媒制作
Subtitles by Red Bee Media
欢迎回到《职业烘焙大赛》，
Welcome back to Bake Off: The Professionals,
在那里寻找英国最好的糕点师的热潮正在升温。
where the search for Britain's best pastry chef is hotting up.
汤姆现在将解释原因。谢谢，利亚姆。是的，我会的。
Tom will now explain why. Thank you, Liam. Yes, I will.
现在，我们从这六组开始
Now, we started off with this set of six
明天结束前会是谁
who by the end of tomorrow
将在这轮预赛中选出三支最好的队伍。
will be whittled down to the three best teams in this set of heats.
然后，下周，我们会遇到新的六人组
Then, next week, we'll meet a new set of six
然后他们也会被缩减到三个人。
who will then be similarly whittled down to three.
新的六人组将被淘汰进入决赛
This new set of six will then be whittled down to the final
他们中的一个将被加冕为糕点皇帝。
where one of them will be crowned Emperor of Pastries.
或者类似的东西。就像世界杯一样。
Or something like that. It's just like the World Cup.
不，不是的。就像奥运会一样。
No, it's not. It's just like the Olympics.
不。f1是一项运动吗?
No. Formula 1, is that a sport?
汤姆，你在说什么?得了吧，利亚姆。
Tom, what are you talking about? Oh, give me a break, Liam.
我只是想让观众能看懂。
I'm just trying to make it so the viewers can understand it.
就像我们说"主菜"而不是蛋糕。
You know, like when we say "entremet" instead of cake.
忽略他。今天是巧克力周，你们只需要知道这些就行了。
Ignore him. It's Chocolate Week, and that's all you guys need to know.
最后一次……噢!
Last time... Ooh!
两队用松饼大战。
the teams battled with croquembouche.
它有一吨重。
It weighs a ton.
Darryl和Bharat的杰作
Darryl and Bharat's masterful showpiece
确保了胜利的逆转
secured a winning comeback.
我真的很喜欢。非常感谢。
I really like it. Thank you very much.
这给迈克尔和丽贝卡敲响了警钟。
There was a wake-up call for Michael and Rebekah.
别哭了。
Don't cry.
但玛尔塔和朱莉的口味不够……
But Marta and Julie came up short on flavour...
不能接受的。
Not acceptable.
. .成为第二支退出比赛的球队。
..and became the second team to leave the competition.
我为我们所做的一切感到骄傲，你呢?
I'm proud of what we've done, aren't you?
这一次……来吧，宝贝。
This time... Come on, baby.
. .第一组预赛结束了。
..the first set of heats come to an end.
哦,sha-la-la。
Ooh, sha-la-la.
最后六强的席位岌岌可危
With a place in the final six at stake...
压力越来越大了。
The pressure is getting to me.
. .摄制组面临着一种他们从未见过的食谱。我很害怕。
..the teams face a recipe they've never seen before. I'm scared.
还有一个完全由巧克力制成的高耸的展示品。
And a towering showpiece made entirely of chocolate.
哦,哔哔声。你觉得它能撑得住吗?
Oh, BLEEP. Do you think it's going to hold?
哪三支球队会晋级?
Which three teams will move forward?
和谁…大问题……会被落下吗?
And who... Big problem. ..will be left behind?
巧克力周将决定哪三支队伍
Chocolate Week will decide which three teams
都将进入决赛阶段。
will make it through to the final stages of the competition.
他的旅程也将走到尽头。
And whose journey will come to an end.
为了确保只有最有天赋的厨师才能晋级，
To ensure only the most gifted chefs progress,
评委们通过秘密挑战提高了赌注。
the judges have upped the ante with a secret challenge.
这是什么?
What is it?
这是第一次球队不知道
This is the first time the teams have no idea
他们要做什么。
what they're about to make.
早上好，厨师们。
Good morning, chefs.
我感觉你今天越来越焦虑了。
I sense an increased level of anxiety today.
这是理所当然的，因为你即将面对
And rightly so, because you're about to face
这是首届秘方挑战赛。
this competition's first-ever Secret Recipe Challenge.
不需要准备，不需要练习，只需要你的智慧和知识。
No preparation, no practice, just your wits and knowledge.
相信我，这个挑战很难。
Trust me when I say this challenge is hard.
我们选择的秘方叫做
The secret recipe we have chosen is called
树叶味D 'automne。
Feuille D'automne.
主厨，我们想看到一层层完美烘焙的蛋白霜
Chef, we want to see layers of perfectly baked meringue
夹上巧克力慕斯，上面撒上巧克力玫瑰酱，
sandwiched with chocolate mousse, topped with chocolate rosace,
在巧克力摊上售卖。
and served on a chocolate stand.
这是你挑战的一部分。
Which must be made as part of your challenge.
你有3.5小时的时间，从现在开始。
You have 3.5 hours, and your time starts now.
我不会发音。自动燃料?
I can't pronounce it. Fuel de auton?
这是法国蛋糕。是的。我从来没见过。
It is a French cake. Yeah. I've never seen it.
当你看到一大堆事情并在努力的时候，这是很困难的
It's difficult when you see a load of things and are trying
弄清楚你该做什么，不该做什么。
to work out what you should do, what you shouldn't do.
我想回家。
I want to go home.
第一次秘密配方。
Secret recipe for the first time.
我很兴奋，因为厨师们没办法准备。
I'm so excited, because the chefs are not able to prepare.
这将归结为两部分。
It will come down to deux part.
一个人要一份秋季小蛋糕，
The Feuille D'automne gateau for one,
巧克力是给其他人的。
and the chocolate stand for the others.
我们想知道他们的本能。他们能想出什么办法?
We want to know their instinct. What can they come up with?
我们首先应该做什么?我想我们得把东西准备好
What should we do first? I think we need to get the stuff ready
为了巧克力摊想清楚我们在做什么。
for the chocolate stand and figure out what we're doing.
每个小组都有一些模具，颜料，
The teams have been given a selection of moulds, paints,
还有制作巧克力摊的工具。
and tools to fashion their chocolate stands.
我可以模仿一下。
I can do a little impression on it.
要有质感。
Have a texture.
做个底，也许……
Make a base, maybe...
. .就像这样。
..something like this.
迈克尔和丽贝卡。
Michael and Rebekah.
总是一缕阳光。
Always a ray of sunshine.
你今天感觉怎么样?不太坏，不太坏。
How are you feeling today? Not too bad, not too bad.
好。好。那展台呢?你画过草图了吗?
Good. Good. What about the stand? Have you done a sketch of it?
我们有一个基本的设计。它看起来像一个可爱的鸡蛋计时器。
We have kind of got a basic design. It looks like a lovely egg timer.
它的功能。把它倒过来。把它倒过来。
It does. Just turn it upside down. Turn it upside down.
如果一切都出了问题，我们就把它翻个底朝天。
If it all goes wrong, we'll turn it upside down.
不管他们怎么说，
Whichever way they choose to present it,
米迦勒和丽贝卡的证人席将由一列
Michael and Rebekah's stand will consist of a column of
三个巧克力球，将用树叶装饰。
three chocolate spheres and will be decorated with leaves.
足够让我们俩惊叹吗?
Is there enough to wow both of us?
我希望如此。
I hope so.
尽量不要过时。不要守旧。
Try not to be old-fashioned. Do not be old-fashioned.
它得看起来像今天的我。
It needs to look like me today.
那么光滑。时尚前进。
So sleek. Fashion forward.
光滑时髦，珍爱，光滑时髦。
Slick and trendy, Cherish, slick and trendy.
各组开始铸造巧克力支架。
The teams set to work casting their chocolate stands.
只有三个半小时
With just three and half hours,
他们必须快速工作，以便有时间让它们凝固。
they must work fast to allow time for them to set.
大概这么高。是的…
About this high. Yeah...
看起来太高了。我认为它不会很快凝固。
It looks too high. I don't think it will set quickly.
上周的获胜者Darryl和Bharat，
Last week's winners, Darryl and Bharat,
我们采取了谨慎的态度……
are taking a cautious approach...
. .有一个简单的柱子和一个装饰着球体的底座。
..with a simple pillar and a base decorated with spheres.
我们知道我们可以做得更多。我想我们当时想，
We know we can do more. I think we thought,
现在是时候了，安全点。
the time frame we are in, go a bit safe.
然而，有一个团队将谨慎抛到九霄云外。
One team, however, is throwing caution to the wind.
最近怎么样?你好。大家早上好。
How's it going? Hello. Good morning, everyone.
我们做得怎么样?
How are we doing?
大家同时发言
ALL SPEAK AT ONCE
我看到了一幅漂亮的画。请带我们过去。
I saw a beautiful drawing. Please take us through.
我们的计划是女性化的，像一条线，像这样。
Our plan is feminine, like a line, like this.
给它一个高度。
Give it height.
英子和西奥要大干一场了。
Hideko and Theo are going big.
他们标志性的前卫设计
Their signature avant-garde design
会看到他们的展台装饰着抽象的形状吗
will see their stand adorned with abstract shapes
还有一朵手工制作的莲花。
and a handcrafted lotus flower.
他在做树叶，也在融化白巧克力
He's making leaves and also melting white chocolate
在花瓣上加一点。所以它更抽象。
a little bit for petals. So it's more abstract.
一遍吗?抽象?
Again? Abstract?
有机食品。自由泳的策略。
Organic. Freestyle strategy.
是的。自由泳。自由泳。让它流动。
Yeah. Freestyle. Freestyle. Let it flow.
让它流动，好吗?
Let it flow, yeah?
你的架子能撑得住蛋糕吗?
Is your stand going to hold your cake?
让我们来看看。让我们来看看。
Let's see. Let's see.
伊曼纽尔和萨姆也希望有一个雄心勃勃的设计
Emmanuel and Sam are also hoping an ambitious design
将帮助他们在决赛中获得一席之地。
will help them secure a place in the final stages of the competition.
这是你能走远的唯一方法
The only way you're going to get far
就是尽你所能全力以赴。
is by going all-out as much as you can.
无论我们做什么，我们都会全力以赴。
And anything we do, we're trying to go all-out.
我们不想回家。我们也不想回家。
We don't want to go home. And we don't want to go home.
他们的看台将由螺旋球柱组成
Their stand will be made of spiral sphere pillars
大理石效果的底座和精致的装饰使其更加突出。
enhanced by a marble-effect base and elaborate decorations.
你在做花吗?是的。
You making the flowers? Yeah.
享受。
Enjoy.
嗯。
Mmm.
珍爱可能会说……
Cherish will probably say...
“厨师，这是很好的。”
"Chef, it's well-tempered."
哦，我能听到噼啪声。是的。
Oh, I can hear the crack. Yup.
你们能行的，伙计。我们会知道的，不是吗?
You guys got this, man. We'll find out, won't we?
还剩两小时，大厨们，你们还有两小时。
Two hours left, chefs, you've got two hours left.
架子正在凝固，等待脱模。
The stand is setting and waiting to be unmould.
然后做蛋糕。
And then making the cake.
球队现在必须把注意力转移
The teams must now turn their attention
给他们的福伊尔·德·蒙
to their Feuille D'automne -
这是一种默默无闻的法国美食，之前没有人做过。
an obscure French delicacy none of them have made before.
酥皮蛋糕由一层蛋白霜组成
A Feuille D'automne consists of layer of meringue
巧克力慕斯，
and chocolate mousse,
最后是一块巧克力
finished with a band of chocolate
上面撒上巧克力玫瑰酱。
and topped with chocolate rosace.
但如果你从未见过，从未做过，
But if you've never seen it before, never done it before,
这将会非常非常奇怪。
it's going to be really, really strange.
我认为这是一个挑战。这就是他们所害怕的。
And I think this is the challenge. This is what they are afraid of.
没有控制的部分。
The part where no control.
我们有了食谱，但知道怎么做是另一回事。
We got the recipe, but knowing how to do it is a different thing.
我不知道它长什么样。不知道。
I have no idea how it looks like. No idea.
就像一层慕斯，中间夹着蛋白霜。酥皮。
Maybe like a layer of the mousse, sandwiched with meringue. Meringue.
早上好,伙计。早上好,利亚姆。你好吗？
Morning, guys. Morning, Liam. How are you?
还不错，最近怎么样?
Yeah, not too bad, how's it going?
现在，我开始做蛋白霜。把它放在机器里搅拌。
So at the moment, I'm starting the meringue. Whip it in the machine.
鞭子。你知道鞭子舞吗?
Whip it. Have you, do you know that dance, Whip It?
我们应该直呼其名吗?利亚姆笑
Should we nae-nae? LIAM LAUGHS
再做一次。我不会做的。
Do that again. I'm not doing it.
再来一次。不。我来抽一下，你这娘们，我就走。好吗?
Just one more time. No. I'll whip it, you nae-nae, and I'll go. OK?
好吧，我们开始吧。
OK, let's do it.
看着我，我的名字。
Watch me nae-nae.
走吧，走吧。我走了，我走了。
Go, get going. I'm gone, I'm gone.
好吧,再见。祝你们好运。再见!
OK, bye. Good luck, guys. Bye!
你在做蛋白霜吗?是的。
Are you doing the meringue? Yeah.
哦,对不起。我来打扫。对不起,厨师。
Oh, sorry. I'll clean it up. Sorry, Chef.
不，不，不。哦，对不起，对不起。
No, no, no. Oh, sorry, sorry.
破坏。蓄意破坏，蓄意破坏，蓄意破坏。
Sabotage. Sabotage, sabotage, sabotage.
蛋白霜是蛋糕的基石。
The meringue is the bedrock of this gateau.
团队正确烘焙是至关重要的。
It's crucial the teams bake them correctly.
很明显，如果蛋白派没有烤好，
Obviously if the meringue is not baked right,
它装不住慕斯。
it doesn't hold the mousse.
如果你烤得不够熟，蛋白霜就会太软。
If you underbake the meringue, it's going to be too soft.
如果你煮得太久，它也很容易坍塌。
If you overcook it, it could also collapse quite easily.
虽然大多数人选择快速烘焙…
While most are opting for a quick bake...
15吗?是的。
15? Yeah.
15分钟。十个
15 minutes. Ten.
. .伊曼纽尔和山姆采取了相反的方法。
..Emmanuel and Sam are taking the opposite approach.
那么，蛋白霜要煮多久?
So, the meringue, how long will it be cooking for?
普通蛋白霜很可能要在里面放40分钟。
The plain meringue would be very likely a good 40 minutes in there.
40分钟吗?他们希望它是硬的。
40 minutes? They want it to be firm.
看起来一切都在他们掌控之中。
Seems like they're in control.
我们会看到，我们会看到是否控制住了。
We'll see, we'll see if the control has been kept.
完全正确。
Exactly.
烤好了，我试着做慕斯，巧克力。
So that bakes, and I try to make mousse, chocolate.
和酥皮。
And meringue.
折叠蛋白霜。
Folding in the meringue.
我觉得他们想要那种轻盈的慕斯。
I think they're looking for that light, airy mousse.
为了保持摩丝的轻盈，
To retain the lightness of their mousse,
通过轻轻折叠来保持空气的流通是很重要的。
it's essential they keep the air in by folding it gently.
我不确定它应该是这样的，但是……今天是猜字日。
I'm not sure it should look like that, but...today is guess day.
太粗糙，就有可能把它变成液体。
Too rough, and they risk reducing it to a liquid.
那是你的摩丝吗?是的。
Is that some of your mousse there? Yes.
这样可以吗?
Is it all right?
非常愉快的。这几乎和天使乐一样好吃。
Very pleasant. This is almost as good as Angel Delight.
大厨们，你们已经完成一半了。
Chefs, you are halfway through.
迈克，我很高兴。我们需要继续努力。
Mike, I'm happy. We need to crack on.
山姆，看这个。他们需要更多。
Sam, look at this. They need a bit more.
有点耗时，但是……
It's a bit time consuming, but...
对于那些已经烤好的蛋白派，可以开始制作了。
For those with meringues baked, the build can begin.
我们可以开始分层了。现在是推动的时候了。
We can start layering. And now is the time to push.
你必须非常快。
You have to be pretty quick.
一旦完成，他们的大门就会被关闭。
Once complete, their gateaus are put to rest.
我们看到了什么?
What do we see?
但伊曼纽尔和萨姆落后了。
But Emmanuel and Sam have fallen behind.
他叹了口气
HE SIGHS
蛋白霜煮过头了。
The meringue is overcooked.
对不起,山姆。我要把巧克力轻轻地放在上面。
Sorry, Sam. I'm going to place chocolate on the top gently.
比如，把它放在一起。
Like, to hold it together.
现在重做蛋白霜已经太晚了。
It's too late to remake a meringue.
在压力下。
Under pressure.
压力太大了。
Definitely under pressure.
你想让我再做一次蛋白霜吗?
You want me to make the meringue again?
好吧，试试吧。你有原料。
OK, go for it. You've got the ingredients.
大厨们，你们还有一个小时。
Chefs, you've got an hour left.
是的。会非常非常紧。
Yes. It'll be very, very tight.
当伊曼纽尔和山姆重新开始时，
As Emmanuel and Sam start again,
其他队用他们的看台继续前进。
the other teams push on with their stands.
哦,哔哔声。
Oh, BLEEP.
开始专注于装饰，展台
Start focusing on the decoration, the stand -
这需要尽快完成。
it needs to be done as soon as possible.
酷豆。
Cool beans.
别再说了。
Don't say that again.
很显然说凉豆并不酷。
Apparently it's not cool to say cool beans.
你又不是14岁了。
You're not 14 years old.
上周，第一名。
Last week, first place.
比如，自信程度很高?
Like, confidence levels, high?
这是我从来没做过的事，很挣扎。
Well, it's something I've never really done, so struggling.
祝你们好运。
Good luck, guys.
当然是在压力之下。
Under pressure, of course.
蛋白霜是整个甜点的主要部分。
Meringue is a major part of the whole dessert.
事情就是这样。这并不理想。
It is what it is. Which isn't ideal.
蛋白派对你有影响吗?有一点，是的。这很烦人，
Has the meringue got to you? A bit, yeah. It's annoying that,
你知道，这已经发生了。你认为你能按时完成吗?
you know, this has happened. Do you reckon you'll finish on time?
我是说，你的蛋白派在里面。
I mean, your meringues are in there.
蛋白派要做多久?37分钟。
How long does meringues take to cook? 37 minutes.
哦……
Oh...
大厨们，你们还有半小时。
Chefs, you have half an hour left.
半小时，大厨们。
Half an hour, chefs.
他们要担心的并不是大门。
Their gateaus aren't all they have to worry about.
现在，他们的展台设计将面临考验。
Now the designs for their stands will be put to the test.
英子和西奥，你们感觉怎么样?
Hideko and Theo, how are you feeling?
有点赶时间。感觉紧张吗?
A bit in a rush. Feeling stressed?
是的。大问题。稳定。
Yeah. Big problem. Stability.
建设本身也有挑战。
Construction comes with its own challenges.
如果它们碰巧掉了……我希望不会。你知道的…
If they happen to drop... I hope it doesn't. You know...
显然我们不希望它下降。它不会下降。
Obviously we don't want it to drop. It's not going to drop.
是的,是的。除非你搞砸了。
Yeah, yeah. Unless you jinx it.
它们拥有的组件越多，需要进行的连接就越多。
The more components they have, the more joins to make.
像树叶一样颤抖。
Literally shaking like a leaf.
整个宇宙崩溃的可能性越大…
And the more chances the whole thing could collapse...
希望稳定。
Hopefully stable.
不自信。
Not confident.
. .把蛋糕也带上。
..bringing the gateau with it.
叹了口气
SIGHS
哔哔声!是压力，压力让我受不了。
BLEEP! It's the pressure - the pressure is getting to me.
蛋白霜，要做好了。
The meringue - need to get it done.
等等，它要断了。
Wait, it's going to break.
那你们俩就有机会赚钱了。
You totes got a money shot then.
底部钻头断了。哔哔声。
The bottom bit broke off. BLEEP.
迈克尔。我很害怕。
Michael. I'm scared.
我们只是在等蛋白派。
We're just actually waiting for that meringue.
它会向右转。蛋白霜会很好吃的。
It will go right. That meringue is going to be right.
它必须是。
It has to be.
这是坏的。
This is broken.
我要把它藏起来。
I'm going to hide it.
它很乱。
It's very messy.
大厨们，你们还有15分钟，15分钟。
Chefs, you have 15 minutes remaining, 15 minutes.
荒谬。
Ridiculous.
你还好吗?
You OK?
是的。我不知道……
Yeah. I don't know...
稳定……
Stability...
哦，那真是过时了。
Oh, that's really gone out.
我不喜欢它。我们有点太静了。
I don't like it. We've gone a bit too static.
似乎没什么问题。
Seems to be all right.
显然，上次看起来还不错，所以……
Obviously, before, it looked all right last time, so...
. .我想十分钟后我们就会知道了。
..we'll find out in about ten minutes, I suppose.
大厨们，你们还有十分钟做杂烩……
Chefs, you have ten minutes left for your Feuille D'...
秋天的蛋糕要完成了。
Autumn cakes to be finished.
需要冷静一下。所以我在做蛋糕的装饰。
Needs to cool down. So I'm working on the decoration for the cake.
压力太大了。
Definitely under pressure.
四人份的玫瑰和巧克力蛋糕，收尾。
Rosace and chocolate band for four, for finishing.
所以乐队还不错。我相信这只是个简单的乐队。
So the band is not too bad. I'm sure it's just a simple band.
是的,很好。
Yeah, good.
这只是我们要努力解决的问题。
It's just the rosace which we're going to struggle with.
玫瑰是用精致的褶边做成的
The rosace is made of delicate ruffles
这是很难掌握的。
that are difficult to master.
走，走，走，走，走。如果团队不能快速行动……
Go, go, go, go, go. If the teams don't work fast...
哔哔声!. .巧克力会凝固的。
BLEEP! ..the chocolate will set.
玫瑰酱不怎么管用。
The rosace doesn't really work.
哔哔声。
BLEEP.
它说要快点。
It said do quickly.
哦,上帝。哔哔声!
Oh, God. BLEEP!
至少想弄点东西在上面。
Trying to get at least something to put on top.
所以所有这些巧克力都是……
So all these chocolates squigglies, from...
不要吃它们，我们需要它们。
Don't eat them, we need them.
你正要把它放进嘴里，是吗?
You were just about to put that in your mouth, weren't you?
别用手指摸巧克力。
Don't you finger the chocolate.
看起来不错。
That looks good.
现在最重要的是继续努力，把事情做好。
It's just now about cracking on and getting things done.
大厨们，你们还有一分钟，就一分钟。
Chefs, you have one minute left, just one minute.
来吧，宝贝。
Come on, baby.
如此脆弱。
So fragile.
基本上，我们必须从无到有。
We've got to make something out of nothing, basically.
我只有一次机会。
I got one chance.
我们不是墨守成规者。
We're not conformists.
我不确定它应该是这个样子，
I'm not sure it should look like that,
但我得给他们点什么
but I have to give them something.
大厨们，你们的时间到了。
Chefs, your time is up.
你的秘方挑战结束了。
Your Secret Recipe Challenge is over.
它代表……差不多。
It stands...just about.
四个福伊尔·德·秋曼
Four Feuille D'automne
还有四个精致的摊位，在三个半小时内设计完成。
and four exquisite stands, designed and built in three and a half hours.
伯努瓦和珍爱等着他们。
Benoit and Cherish await them.
我真的很喜欢你的立场。
I really like the way you interplay your stand.
你抬高高度，和其他选手相比，
You lift up the height, and compared to the rest of the contestants,
你在这方面很突出。
you stand out, for this.
谢谢你！
Thank you.
然而，我们可以看到你有一点挣扎
However, we can see that you struggled a little bit
有褶边的。
with the ruffle.
这不是我们要找的。
It's not what we're looking for.
对，就像木屑或木屑。
Yeah, it is like wood shavings or wood chips.
秋天了，秋天了。
It's autumn, autumn.
是的，现在是秋天，没错。
Yeah, it's autumn, all right, yeah.
希望它尝起来比看起来好一点。
Hopefully it will taste a little bit better than it looks.
这可不是什么好消息。
Well, it's not great news.
这不是巧克力慕斯。
It's not a chocolate mousse.
它更像是一种黏黏的，甘纳糖的，甜的东西。
It's closer to a kind of a sticky, ganachey, sweet thing.
我们的蛋白霜没煮熟。如你所见，它很软。
Our meringue is undercooked. As you can see, it is soft.
我不喜欢吃这个。
I didn't enjoy eating this.
对我来说很黏。
It's very slimy for me.
对不起。
Sorry.
从远处看，这是一个非常昂贵和高级的蛋糕。
From far, it's a very expensive and premium cake.
那是很远的地方。那就呆在那儿吧!
That's from far. Stay over there, then!
笑声
LAUGHTER
回来!
Get back!
她声称
SHE EXCLAIMS
当我走近看蛋糕时，
When I walk closer to look at the cake,
我只能看到两个圆盘，三个球，这很安全。
all I can see is just two disks, three balls - it's very safe.
这并不像真正的玫瑰那样优雅，但它们就在那里，
This is not as elegant as a proper rosace, but they are there,
有很多这样的人。
there are plenty of them.
蛋白霜烤得不够好，但至少酥脆了，
That meringue is not baked enough, but at least you've got crispiness,
这样我就可以吃了
so I can eat that.
巧克力慕斯太浓了，太黏了。
Chocolate mousse is so dense, is so gummy.
吃这片蛋糕真不舒服。
It's not enjoyable eating this slice of cake.
我将从证人席开始。
I will start with the stand.
底料给人一种时髦的感觉。花,
The base gives a nice little funky effect. The flower,
技术很棒，做得很好。
the technique is great, so well done.
这条褶边看起来很吸引人。
The ruffle looks quite appealing.
就这点而言，我认为你做得很好。
For that, I think you did very well.
巧克力慕斯很好吃。
The chocolate mousse is pleasant.
我喜欢吃你的蛋白霜。
I enjoyed eating your meringue.
烤得也很好。你控制好了自己的时间
Well-baked as well. You managed to control your time enough to be able
重新振作，犯错误，然后改正错误。
to bounce back and make a mistake and fix your mistake.
非常感谢。谢谢你！
Thank you very much. Thank you.
你给我们做了蛋糕。
You managed to serve us the gateau.
好吧，我想积极的一面，我只能说这么多了。
Well, I think for positive sides, that's about all that I can say.
是的。首先，我认为这个展位很有条理。
Yeah. First of all, the stand I think is very structured.
我还以为你们俩能有更多收获呢。
I was hoping for more from both of you.
嗯嗯。褶边，你少了一点，不够。
Mm-hm. The ruffle, you came up a bit short, there's not enough.
但至少要多做这些，并试着做一束花。没有完成。
But at least do plenty of this, and try to make a bouquet. Not finished.
再加一点巧克力慕斯盖在蛋白霜上
And a little bit of chocolate mousse to cap that meringue
是制作一份美味的羊腿菜的一部分。
is part of what makes a nice Feuille D'automne.
巧克力慕斯很重。
Chocolate mousse is quite heavy.
蛋白霜是生的，抱歉，我不能吃这个。
The meringue is uncooked, so, sorry, can't eat this.
蛋白派，来吧。这是我们的生意，这是我们的工作。
Meringues - come on. This is our trade, this is what we do.
我们做蛋白酥皮。不适合我，谢谢。
We do meringues. Not working for me, thank you.
好的。谢谢你！
OK. Thank you.
没有问题。
No problem.
天啊，来这个节目真是个坏主意。
Oh, God, this was a bad idea, to come on this show.
这是谁的主意?你的。
Whose idea was it? Yours.
是的，我们有点失望，因为，你知道，再一次，
Yeah, we feel disappointed, a bit, because, you know, again,
就像我们说的，我们是专业人士，所以…
like we say, we're professionals, so...
我们想成为专业人士。
Well, we're trying to be professionals.
我很擅长钓鱼，所以我可能会去钓鱼。
I'm really good at fishing, so I might take that up.
Showpiece是它的重要组成部分，它可以改变游戏规则。
The Showpiece is such a big part of it that that can be a game-changer.
你今天可以过得很糟糕，做一场精彩的表演，
You can have a rubbish day today, do an amazing Showpiece,
你是第一名。
and you're number one.
完全用巧克力制作一个展览品需要很多人
Constructing a Showpiece entirely from chocolate will require so many
这些元素让各支队伍有了“黄金时间”去锤炼
elements that the teams have been given a "golden hour" to temper and
准备好任何需要过夜的东西。
prepare anything that needs to set overnight.
你觉得谁最危险?
Who do you sense is most in danger?
我们甜蜜艺术实验室的朋友们真的会思考
Well, our friends from the Sweet Art Lab can actually think
不墨守成规，但如果要传递经典，
outside the box, but when it's about delivering the classics,
他们似乎有点挣扎。
they seem to struggle a little.
至于我，我很担心圣大卫酒店。
As for me, I'm worried about St David's Hotel.
在视觉方面，我对他们今天的作品感到非常失望。
Visual-wise, I was very disappointed with what they produced today.
名胜世界上周表现非常出色。
Resorts World did so well last week.
但很明显他们在挣扎。
But obviously they struggle.
如果他们想在这场比赛中继续前进，
If they want to go forward in this competition,
他们当然必须提高自己的水平。
they will certainly have to raise their game.
所以，最吸引人的门道之一就是希尔顿公园巷。
So, one of the most attractive gateaux was Hilton Park Lane.
他们做得很好。
They did quite well.
但是，你知道，我们看到了其他球队的反弹。
But, you know, we've seen the other teams bounce back.
一切都是为了游戏。好戏上演。
Everything is to play for. It's showtime.
小羊咩咩叫
LAMBS BLEAT
早上好，厨师们。
Good morning, chefs.
我们希望你们都从昨天的秘方挑战中恢复过来了。
We hope you all have recovered from yesterday's Secret Recipe Challenge.
评委们，请告诉我们你们选出的作品。
Judges, please tell us what you've chosen for today's Showpiece.
好了，厨师们，今天我们希望你们围绕这个主题做一个展示
Well, chefs, today we would like you to make a Showpiece around the theme
化装舞会的。"
of "masked ball."
你的作品必须包括两种不同的类型
Your Showpiece must include two different types
模制和填充的巧克力，总共八份。
of moulded and filled chocolate, for eight in total.
您的展品必须至少有一个活动部件。
Your Showpiece must have at least one moving part.
移动的部分会是某人的脸吗，
Can the moving part be someone's face,
当他们把它塞进嘴里的时候?
as they're stuffing it in their gobs?
绝对不是。
Absolutely not.
厨师们，你们昨晚只有一个小时的准备时间，
Chefs, you had one golden hour last night to prepare,
你还有四个小时来完成今天的挑战。
and you have four more hours to complete today's challenge.
你的时间从现在开始。
Your time starts now.
正确的。
Right.
显然有很多事要做，
Obviously a lot to do,
但如果我们继续努力，就会没事的。
but if we push on we should be fine.
你想要这个?是的。谢谢你！
You want this? Yeah. Thank you.
现在我只需要做面具了。
So now I've just got to do the mask.
我只是在上面涂了点巧克力。
I'm just coating it with a bit of chocolate.
自16世纪以来，假面舞会占据了
Since the 16th century, masked balls have occupied
国王和王后日历上的圣地
a hallowed place on the calendars of kings, queens
和整个欧洲的贵族
and nobility across Europe.
假面舞会就像一个优雅、顽皮的聚会。
A masked ball is like an elegant, naughty party.
我想去参加化装舞会。
I'd like to go to a masked ball.
听起来很有趣。
It sounds quite fun.
我不喜欢打扮。
I don't like dressing up.
说句公道话，我不喜欢派对。
I'm not a fan of parties, to be fair.
是的,对的。
Yeah, right.
参赛队伍必须将所有的魅力和成熟融入
The teams must channel all that glamour and sophistication into
完美的巧克力展示了这些壮观的事件。
immaculate chocolate Showpieces that evoke these spectacular events.
面具需要有超乎想象的细节。
The mask needs to have details beyond imaginations.
我们想看到很多奢侈的东西。
We want to see a lot of extravagance.
我们想玩得开心。
We want to have fun.
我们想看到运动，我们想看到音乐。
We want to see movement, we want to see music.
我希望厨师有创造力和创新精神。
I want the chef to be creative and innovative.
我想看到闪闪发光，香槟酒冒出来。
I want to see glitter, champagne popping up.
带我去舞会。
Take me to the ball.
除了他们的表演作品，他们还必须制作48个完美的糖果
Along with their Showpieces, they must produce 48 flawless bonbons
他们的颓废不亚于政党本身。
that are no less decadent than the parties themselves.
我们已经试过了。我认为它们是有效的。
We've tried and tested the favours. I think they work.
很明显，法官们可能会有不同的意见。
Obviously the judges might have a different opinion.
巧克力软糖就是要确保这些小形状
Chocolate bonbon is all about making sure those little shapes
都铸得很完美。
are cast perfectly.
它们需要在我的味蕾上探戈，给我一点
They need to tango on my palate and give me a bit of
cha-cha-cha。
cha-cha-cha.
你有香槟淋浴。
You have some champagne shower.
#戏剧!＃
# Drama! #
谁来摇一摇。
Someone shake it all.
对不起,Hideko。没关系。
Sorry, Hideko. It's OK.
所有的团队都花了他们的黄金时间来挑选元素
All the teams spent their golden hour casting elements
为了他们的展览。
for their Showpiece.
现在我们要看看结果如何。
Now we need to see how it's coming out.
总是很有挑战性的时刻。
Always quite a challenging moment.
需要帮忙吗，Hideko?不，没关系。
Need a hand, Hideko? No, it's OK.
对Hideko来说，现在是关键时刻。
And for Hideko, now is the moment of truth.
这就是我。
This is me.
这是一个酒窝。
This is a dimple.
早上好,伙计。早上好。早....
Morning, guys. Good morning. Morning.
你能多告诉我们一些关于Showpiece的事吗
Would you be able to tell us a bit more about that Showpiece
你今天在为我们创作吗?是的。
you are creating for us today? Yes.
所以，它会像一个舞厅。
So, it's going to be like a ballroom.
这些楼梯在展厅后面，
These stairs going behind the Showpiece,
而英子将站在最上面。
and it's going to be Hideko's on the top.
她一夜之间把自己的脸打了个精光。
She cast her own face overnight.
一张漂亮的脸。
A beautiful face.
运动的部分是什么?扇在脸上，
So what's the moving part going to be? Fans on top of the face,
就像一个粉丝。是的。
so like a fan. Yes.
当它……就像一种感觉。我在电影里见过。
When it... Like a feeling. I've seen it in films.
舞厅里有两种糖果
Inside the ballroom will be two types of bonbons -
白巧克力，里面有草莓玫瑰凝胶
a white chocolate, filled with strawberry rose gel
还有香槟甘纳许，
and champagne ganache,
还有一块金色斑点的黑巧克力
and a gold-flecked dark chocolate
里面有柚子胶和清酒甘纳许。
filled with yuzu gel and sake ganache.
我们现在可以尝尝清酒吗?
Can we taste some sake now?
当然，如果你愿意的话。
Yes, of course, if you want to.
这是用大米做的，对吗?
It's made from rice, is it?
发酵的大米。
Fermented rice.
毫米。
Mm.
哦!
Oh!
我的胸毛还不够长。
I don't have enough hairs on my chest for that.
哦，别这样，这是……
Oh, come on - it's...
Darryl和Bharat也在喝酒。
Darryl and Bharat are also hitting the bottle.
这是展览的主体结构。
This is the main structure for the Showpiece.
它是香槟酒瓶的形状。
It's the shape of a champagne bottle.
我们将有一个旋转面具和一些羽毛出来。
We're going to have a rotating mask and some feathers coming out.
在他们旋转的面具下面坐着24个白斑
Below their rotating mask will sit 24 white-flecked
黑巧克力软糖
dark chocolate bonbons
里面有甜焦糖和百香果凝胶。
filled with a sweet caramel and passion fruit gel.
旁边放着24块白巧克力，
Alongside will sit 24 white chocolates,
分层的白巧克力甘纳许和香槟凝胶。
layered with white chocolate ganache and champagne gel.
你还有什么要做的吗，要把香槟的主意带来吗?
Are you doing anything else, to kind of bring the champagne idea?
因为香槟，当它被转化成
Because champagne, when it's actually being transformed into
一种凝胶，它尝起来更像葡萄酒，而不是香槟的味道。
a gel, it tastes more like wine as opposed to the champagne element.
是的，我们已经试着提高了。
Yes, we've tried to boost it.
与什么?加些柠檬酸来恢复味道
With what? With some citric acid to bring back the flavour
香槟，因为其他的都很平淡，是的。
of the champagne, because otherwise it is quite flat, yeah.
这让我开始跳探戈了。
This just makes me starting to tango.
每个Showpiece都需要一个基地，团队可以制作基地
Every Showpiece needs a base, and the teams can make them
可达一米宽。
up to a metre wide.
伊曼纽尔和山姆正在用全宽度把面具拿回来
And Emmanuel and Sam are using the full width to take the mask back
回到它的精神家园。
to its spiritual home.
我们在做一个威尼斯主题的展览。
We're doing a sort of Venice-themed Showpiece.
我们以水为基础，所以我们想，
We've got a water as our base, so we thought,
为什么不把我们的糖果和水混在一起呢?
why not incorporate one of our bonbons with the water?
所以我们得到了一种波浪效应。
So we've gone for a sort of waved effect.
他们的波浪效应糖果将是分层的
Their waved-effect bonbons will be layered
配上白巧克力、甘草甘纳许和樱桃凝胶。
with white chocolate liquorice ganache, and cherry gel.
他们还会提供24块黑巧克力糖果
They will also serve 24 dark chocolate bonbons
里面有焦糖和血橙凝胶。
filled with caramel and blood orange gel.
威尼斯有最漂亮、最优雅、最令人印象深刻的面具
Venice have got the most beautiful, elegant and impressive masks
在这个世界上。
in the world.
现在，如果你选择威尼斯这个主题，面具就必须成功。
Now, if you went for this theme of Venice, the mask needs to make it.
你能带我去吗?我会的。明天我们就走。
Will you take me there? I would. Tomorrow we go.
我可以不来吗?你可以。
Can I not come? You can.
你可以。你会跳一整天的舞。
You can. You will be dancing all day long.
每队的展示作品必须包含一个活动部件。
Each team's Showpiece must incorporate a moving part.
这是中间那个带着面具的动作。
That's for the movement in the middle, with the mask.
我让扇子一直在动，就像羽毛一样，在动。
I'm making the fan moving, always, like a feather, moving.
虽然大多数人选择电池驱动的运动…
While most are opting for battery-operated motion...
我们还带了一个玩具坦克。
We've actually brought a toy tank.
我们把船放在上面，它会绕着水转。
We'll have the boat on it, and it's going to go around the water.
迈克尔和丽贝卡的设计就没那么有活力了。
Michael and Rebekah's design is a little less dynamic.
我们去找准备参加舞会的人，
We've gone for somebody getting ready to go to a ball,
我们做了一个梳妆台。
so we've done a vanity table.
梳妆台前面的抽屉，
The drawer that's in the front of the dressing table,
你可以拔出来，所以严格来说我们有活动部件。
you'll be able to pull out, so technically we have moving parts.
技术上。
Technically.
他们的梳妆台里放着白巧克力糖果
Inside their vanity table will be white chocolate bonbons
铺上草莓泥和香槟凝胶，
lined with strawberry puree and champagne gel,
黑巧克力夹心糖上撒着百香果，
and dark chocolate bonbons layered with passion fruit,
蜂蜜和白巧克力。
honey and white chocolate.
嗨,丽贝卡。嗨,迈克尔。
Hi, Rebekah. Hi, Michael.
你好。你好。迈克尔，我听说你有另一个自我
Hello. Hello. Now, Michael, I heard a rumour you have an alter ego -
对吗?是的，我曾经有另一个自我。
is that correct? I used to have an alter ego, yeah.
几年前，我曾经是一名变装演员。
Years ago now, I used to be a drag performer.
真的吗?
Really?
她的名字叫蒂蒂·麦克维蒂。
Her name was Titty McVitie.
她选了什么样的衣服?
What sort of outfits did she go for?
任何适合她的衣服。她是个大女孩了。
Any ones that would fit her. She's a big girl.
大厨们，你们有一个小时的时间。
Chefs, you've had one hour.
离化装舞会还有三个小时。
You have three hours left until the masked ball.
我希望我能走，我就不用一直呆在这里打扫了。
I hope I get to go, I don't have to stay here sweeping up all the time.
我的仙女教母来了。
My fairy godmother's here.
上帝!
God!
我要开始吃糖果了。
I'm starting on the bonbons.
糖果虽然很小，
A bonbon, while small in size,
由许多元素组成，赋予它独特的高端吸引力。
is comprised of many elements that give it a distinct high-end appeal.
首先是美丽的外观。
And first on the list is a beautiful exterior.
手持螺丝刀。
Hand-held screwdriver.
他模仿电动工具
HE IMITATES POWER TOOL
我要用它来做一个漩涡的效果。
I'm going to use it to make a swirly effect.
这让它的动作非常快，这样你就能得到清晰的线条。
It gives it a really fast motion, and that's when you get clean lines.
你不能用手指这样做。
You can't do that with your finger.
我们确实喜欢小玩意。
We do like a gadget.
接下来是精细铸造的外壳。
Next, a finely cast outer shell.
它很脆弱。
It's very flimsy.
结构巧克力工程师。
Structural chocolate engineers.
现在我要把凝胶和甘纳许填满。
I'm now going to fill the gel and the ganache.
在每一个环节，饮食体验都是最重要的，
At every turn, the eating experience is paramount,
每一点都和造型一样重要。
and every bit as important as the look.
你觉得我应该把香槟放在底部还是顶部?
Do you think I should put champagne on the bottom, or at the top?
上面是软凝胶，然后是甘纳许。
Top, so when they bite it's the soft gel, then ganache.
每一层都需要技巧和技巧。
Each layer requires skill and finesse.
我正在给巧克力盖上盖子，把它摊开
I'm just capping the chocolates now, spreading it out
用调色刀。我喜欢尽可能快地走。
with a palette knife. I like to go as fast as we can.
速度是最重要的。
Speed is of the essence.
动作太慢，巧克力会凝固。
Move too slowly and the chocolate will set...
这可不太好。
This is not good.
. .留下一个不整洁不精确的糖果。
..leaving an untidy and imprecise bonbon.
不正常!
WHACK!
我发现巧克力有问题。略厚。
I found a problem on the chocolate. Slightly thick.
有点打破了……
Kind of break that...
困难并没有就此结束。
And the difficulties don't end there.
随着糖果的摆放，注意力转移到他们的展示品上。
With bonbons setting, attention switches to their Showpieces.
很多人在看。
Lots of people watching.
但山姆的超宽水基…
But Sam's extra-wide watery base...
把哔哔声板贴在那里不是个好主意。
It was a bad idea to stick that BLEEP board on there.
. .可能已经被扔进下水道了。
..may have already gone down the plughole.
我就知道我们不该这么做。
I knew we shouldn't have done it.
大厨们，你们还有一个小时。
Chefs, you have one hour left.
那是一个小时。
That's one hour.
哔哔声。
BLEEP.
这个开了吗?
Is this on?
时间不多了。
Time is starting to run out.
我们得埋头干我们该干的事。
We need to get our heads down and just get on with what we need to do.
我必须组装。
I have to assemble.
当大多数团队开始将他们的展示作品变为现实时，
While most of the teams start to bring their showpieces to life,
对山姆和伊曼纽尔来说，
for Sam and Emmanuel,
他们的威尼斯梦破灭了。
a shattered base has left their Venice dream high and dry.
这将是一个有趣的谜题。
It's going to be a fun puzzle.
我现在得好好玩拼图了。
I'm going to need to be good at jigsaws right now.
这是一个让我非常兴奋的挑战。
This is one of the challenges that I am so excited with.
面具和舞会。
Masks and ball.
Hideko用自己的脸做了面具。
The Hideko has actually used their own face for that mask.
我希望她给它上色，让它变得华丽而有趣。
I hope she colours it and she makes it quite flamboyant and fun as well.
达里尔和巴拉特。
Daryl and Bharat.
他们将自己的主体结构描述为香槟酒瓶。
They describe their main structure as a champagne bottle.
它更接近一瓶水，你说呢?
It's closer to a bottle of water, wouldn't you say?
但是，嘿，这可能是可行的。
But, hey, it may work with the scheme of things.
丽贝卡和迈克尔，你觉得他们怎么样?
Rebekah and Michael, what you think of them?
视情况而定。有时候，细节决定成败。
It depends. The devil, sometimes, is in the details.
是的。问题是，
Yes. The question with them,
他们的展示会上有足够的细节吗?
will there be enough details on their showpiece?
我们的团队来自希尔顿公园巷。
And we've got our team from The Hilton Park Lane.
显然，他们有一点压力。
Obviously, they are a little bit under pressure.
他们必须加快速度，加快速度，继续前进，继续前进，更快。
They have to rapido, rapido and move on, move on and faster, now.
只需要在上面加一点蓝色的褶皱。
Just a little bit of blue pucker right over the top.
对，就是这样。试着有时间去做一些漂亮的东西。
Right, that's it. Try and have time to build something nice.
大厨们，你们还有半小时。半小时，大厨们。
Chefs, you have half an hour left. Half an hour, chefs.
我们，我们快到时间了。
We, we are getting close now to time.
我们要集中精力完成任务。
We need to focus on getting finished.
不是……
Not...
在它凝固之前我需要它。
I need this before it sets.
好吧，继续。继续。
Right, go on. Go on.
这很好。
That's fine.
噢!你在找什么?
Ooh! What are you looking for?
的球。
The balls.
哇，哇，哇，哇，哇。你不知道里面有什么。
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa. You don't know what's in it.
哦，少了一个。
Oh, one short.
你确实需要一只稳健的手。
You definitely need a steady hand.
哔哔声。
BLEEP.
这什么?那是维斯帕巧克力棒，你把它粘在上面了吗?
What that? That's a Wispa bar, is that, you're sticking on the top there?
哦，我喜欢威斯帕棒。我做的事。你最喜欢什么巧克力?
Oh, I love Wispa bars. I do. What's your favourite chocolate?
Twix。Twix吗?毫米。真的吗?是的。
Twix. Twix? Mm. Really? Yeah.
伊曼纽尔。为什么不呢?
Emmanuel. Why not?
糕点师?希尔顿公园巷?嗯，你知道的。抱歉，伙计们，你们知道。
Pastry chef? Hilton Park Lane? Well, you know. Sorry, guys, you know.
最喜欢的巧克力棒?Twix。
Favourite chocolate bar? Twix.
是的。你知道我最喜欢吃什么吗?那是什么?人脸形状的东西。
Yes. Do you know what I really fancy eating? What's that? Something in the shape of a human face.
你有什么东西吗?等待,等待。
Have you got anything? Wait, wait.
你为什么不试试这件呢?哦，我能试穿一下吗?
Why don't you try this one on? Oh, can I try this on?
是的。显然，它是巧克力。
Yes. Obviously, it chocolate.
哦。就像金·凯瑞。
Oh. It's like Jim Carrey.
啊。每件展品的前面和中心都是面具。
Ah. Front and centre of every showpiece is the mask.
是的。这巧克力。哦,哔哔声。
Yeah. That chocolate. Oh, BLEEP.
将精美的手工绘制的巧克力粘在一起需要细致的触摸。
Attaching finely cast hand-painted chocolate requires a delicate touch.
呼吸,呼吸。
Breathe, breathe.
最轻微的错误举动……
The slightest wrong move...
现在是一天中最危险的时候。
Riskiest part of the day right now.
. .他们所有的努力都会付诸东流。
..and all their hard work will be destroyed.
好吧，好吧，好吧，你可以放手了。
OK, OK, OK, you can let go.
我要放手吗?
I let go?
是的。把我的手冻住。我也不在乎
Yeah. Just freeze my hand. I don't care.
大厨们，你们还有十分钟。还有十分钟。
Chefs, you have ten minutes left. That's ten minutes left.
哔哔声。
BLEEP.
本来可以更整洁的，但我们时间很紧。
Could be a lot neater, but we're really pushed for time.
哦，莎啦啦。
Ooh, sha la la.
大厨们，你们还有五分钟。那是五分钟。
Chefs, you have five minutes left. That's five minutes.
明白了，明白了。去做吧。
Got it, got it. Go ahead.
你可以的。我得把它放下，然后滑动。
You've got this. I'm going to have to drop it and slide it.
哔哔声。在桌子边上。
BLEEP. On the edge of the table.
在吗?是的。
There? Yeah.
把面具放在那里是因为我对剧本不满意
Put the mask there because I wasn't happy with the writing
实际上是在镜子上，用来盖住它。
that's actually on the mirror, to kind of cover it.
我们能不能把可可咬掉的东西刮掉然后在镜子上写点更好的东西?
Can we scrape that Cocoa bit off and try to write something better on the mirror or no?
只是在画黑线，好让我们的贡多拉跟着走。
Just painting the black line for our gondola to follow.
Oop……哔哔声!
Oop... BLEEP!
哔哔声。
BLEEP.
大厨们，你们还有一分钟。这是一分钟。
Chefs, you have one minute left. That's one minute.
感受压力。
Feel the pressure.
我们，呃，得快点了。
We, er, need to get a move on.
大厨们，你们的时间到了。
Chefs, your time is up.
哦,哦。请离开你的展品。
Uh-oh, uh-oh. Please step away from your showpieces.
所以，没关系，没关系。别担心。
So, it's OK, it's OK. Don't worry.
这太疯狂了。
That was mental.
这是聪明的。
That's clever.
不融化。
Don't melt.
这些巧克力很好吃。
Them chocolates are nice.
只是…
Just...
短短五小时内就上演了四场精彩的假面舞会。
Four stunning masked ball showpieces in just five hours.
但是谁将赢得决赛的席位呢
But who will earn their place in the final stages of the competition
谁不会给人留下深刻印象呢?
and who will fail to impress?
我们带来了一点乐趣。
A bit of fun, we bring.
太酷了。我想我要在那儿待一整天。
That is cool. I'm going to be there all day, I think.
我喜欢摇摆的小贡多拉。
I like the little wiggling gondola.
你的小提琴，你如何让它充满活力是因为你如何融入
Your violin, how you bring it alive is because how you incorporate the
颜色。做得很好。
colour in. Really nicely done.
总的来说，你的故事很精彩，但对我来说，
Overall, you have a great story, but, for me,
你的面具不够坚固。
your mask is not strong enough.
我会看面具，让它更有戏剧性。
I would have looked the mask to have more drama.
提醒我们我们拥有什么。
Remind us what we have.
樱桃凝胶，然后是甘草樱桃甘纳许。
Cherry gel and then a liquorice and cherry ganache.
从视觉上看，非常吸引人。
Visually, very appealing.
它看起来就像一个波浪。
And it actually looks like a wave.
这种吃的感觉很有趣。
The eating sensation is quite intriguing.
樱桃和甘草的味道很浓，我很喜欢。
The cherry and the liquorice kick in and I actually quite like it.
另一个是血橙和焦糖。
And the other one is a blood orange and caramel.
蛋壳很薄很精致，但是太奶油了。
The shell is very thin and elegant, but it's too creamy.
我想让巧克力酱更有质感。
I want the ganache to have a little more texture.
非常感谢。
Thank you very much.
他呼出
HE EXHALES
哦,上帝。
Oh, God.
请给我们看看你的活动部件好吗?
Could you show us your moving part, please?
抽屉打开了。
The drawer opens.
好吧，好吧。
OK, all right.
同时，巧克力盒的盖子也会脱落。哦,好吧。
Also, the lid comes off the chocolate box. Oh, OK.
我有点失望，因为它在桌子上有点裸露。
I was a bit disappointed because it was a little bit bare on the table.
然后，看着你的镜子，
And then, looking at your mirror,
你能告诉我们背后的文字是什么吗?
could you please tell us what is the writing behind?
上面确实写着"去参加舞会了，抱抱"
It did say "Gone to the ball, XOXO",
但我并不满意。所以我把面具放在那里。
but I wasn't happy with it. That's why I put the mask there.
这就是正确使用口罩的方法。
So that was the proper use of the mask.
它实际上已经被蒙住了!它实际上被蒙住了!
It actually has masked! It actually masked!
我们来尝尝吧?红色的是草莓和香槟。
Shall we taste? The red one is a strawberry and champagne.
从视觉上看，还不错。
Visually, it's not too bad.
你把红色放进去是因为你想把草莓放进去。
You put the red in because you want to bring in the strawberry.
草莓味的，我完全尝不出味道，而且有点粉末状。
Strawberry, I could not taste it at all and it's a bit powdery.
你能提醒我们这里面是什么吗?
Can you remind us what's inside this one?
这是百香果巧克力酱。
It's a passion fruit ganache.
它看起来不像一块令人兴奋的巧克力。
It doesn't look like an exciting chocolate to look at.
这有点悲伤。
It's a little bit sad.
但总的来说，巧克力的浇铸，
But, overall, the casting of the chocolate,
看起来你投得很好。
it looks like you cast it nicely.
你的百香果很香。
Your passion fruit is fragrant.
是的。非常感谢。
Yeah. Thank you very much.
我的第一印象非常深刻。
My first impression is, very impressive.
我很喜欢你画面具的方式。
I really like the way you paint the mask.
很好。工作的整洁性有了极大的提高。
Very nice. Neatness of work has improved tremendously.
我记得第一轮，你差点就输了，
I remember the first round, where you almost went,
如果你想进入决赛，这就是你要做的。
and this is where it needs to be if you want to be in the final.
是的。
Yeah.
提醒我们一下你的巧克力里面有什么。
Remind us what you have inside your chocolates for us.
是的，我们有香槟，白巧克力和覆盆子。
Yes, so, we have the champagne, white chocolate and raspberry.
我很喜欢你放进去的铜，
I really like the copper that you put in,
你用的那个小玩意。
the little gadget that you use.
一把螺丝刀。这是一个很好的技巧。
A screwdriver. It's quite a nice technique.
我不太热衷。
I am not too keen.
它尝起来不像香槟。
It just doesn't taste like champagne.
现在尝起来像廉价酒。
It tastes like cheap wine now.
还有一个。百香果和焦糖。
There is another one. Passion fruit and caramel.
我真的很喜欢底部。
I really like the bottom.
我觉得做得很漂亮。
I think that is really beautifully done.
这一次，我愿意回到一周中的任何一天。
This one, I would go back to any day of the week.
百香果釉。
Passion fruit glaze.
可爱。我开始恰恰恰恰!
Lovely. I start to cha-cha-cha!
哦，真漂亮!
Ooh, it's beautiful!
哇，真漂亮。我喜欢它。
Wow, it's so beautiful. I love it.
百香果和焦糖很搭。
The passion fruit just kicks in with your caramel.
耸人听闻的。做得很好。干得好，伙计们。
Sensational. Well done. Good job, guys.
谢谢你！谢谢你！干得好，伙计们。
Thank you. Thank you. Well done, guys.
这是移动。
It's moving.
是的。你看到了身高，看到了红色面具。
Yeah. You see height, you see a red mask.
我认为这是一个非常戏剧性的作品。
A very dramatic piece, I think.
这是一个巧克力杯吗?是的。
Is this a chocolate cup? Yes.
你要香槟吗?
Would you like champagne?
是的,请。他们给了她一些酒。
Yes, please. They've given her some booze.
这是聪明的。
That's clever.
哇!哦!
Whoa! Oh!
哦,lo-lo-lo-lo-lo-lo-lo-lo !笑声
Oh, lo-lo-lo-lo-lo-lo-lo-lo! LAUGHTER
好主意?
Uh, good idea?
请。
Please.
你把自己的脸弄得很难看。
Well, a good effort that you cast your own face.
然而，这个面具让我想起了Lady Gaga，那件生牛肉装。
However, the mask reminds me of Lady Gaga, the raw beef dress.
笑声
LAUGHTER
直走。各处的装饰都很粗糙。
Straight away. The finishing everywhere is really rough.
如果你想在比赛中取得进步，
If you want to progress in this competition,
你需要注意你的整洁。
you will need to address your neatness.
我们在很多场合都见过你们这样。
We've seen that on too many occasions with you guys.
我们来尝尝吧?那个是柚子果酱
Shall we taste? That one is a yuzu jam
一杯黑巧克力和清酒甘纳许。
and a dark chocolate and sake ganache.
柚子很香。
The yuzu is very fragrant.
如果说有什么不同的话，那就是我缺少一点清酒，
If anything, I'm lacking a little bit of sake,
因为如果它在巧克力酱里，就会有很多苦味。
because if it's in the ganache, we've got a lot of bitterness.
下一个。香槟、白巧克力和玫瑰酒。
Next one. Champagne, white chocolate and rose.
甘纳许的味道和香槟混在一起非常微妙。
The ganache comes in with the champagne very, very subtle.
然而，当我把它转回去时，
However, when I turn it back,
我觉得选角没有做好。
I think the casting was not properly done.
选角不对。商店里到处都是，但我是说
The casting is wrong. It is all over the shop, but I mean
甚至是可以接受的。
way out of even anything acceptable.
这让我们很难享受它。
It makes it very difficult to enjoy.
嗯。
Mmm.
那瓶香槟可以给我吗?
Can I take the bottle of champagne?
我要一杯好酒。谢谢你！谢谢你！
I'll have a proper glass. Thank you. Thank you.
不能再糟了。不能更糟了。
It couldn't be worse. Couldn't be worse.
基于这两个挑战，
Based on both challenges,
Benoit和珍惜现在将对球队进行排名，只有前三名
Benoit and Cherish will now rank the teams and only the top three will
在比赛的最后阶段顶替他们的位置。
take their place in the final stages of the competition.
你参加比赛不是为了离开，你想赢得比赛。
You don't enter a competition to leave, you want to win it.
另一个团队都是大酒店，大团队。
The other team is all big hotel, big team.
我们只是个小公司。
We are only, like, a little company.
是的，这将是一种胜利。
Yeah, it will be kind of a victory to go through.
但这显然将是一个艰难的判断……
But it will obviously be a tough judgment...
. .所以…我们不知道。
..so...we don't know.
希望，希望我们能留下来。
Hopefully, hopefully we stay.
猫头鹰咄
OWL HOOTS
Benoit和珍惜已经做出了决定。
Benoit and Cherish have made their decision.
第一名的队伍在两项挑战中都表现出色，
The team in first place excelled in both challenges,
尤其是在昨天的秘方挑战中。
especially in yesterday's secret recipe challenge.
恭喜你……
Congratulations...
. .希尔顿公园巷的伊曼纽尔和山姆。
..Emmanuel and Sam from Hilton Park Lane.
你晋级到比赛的下一阶段了。
You are through to the next stage in the competition.
第二名是来自名胜世界的Darryl和Bharat。
In second place are Darryl and Bharat from Resorts World.
恭喜你，你也通过了。
Congratulations - you are also through.
那么圣大卫酒店的迈克尔和丽贝卡，
Which leaves Michael and Rebekah from St David's Hotel,
还有来自Sweet Art Lab的Hideko和Theo。
and Hideko and Theo from Sweet Art Lab.
我不太喜欢我接下来要做的事
I'm not a massive fan of what I have to do next
因为说实话，你们都是了不起的人，更不用说厨师了。
because you guys, honestly, are amazing people, let alone chefs.
但是，经过深思熟虑，
But, after much deliberation,
评委们决定今晚离开我们的队伍是…
the judges decided that the team who will be leaving us tonight is...
. .迈克尔和丽贝卡。
..Michael and Rebekah.
做得很好。做得很好。
Well done. Well done.
我们很失望要回家了
We're disappointed to be going home,
但我们每一分钟都很享受，
but we've enjoyed every minute of it,
所以，是的，我不会改变它。我们已经做了…
so, yeah, like, I wouldn't change it. We've done...
我想改变…也许今天就把展品换了!
I'd change...change the showpiece today, maybe!
你知道吗，你已经为自己感到骄傲了。
Hey, you know, you've done yourself proud.
你工作很努力。哦,是的。你工作很努力。
You've worked hard. Oh, yeah. You've worked hard.
你工作很努力。
You've worked so hard.
现在回到正常的生活中会很奇怪。
It's going to be weird going back to normal life now.
试着在我们之间建立一个小小的家庭。
Trying to build a little family unit between us all.
希望我们能一直保持联系，继续学习。是的。
Hopefully we always stay in touch and keep on learning. Yep.
你的想法很好。
You've got good ideas.
我的意思是，创意是存在的。
I mean, originality is there.
我想我们会出去的。
I thought we would go out.
通过。通过了下一轮。
Passed through. Passed through the next round.
下次……
Next time...
走，走，走，走。
Go, go, go, go.
. .第二轮预赛开始。
..the second set of heats begin.
后退，后退，后退，后退。
Back, back, back, back.
有六个全新的专业团队。
With six brand-new professional teams.
如果出了问题，都是他的错。
If it all goes wrong, it's his fault.
谁将掌握这些微缩模型?
Who will master the miniatures?
这些很漂亮。
These are beaut.
还有她的法式蛋糕梦……
And whose patisserie dreams...
别倒霉，别倒霉!
Don't jinx it, don't jinx it!
. .会以一场巨大的混乱告终吗?
..will end in a monumental mess?
哦,哔哔声!
Oh, BLEEP!
我拒绝吃这个。
I refuse to eat this.
这太残忍了。
That was brutal.
大家好，欢迎来到《烘焙大赛:专业版》。
Hello, and welcome to Bake Off: The Professionals.
我叫汤姆·艾伦。
My name's Tom Allen.
利亚姆·查尔斯报道。四个名字，两个很有趣的人。
I'm Liam Charles. Four first names, two really fun guys.
我们正在寻找英国最好的专业糕点师。
We're searching for Britain's best professional pastry chefs.
好吧，我在寻找幸福，当然，这也是，为什么不呢?
Well, I'm searching for happiness but, sure, that too, why not?
今天我们有六支新队伍准备给大家留下深刻印象。
And today we have six new teams ready to impress.
我们去接他们好吗?哦，是的，我们走吧!这不是很有趣吗?
Shall we go and meet them? Oh, yes, let's! Isn't this fun!
利亚姆，你就像杰米·奥利弗和我的糕点师瓦莱丽。
Liam, you're like the Jamie Oliver to my Patisserie Valerie.
最后一次……
Last time...
第一组预赛以一场惊心动魄的比赛结束
The first set of heats ended with a nerve-shattering
展示品的挑战。
showpiece challenge.
该死的哔哔声。你觉得它能撑得住吗?
What the BLEEP. Do you think it's going to hold?
还有甜心实验室、希尔顿公园巷和名胜世界……
And Sweetheart Lab, Hilton Park Lane and Resorts World...
这是精神。
That's mental.
. .成为第一支进入6强的队伍。
..Became the first teams to make the final six.
现在我们迎来了六个全新的团队…
Now we meet six brand-new teams...
我们确实很紧张，但我们准备好了。走,走。
We're nervous, definitely, but we're ready for today. Go, go.
我想说这是我做过的最重要的事情
I would say this is the biggest thing I've done
就糕点而言。
in terms of patisserie.
. .当他们准备面对世界知名头目的审判时
..As they prepare to face the judgment of world-renowned head
糕点师贝努瓦和珍爱。
patissieres Benoit and Cherish.
我们会一直盯着你。
We will be watching you at all times.
我为他们担心。
I'm scared for them.
. .还有两项艰巨的挑战。
..And two daunting challenges.
我不想去想现在的时间。
I don't want to think about the time now.
我们将会发现这些队伍中是否有…
We're about to discover if any of these teams...
这些鱼很漂亮。
These baps are beautiful.
. .拥有它所需要的一切。
..Have what it takes.
. .加冕冠军……完成了。
..To be crowned champions... Finish up.
. .《烘焙大赛:专业人士》
..Of Bake Off: The Professionals.
是的。
Yeah.
很神奇的。
Amazing.
在接下来的两天里
Over the next two days,
这六支新的专业糕点师队伍
these six new teams of professional pastry chefs
必须在最高水平上竞争才能获得一席之地
will have to compete at the highest level to earn a place
在下一轮比赛中。
in the next round of the competition.
祝你好运。
Good luck.
大厨们好，欢迎来到《烘焙大赛:专业厨房》。
Hello, chefs, and welcome to the Bake Off: The Professionals kitchen.
你们将在这里与英国最好的糕点师进行较量，
You're here to test yourself against the best pastry chefs in the UK,
只有你能做到最好。
and only your very best will do.
评委们的第一个挑战，迷你经典。
So, the judges' first challenge, miniature classics.
这是对传统糕点技艺的真正考验。
A true test of traditional patisserie skills.
你们必须生产两批，每批24个，
You must produce two batches, 24 of each,
每批面点都必须完全相同。
and each pastry within those batches must be absolutely identical.
我选择了新桥。
I've chosen Pont Neuf.
这是一种法式经典糕点，有酥皮
It's a French classical pastry, which has a puff pastry case
内馅有苹果泥、法式酥皮和泡芙酥皮。
filled with an apple compote, creme patissiere and choux pastry.
虽然这是一个非常简单的汇编，
Though it's a very simple compilation,
这在技术上具有挑战性。
it is technically challenging.
和珍惜。大厨们，我选了柠檬挞。
And Cherish. Chefs, I've chosen Tarte au Citron.
我想看看这个美丽精致的贝壳
I want to see this beautiful, delicate shell
美味的馅料捕捉到了柠檬的美妙味道。
with delicious filling that captures the amazing taste of lemon.
请注意，厨师们，这是我的最爱之一。
Be warned, chefs, this is one of my all-time favourites.
别让我失望。
Do not disappoint me.
我不知道厨师们怎么样，珍爱，
I don't know about the chefs, Cherish,
但我绝不会让你失望
but I would never disappoint you.
不敢。所以,厨师,
Wouldn't dare. So, chefs,
你有三个半小时的时间，现在开始计时。
you have three and a half hours and your time starts now.
好了，开始吧。你能把下面的筛子递给我吗?
All right, we're on. Can you pass me my sieve from down there?
四个鸡蛋，细砂糖，黄油。
Four eggs, caster sugar, butter.
要在三个半小时内制作48个模型
With 48 miniatures to produce in just three and a half hours...
我们有很多事要做。
We've got a lot to do.
. .团队管理和组织将是关键。
..Team management and organisation will be key.
小心你的腿，小心你的腿。
Watch your legs, watch your legs.
我们知道我们的计划是什么。我们知道自己是如何计时的
We know what our plan is. We know how we timed ourselves,
这就是我们要做的。
so that's what we're going to do.
全新的热火，六支新队伍。
Brand-new heat, six new teams.
我想让厨师们给我展示他们所有的手艺，然后给我摆出来。
I want the chefs to show me all they have and put it out for me.
我想看到的是24的创新和创意
What I would like to see is 24 innovative and creative
香橼酒。它是由sablee制成的，一种甜酥皮，
Tarte au Citron. It's made from sablee, a sweet pastry casing,
里面是漂亮柔滑的柠檬馅。
and filled with a beautiful, silky smooth, lemon filling.
它们必须精确、一致，最重要的是，
They have to be precise, identical and, most important,
我想让他们在香橼酒上贴上自己的印记。
I want them to put their own stamp on the Tarte au Citron.
厨师们必须在每一步都表现出色
The chefs will have to demonstrate excellence at every step
如果他们想要达到评委严苛的标准。
of the bake if they're to meet the judges' exacting standards.
是啊，别这样。
Yeah, don't do it like this.
把所有的都放进去。这不是偶数。
Just put all of it. That's not even.
队长穆斯塔法和他经验不足的队友
And team captain Mustapha and his less experienced team-mate
我们仍然充满信心。
are still feeling confident.
我们有技能。我知道这很有压力
We've got the skills. I know it's a pressure,
但我们一定会做到的。
but we'll make it happen for sure.
穆斯塔法不仅是一名副糕点师，还担任讲师
As well as being a sous pastry chef, Mustapha also instructs
Clink是一家在监狱培训囚犯的慈善机构
at the Clink, a charity that works in prisons training inmates
出狱后在高级餐厅工作。
for careers in fine dining after their release.
他选择了凯文，一个才华横溢但刚从Clink毕业的学生，
He's chosen Kevin, a talented but recent graduate of the Clink,
和他一起参加比赛。
to join him in the competition.
穆斯塔法的玻璃圆顶上有层层柠檬玛德琳海绵蛋糕，
Mustapha's glazed domes with layers of lemon madeleine sponge,
柠檬蛋白霜慕斯，
lemon meringue mousse,
柠檬果酱和柠檬奶油可能看起来不像柠檬蛋挞，
lemon marmalade and lemon cream may not look like a Tarte au Citron,
但它尝起来肯定像。
but it should certainly taste like one.
说实话，我在这里一直很安全。
I've played safe in here, honestly.
最重要的是味道。
It's just all about the flavour.
对于他们的口味，凯利和凯蒂要做点什么
For their flavours, Kelly and Katie are going for something
更有实验性一点。
a little more experimental.
我们决定把伯爵茶放进去。
We decided to put Earl Grey into it.
有一些香草的味道。
It's got some vanilla tones going through it.
它还是很有柑橘味，所以我觉得柠檬还是最吸引人的，
It's still quite citrusy, so I think lemon is still the star attraction,
但是你在后面看到了这个。
but you've just got this at the back.
还有这个可爱的香草味的。
As well, just this lovely, vanilla-y, ooh.
凯利和凯蒂在著名的WI烹饪学校教糕点，
Kelly and Katie teach patisserie at the renowned WI Cookery School,
他们渴望证明WI还有更多的东西
and they're keen to prove there's more to the WI
而不仅仅是果酱和维多利亚海绵蛋糕
than just jam and Victoria sponge.
他们的柚子酒将会看到一个光滑的柠檬巴瓦卢瓦圆顶
Their Tarte au Citron will see a glazed lemon bavarois dome
周围是佛手柑凝乳和茶味凝胶
surrounded by bergamot curd and, for their tea flavoured gel
和萨博利基地，他们用的不是普通的伯爵茶。
and sablee base, they're using no ordinary Earl Grey.
这是一种特殊的混合物。
It's a special blend.
它叫《少女灰》。
It's called Girly Grey.
显然，作为一支全女子球队，
Obviously, being an all girl team as well,
我们觉得这是个不错的小…
we thought that was a nice little...
闻起来好吗?这里有一点乐趣。
Does it smell good? A bit of fun there.
很有柑橘味。
It's very citrusy.
闻起来很有柑橘味，所以我明白了。
It smells very citrusy, so I see the connection.
你知道我喜欢你什么吗?
You know what I like about you?
女孩的力量。
Girl power.
肯定。加油，女性力量!
Definitely. Go, girl power!
不会让我失望的。
Not going to disappoint me.
绝对不会。绝对不是。
Definitely not. Absolutely not.
凯莉和凯蒂并不是唯一依靠女性力量的人。
Kelly and Katie aren't the only ones relying on a bit of girl power.
我带来了我女儿的尺子。
I brought my daughter's ruler.
她不知道我拿了，但宽度正好。
She doesn't know I've got it, but it's the right width.
除了他女儿的帮助，
As well as help from his daughter,
队长格雷厄姆，已经让他的老板迪恩报名了。
team captain, Graham, has enrolled his boss, Dean.
这次情况完全不同了，所以他最好对我好一点。
The shoe's on the other foot this time, so he'd better be nice to me.
我一直对他很好，所以…
I'm always nice to him, so...
这对搭档在银石赛道工作
This duo work at Silverstone,
他们已经习惯了为数千人提供餐饮的压力
and they're used to the pressure of catering for thousands of people
在维修区上方的厨房里。
from their kitchen above the pit lane.
我们的任务是让银石为我们的食物而出名。
The mission is to put Silverstone on the map for our food.
可能会以你的名字命名一个角落。
Might name a corner after you.
是的,也许吧。
Yeah, maybe.
格雷厄姆正在放一块柠檬凝乳
Graham is placing a cube of lemon curd embellished
用覆盆子凝胶和蛋白霜做成一个独立的糕点轮。
with raspberry gel and meringue into a freestanding pastry wheel.
我想在银石赛道会有很多重大赛事。
At Silverstone, you have a lot of big events, I imagine.
是的，我们有大奖赛，经典赛，摩托大奖赛。
Yeah, we have the Grand Prix, Classics, Moto GP.
很有压力吗?是的,一流的。
Very stressful? Yeah, big-time.
当你有30名厨师需要照顾时，
When you've got a brigade of 30 chefs to look after,
这很不一样。
it's quite different.
迪恩，他有时会发脾气吗?
Dean, does he have tantrums sometimes?
呃…两者都做一点。对，他吼了一声就走了。
Er... Do a bit of both. Yeah, he gets a bit shouty then walks off.
很好，我希望我们能看到。
Great, well, I hope we get to see that.
你可能会，也可能不会。
Yeah, you might do, you might not.
骂了几句，又骂了几句。
A bit of swearing, a bit of effing and jeffing.
是的。我以前曾因语言问题被责备过。
Yes. I've been told off for my language before.
可爱。记住，这不是公众投票，所以无所谓。
Lovely. Remember, it's not a public vote, so it doesn't matter.
你可以在整个比赛过程中都是一个正确的BLEEP。
You can be a right BLEEP the whole way through this competition.
不，没关系。你不需要让任何人喜欢你。
No, it doesn't matter. You don't have to make anyone like you.
请不要鼓励他。哦!
Don't encourage him, please. Oh!
斯拉芙和玛丽亚不会有爆发的危险。
There's no risk of an outburst from Slav and Maria.
我们有点安静，但这就是我们工作的方式。
We are a bit quiet, but that's how we are working.
我们一般都很安静。
We are very quiet in general.
作为厨师有点不寻常。
A bit unusual as chefs.
斯拉夫和玛丽亚在精品巧克力店R Chocolate工作，
Slav and Maria work at boutique chocolatiers R Chocolate,
定制美食。
creating bespoke delicacies.
必应(Bing) !
Bing!
所以斯拉夫人忍不住要加入
So Slav couldn't resist incorporating
白巧克力布丁放进柠檬挞里，
white chocolate feuilletine into his lemon tart,
浇上柠檬慕斯和柠檬沙司。
topping off lemon mousseline and a lemon sablee disc.
看我的小纱布多亮啊!
Look how shiny my feuilletine is!
它是如此闪亮。
It's so shiny.
是的，是的。这是我们的白巧克力小蛋糕，
Yeah, it is. That is our white chocolate feuilletine,
非常闪亮。好。
which is very shiny. Good.
虽然大多数团队都选择了当代设计，
While most teams have opted for contemporary designs,
琳恩和罗曼不会冒险的。
Leanne and Roman are taking no chances.
我们坚持经典。
We're sticking to the classic.
这是我们的工作，希望他们会喜欢。
It's what we do at work, so hopefully they'll like it.
在只有23岁和26岁的时候，
At only 23 and 26 years old,
来自Hotel Cafe Royal的Leanne和Roman是最年轻的团队
Leanne and Roman from Hotel Cafe Royal are the youngest team
在这激烈的竞争中。虽然看起来很传统，
in this heat of the competition. Although it might look traditional,
它们赋予了柠檬酸挞的核心风味
they're giving their Tarte au Citron's core flavour
加入甜菜根和百里香的独特风味
a unique savoury twist by adding beetroot and thyme
意大利蛋白糖饼。
Italian meringues.
甜菜根，百里香和柠檬?上次我吃了甜菜根，百里香和柠檬，
Beetroot, thyme and lemon? Last time I had beetroot, thyme and lemon,
这是开胃菜，配一些油醋沙司。
that was as a starter with some vinaigrette.
我想这些味道混合在一起会让你惊叹不已。
I think the flavours together will wow you.
因为我觉得你不指望它味道好，
Because I don't think you're expecting it to taste nice,
但希望它会。
but hopefully it will.
好的，甜菜根和柠檬。
OK, beetroot and lemon.
我能说什么呢?我们走着瞧。
What can I say? We shall see.
谢谢你！再见。
Thank you. See you later.
我不太确定他们是否喜欢我们的计划!
I'm not too sure if they like our plan!
不，我不认为……
No, I don't think...
还有烘蛋挞……
With tart cases baking...
这些是我的泡芙糕点呼啦圈。
These are my choux pastry hula hoops.
希望他们会没事。
Hopefully they'll be fine. ..
. .团队需要利用每一分钟来完善他们的填充物。
..The teams need to use every minute to perfect their fillings.
埃迪和马希德希望增加他们的饱腹感
And Eddie and Mahshid are hoping to boost their filling
加上一点花的力量。
with a touch of flower power.
在上面，我们有一个独立的柠檬凝乳和芙蓉果冻
On top, we've got a freestanding lemon curd and hibiscus jelly to
要强调味道。
really emphasise the flavour.
艾迪和马希德在世界著名的伦敦萨沃伊工作。
Eddie and Mahshid work at the world famous Savoy in London.
他们想把下午茶的优雅带来
They want to bring the elegance of their afternoon tea
与艾迪精心制作的酥皮蛋糕比拼
to the competition with Eddie's delicately waved pastry base,
最后撒上柠檬乳，
topped off with a piped lemon curd,
柠檬海绵，木槿和黑加仑果冻块。
lemon sponge and hibiscus and blackcurrant infused jelly cubes.
你打算怎么做木槿果冻?
How are you going to set your hibiscus jelly?
明胶。所以你用的是鱼胶?
With gelatine. So you're using a fish gelatine?
鱼明胶。你觉得你有足够的时间来凝固你的明胶吗?
Fish gelatine. Do you think you have enough time to set your gelatine?
是的，它会凝固。我希望如此。
Yes, it will set. I hope so.
说到时间，我们让他们继续吧?
Speaking of time, shall we let them crack on?
我想我们应该。我认为这是个好主意。
I think we should. I think that's a good idea.
我们应该晚点再来。来吧，伙计们。
We should come back later. Come on, guys.
厨师们，祝你们好运。
Good luck, chefs.
除非他们很快就把牙补好，
Unless they set their fillings quickly,
各队将没有时间组装零件。
the teams will run out of time to assemble their parts.
加上冰柜，加上冰柜。快走，快走。
Plus freezer, plus freezer. Go quickly, quickly.
快，快，快。
Quickly, quickly, quickly.
但是，与其他团队不同的是，
But, unlike all the other teams,
琳恩和罗曼打算在他们的案子里伪造文件，
Leanne and Roman plan to cook their filings in their tart cases,
所以他们需要额外的时间来做第二次烘焙。
so they'll need to find extra time for a second bake.
一旦挞烤好了，我就可以加入挞粉了。
As soon as the tarts are part baked, I can add the tart mix.
都是关于烹饪的。
It's all about the cooking.
大厨们，你们还有一个半小时。
Chefs, you have an hour and a half left.
用力，请用力一点。
Push, push a little bit, please.
是的,厨师。
Yes, chef.
而不是让他们的填充物牢固，
Instead of setting their fillings firm,
艾迪不小心把它们冻住了。
Eddie has accidentally frozen them solid.
我们现在要哔哔了。
We're going to be BLEEP now.
我们需要重新启动我们的东西。
We need to restart our stuff.
我们必须，
We're going to have to,
因为我不会把这个拿给评委看的。
because I'm not going to serve that to the judges.
这是不可接受的。我得抓紧时间，不然我们就不
It's not acceptable. I need to crack on with this otherwise we're not
可以做任何东西。柠檬凝乳的配方在哪里?
going to be able to serve anything. Where's that lemon curd recipe?
小心些而已。
Be careful.
你能把门打开吗?
Can you get this door?
好的，我去拿。
Yeah, I'll get it.
它可以更好。
It could be better.
它可以更好。因为冰箱的情况，
It could be a lot better. Because of the freezer situation,
我得重做柠檬凝乳和芙蓉果冻做蛋挞。
I have to remake the lemon curd and the hibiscus jelly for the tart.
这里越来越热了，还是只有我这么觉得?
It's getting hot in here now, or is it just me?
它是热的。
It's hot.
如果用完美的柠檬挞给人留下深刻印象还不够困难的话……
If trying to impress with perfect lemon tarts wasn't tough enough...
这些团队还必须处理一批伯努瓦的经典新桥。
The teams also have to tackle a batch of Benoit's classic Pont Neuf.
一座古典的新桥，非常传统
A classical Pont Neuf, very traditional
法式小食谱，我很喜欢。
French little recipe, which I love.
第一步，做酥皮。
So, first step, the puff pastry.
面点要完美。
The pastry needs to be perfect.
在酥皮上铺一层苹果泥，
Line your pastry case, a little layer of apple compote,
将酥皮，奶油和泡芙酥皮混合在一起，捏成一团。
the combination of pastry, cream and choux pastry, pipe in a nice blob.
在上面，一个可爱的酥皮交叉，
On the top, a lovely puff pastry cross,
放入烤箱烤至金黄。
bake in the oven until nice and golden.
釉上红醋栗果酱，另外两个角涂上糖粉。
Glaze with redcurrant jam, icing sugar in the other two corners.
它们都必须完美和精确。
They all have to be perfect and precise.
这将是一个挑战。
That will be the challenge.
这看起来很简单，但伯努瓦期待完美的执行
It may seem simple, but Benoit will expect a perfect execution
这部经典的每一个元素。
of every element of this classic.
我们都是WI成员。
We're both WI members.
如果我们不擅长果酱，那就会很…
If we suck at jam, it's going to be very...
尴尬。非常尴尬。
Embarrassing. Very embarrassing.
尽管这些元素都很熟悉，但新桥
And, although those elements are familiar, the Pont Neuf
它本身可能不是。
itself may not be.
你试过多少次了?
How many times have you tried this?
呃…关于一次。
Er... About once.
一次?一次。一次!
Once? Once. Once!
你试过一次新桥?!
You've tried the Pont Neuf once?!
这是正确的。第一次成功了吗?
That's right. And did it work the first time?
是的。新手的好运气?
Yeah. Beginner's luck?
别倒霉，别倒霉!
Don't jinx it, don't jinx it!
我们不应该这么说。我知道你会再次成功的。
We shouldn't say that. I know you're going to nail it again.
是的。我要把它砸了。来吧，孔蒂。
Yes. I'm going to smash it. Come on, compote.
来吧。厨师,厨师。
Come on. Cook, cook.
煮苹果做果盘是一种微妙的平衡。
Cooking apples for a compote is a delicate balancing act.
它看起来很漂亮。
It's looking beautiful.
如果水果现在还没有充分还原，等会儿烤的时候，
If the fruit isn't reduced enough now, when baked later,
多余的水分会变成蒸汽，
excess moisture will turn to steam,
在糕点中间形成气穴。
causing air pockets in the centre of the pastries.
泥做的。做得很好。
Compote's done. Well done.
谢谢你！我喜欢表扬。
Thank you. I like some praise.
在新桥的拱顶上有一种更不寻常的填充物……
In a Pont Neuf on top of the compote is a more unusual filling...
这是泡芙酥皮和奶油的混合物。
It's a choux pastry and creme pat mixed together.
. .格雷厄姆正在努力让它变稠。
..That Graham is struggling to thicken.
这不是BLEEP烹饪。
It's not BLEEP cooking.
开始了，快，你落后了，伙计。
It's on, quick, you're behind, mate.
不，我们很好。
No, we're all right.
我们现在压力很大，这是肯定的。
We are under the pressure now, for sure.
引擎盖上的一切都很好。
It's all good in the hood.
一旦组装完毕，新桥至少需要30分钟
Once assembled, the Pont Neuf will need at least 30 minutes
正确烘焙。
to bake correctly.
但是在填馅上浪费了时间，只用了40分钟，
But having lost time on their fillings, and with just 40 minutes,
剩下的格雷厄姆和迪恩还没做好。
remaining Graham and Dean's still aren't ready for the oven.
他们怎么样?太薄?不太薄，伙计。
How are they? Too thin? It's not too thin, mate.
一切都运行得很好。
It's all working quite nicely.
琳恩和罗曼还需要烤他们的柠檬挞馅。
And Leanne and Roman still need to bake their Tarte au Citron filling.
我一点也不放松。到新桥要花20分钟。
I'm not relaxed. The Pont Neuf is going to take 20 minutes.
这要花20分钟。
This is going to take 20 minutes.
我们还有35分钟。
And we've got 35 minutes left.
所以…我会准备好做柠檬酱的釉料。
So... Will try to get the glaze ready for my lemon sauce.
如果我幸运的话。
If I'm lucky.
我知道你现在在想什么。
I know what you think about the time now.
是啊，我们现在就在悬崖边上。
Yeah, we're right on the edge now.
先把这个做好，然后看看有没有时间煮。
Got to get this done and then, see if we've got time to cook it.
各位，你们有半个小时的时间!
You've got half an hour, everyone!
半小时,厨师!
Half-an-hour, chefs!
半小时了!真的吗?
Half-an-hour left! Really?
我希望你有足够的时间完成所有的事情。
I hope you've got enough time to finish everything.
我们就快到了。
We're almost there.
基本上，组装是最耗时的部分。
Basically, it's the assembly that's the time-consuming bit.
我们现在落后了。
We're behind now.
因为我们只剩下半小时了，凝乳还没凝固。
Because we only have half an hour left and the curd has not set.
这些娃娃真漂亮。
These babs are beaut.
谢谢你！16,18,20,22。
Thank you! 16, 18, 20, 22.
是的，我们所有的元素都融合在一起了。
Yeah, all our elements are coming together now.
这道菜刚刚上桌。
It's just getting on the plate really.
马希德有足够的时间重新制作她的柠檬凝乳。
Mahshid has had just enough time to remake her lemon curd.
我们可以用柠檬凝乳，感谢上帝。是吗?是的。
We can use the lemon curd, thank God. Yeah? Yeah.
现在我们完全在哔哔声中。
Now we're completely in the BLEEP.
但现在另一支队伍与冰柜发生了冲突。
But now another team has fallen foul of the freezer.
凯丽和凯蒂做蛋挞的重要元素
A vital element of Kelly and Katie's tart,
茶味凝胶已冻成固体。
the tea flavoured gel has frozen solid.
凝胶的作用不太好。
The gel isn't going very well.
哦,废话。我们就这样算了吧?
Oh, crap. Should we just leave it?
先不管它吧。
Just leave it for now.
管一下就行了。
The piping will do.
这是必须的。我们没有别的选择。
Well it's going to have to do. We have no other choice.
他们煮得过久。
They're overcooked.
啊,哔哔声。我现在不想待在这里。
Ah, BLEEP. I don't want to be here right now.
我不是在开玩笑。
I'm not even joking.
所以，柠檬挞煮过头了。
So, the lemon tart overcooked.
大厨们，你们还有15分钟!
Chefs, you have 15 minutes left!
还剩15分钟!
15 minutes left!
你掉了一个?是的，我掉了一个。
You dropped one? Yeah, I dropped one.
所以只剩下一个了。
So we've only got one left.
我们只能再失去一个。
We can only lose one more.
它们需要冷却。除此之外，他们还需要更多。
They need to cool. Any more, they need more.
或者它们会坍塌。这还是错的吗?
Or they're going to collapse. Is it wrong, still?
不，不，不，这没有错。
No, no, no, it's not wrong.
一致性。
Uniformity.
这真的很苍白。我很抱歉。
This is really pale. I'm sorry.
快，快，快，快!
Go, go, go, go!
厨师!你还有一分钟!
Chefs! You have one minute left!
我们不可能把果酱放进去。
We're not going to be able to put the jam in.
我为他们担心。哦,男孩。
I'm scared for them. Oh, boy.
来吧，进去吧。
Come on, just go in.
哦,哔哔声!
Oh, BLEEP!
厨师!你的时间到了!
Chefs! Your time is up!
我很沮丧。
I'm so frustrated.
我们还有五分钟就到。
We're five minutes off of that.
就是这样，哔哔的五分钟。
That's all it was, five BLEEP minutes.
我们的六支新队伍现在必须面对珍爱和伯努瓦的评判
Our six new teams now have to face the judgment of Cherish and Benoit
这是第一次。
for the very first time.
萨,
The Savoy,
请把你的迷你经典作品拿过来好吗?
could you please bring your miniature classics to the table?
我们有24条新路…
We've got 24 Pont Neufs...
. .烤。
..nicely baked.
烤得很好。
Really nicely baked.
哎呦。
Whoops.
不幸的是，面点的外面已经熟了，
Unfortunately, the pastry's cooked on the outside,
里面还没煮熟。
the inside is seriously undercooked.
都是因为你的蒸汽。
All because of your steam.
这个小蛋糕的挑战在于如何管理蒸汽。
The challenge of this petit gateau is management of that steam.
它太酸了，我不喜欢。
It's too acidic to my liking.
我原则上同意珍爱的观点。
I agree with Cherish in principle.
它可能有点酸
It's maybe a little bit acidic
但是，因为它的酸度，你会有一点新鲜感
but, because of the acidity, you've got a bit of freshness
这就是我在新桥寻找的东西。
which is what I was looking for with the Pont Neuf.
柠檬馅饼。
Lemon tart.
非常有创意，这就是我们想要的。
Very innovative and creative, this is what we're looking for.
是的，是的，绝对的。
Yeah, yeah, definitely.
你应该为此感到骄傲，
You should be very proud of this,
你是如何解决问题的
of the way I see you rectified your problem.
我印象非常深刻。
I was very impressed.
谢谢你！
Thank you.
我喜欢你的芙蓉果冻。
I like your hibiscus jelly.
和柠檬搭配效果很好。
Works well with the lemon.
我觉得很相配。
I think it matches very well.
你的柠檬，黑加仑和木槿，
Your lemon and your blackcurrant and hibiscus,
很漂亮，做得很好。
beautiful, well done.
非常感谢。谢谢你！
Thank you very much. Thank you.
啊,笨蛋!
Ah, boobs!
至于新桥，它的边缘相当粗糙。
With the Pont Neuf, it's pretty rough on the edges.
我们看不太清楚十字架。
We can't see the cross very well.
这果酱看起来不像果酱。
The jam doesn't look like a jam.
哦。
Oops.
里面有很多蒸汽。毫米。
A lot of steam inside. Mm.
对不起，还没煮熟。我就是吃不下。
Sorry, it's not cooked. I just can't eat it.
柠檬蛋挞。我们试试好吗?是的。
The lemon tart. Shall we try? Oui.
你可以看到，基本上，它没有上釉。
You can see, basically, it's not glazed.
它非常非常不整洁。
It is very, very untidy.
实际上很愉快。嗯，我喜欢那种犀利的感觉。
It's actually pleasant. Mm. I like that little sharpness.
有一种可爱的感觉，你怎么说?停吗?
There is that lovely ting, tinge, how do you say that? Ting?
活力。活力。唐。
Zing. Zing. Tang.
活力汤。Zing tang，新词。
Zing tang. Zing tang, new word.
啊。
Ah.
至少你没有一个大的蒸汽袋。
At least you don't have a large pocket of steam.
但通常情况下，它的质地会让它稍微淡一些。
But normally the texture will make it slightly lighter.
它不再是新桥了。
It is not a Pont Neuf any more.
这更像是一个果馅饼。
This is more like a flan.
我只想尝尝苹果。
I'll only try the apple.
正如你所看到的，它是生的，它会让我的肚子不舒服。
As you can see, it is uncooked, it will make my tummy upset.
柠檬馅饼。就陈述而言，你做得很好。
Lemon tart. In terms of presentation, you did very well.
真的很喜欢貂皮和慕斯里的搭配，
Really like the combination of your sable with your mousseline,
最后用你放的小蛋糕来完成。
and then finish up with the feuilletine that you put.
做得很好。谢谢你！
Well done. Thank you.
只是对你的果酱有点失望。
Just a little bit disappointed with your jam.
我觉得你的果酱应该再浓一点。
I thought your jam should be a bit thicker.
但也有一些技巧。
But there is some finesse.
十字是整齐的。
Cross is neat.
在口味方面，我们想要一种浓郁的苹果味，
In terms of flavour profile, we are looking for a strong apple flavour,
淡淡的香草味
a light vanilla texture of your
混合了法式奶油和泡芙糕点。
combined mixture of creme patissiere and choux pastry.
实际上，没有一种光线能穿透
None of it is actually shining through
它失去了它的个性。
and it loses its personality.
柠檬馅饼。
Lemon tart.
你得打扮一下，姑娘们，加油!
You need to dress it up a little bit, girls, come on!
对我来说，已经完成了一半。
It's half-done, for me.
嗯，我有柠檬
Well, I got lemon
但你倒了些茶进去。嗯嗯。
but you brought some tea into it. Mm-hm.
非常非常温和。
It's very, very mild.
你也看到了，我根本没碰你的糕点
Well, as you can see, I did not touch your pastry at all
因为我觉得里面是生的
because I think it's raw inside
我不得不拒绝吃你的糕点。
and I have to refuse to eat your pastry.
繁荣。
Boom.
那就来柠檬挞吧。柠檬馅饼。
Lemon tart, then. Lemon tart.
我并不想让你泄气
I don't mean to be discouraging
但我希望你们俩能多给点。
but I was hoping for a little bit more from you two.
这是厨师们发挥创造力的地方!
This is where the chefs get creative!
但当我看着它的时候，它会说，“啊，这只是一个馅饼。”
But when I look at it, it's, "Ah, it's only a tart."
我觉得你的柠檬馅煮过头了。
I think you overcooked your lemon filling.
这里很像鸡蛋。
Over here is very eggy.
还有你尝试过的所有味道
And all the flavour profiles you tried to work with
为了增强你的味道，没有柠檬馅饼。
to enhance your lemon tarts are not there.
好了，这有点基础。
OK, it's a little bit basic.
是的。
Yep.
怎么了，大厨?
What happened, chef?
我们只是没时间了，不是吗?我想是的。
We just ran out of a bit of time, didn't we, really? I think, yeah.
看起来，
By the looks of it,
你也没果酱了，是吧?
you ran out of jam, as well, didn't you?
还没煮熟呢。
Well, it's not cooked.
如果没有煮熟，就不好吃
If it's not cooked, it's not nice to eat
所以让我们祈祷柠檬挞能自我救赎吧。
so let's hope the lemon tart redeems itself.
好的。
OK.
糕点,再一次。
Pastry, again.
你做得不对。对我来说还不够熟。
You didn't cook it right. It's just under-baked for me.
够有趣吗?
Is it interesting enough?
你应该再往前推一点。
You should have pushed it a little bit further.
只是对自己很失望，真的。
Just disappointed with myself, really.
因为我知道我更好了。
Cos I know I'm better.
我的意思是，就我个人而言，我认为，你知道，还有很多事情要做。
I mean, personally, I think, you know, there's still all to play for.
为了明天的表演挑战，
For tomorrow's showpiece challenge,
厨师们得到了宝贵的时间
the chefs have been given a golden hour
准备任何需要过夜的材料。
to prepare any elements that need setting overnight.
所以第一天没人把它弄坏
So no-one really, like, smashed it the first day
但我们都同意萨沃伊比其他地方做得更好。
but we can all agree that the Savoy did better than the rest.
我认为他们目前处于领先地位。
I think they're leading at the moment.
但差距很小，因为每个人都差不多
But by a small margin because everybody was pretty much
度过了艰难的一天。
having a rough day.
那WI的女孩呢?
And for the girls from the WI?
我想象着他们的新桥
I thought visually their Pont Neuf
是最接近它应有的样子。
was the closest to what it should look like.
R巧克力队?
Team R Chocolate?
你知道吗，他们的柠檬挞真的很酷。
You know, their lemon tart was really cool.
你看，这是潜在的。
Well, you see, it is potential.
它们在盘子里产生的是潜力。
What they produce on the plate is potential.
而下面的二人组，
And the duos, perhaps, at the bottom,
他们更挣扎的地方，就是叮当声，
where they're struggling a little bit more, would be the Clink,
格雷厄姆的银石车队。是的。
Graham's team from Silverstone. Yeah.
还有皇家咖啡馆里琳恩的团队。
And Leanne's team from Cafe Royal.
所以期待明天的表演挑战。
So looking forward to tomorrow, the showpiece challenge.
明天什么都可能发生。
Anything can happen tomorrow.
我希望厨师能发挥他们的想象力。
I would like the chef to unleash their imagination.
当你打开门走进去，感觉很神奇，
When you open the door and you walk in and it's so magical,
太棒了，太性感了。
it's so wonderful, it's so sexy.
一个性感的展示糕点。是的。
A sexy showpiece pastry. Yeah.
早上好。早....早....
Good morning. Morning. Morning.
早上好，厨师们。希望你昨晚睡得好。
Good morning, chefs. I hope you had a good night's sleep.
你将需要你所有的能量
You are going to need all your energy
来参加今天的Showpiece挑战赛。
for today's Showpiece Challenge.
一切都是为了让平凡变得不平凡。
It's all about taking the ordinary and making it extraordinary.
就像威瑟斯彭开始供应早餐的时候。
You know, like, when Wetherspoon's started serving breakfast.
现在，对于这次挑战，评委们希望你们能获得灵感
Now, for this challenge, the judges would like you to take inspiration
这是一道经典的英式甜点
from a classic English dessert.
评委们，能告诉我们你们选出了哪支队伍吗?
So, judges, can you tell us what you've chosen for the teams?
汤姆，我们选择了伊顿公学。
Well, Tom, we have chosen Eton mess.
当然，我们想要一个现代的英国经典。
Of course, we want a modern twist on that British classic.
你的甜点至少要能喂饱24个人。
Your dessert must feed at least 24 people.
我希望你在口味和口感上有创意。
I would like you to be creative with your flavour and texture.
你的设计必须以美吸引我们的眼球。
Your design must capture our eye with beauty.
请注意，我们会一直盯着你。
Be warned, we will be watching you at all times.
谢谢你，珍爱，你说得既充实又恐怖
Thank you, Cherish, that was both informative and terrifying
同时。
at the same time.
你昨晚准备了一个小时，现在只剩下四个小时了
You had one hour last night to prep and you have four hours remaining
完成挑战。
to complete the challenge.
你的时间开始了……
And your time starts...
. .。
..now.
正确的。我们走吧。
Right. Let's go.
我们开始吧。
Let's do it.
当你这样做的时候，把蛋白霜涂上，直接放进烤箱。
As you're doing that, get your meringue on, get that straight in the oven.
伊顿公学最早是在世界著名的伊顿公学供应的
Eton mess was first served at the world-famous Eton College
在19世纪，
in the 1800s,
直到今天，在他们与哈罗大学的年度板球比赛中，他们仍然用这种饮料。
and it's still served today at their annual cricket match against Harrow.
伊顿公学的难题是，这是最基本的食谱，
The challenge with the Eton mess, it's the most basic recipe,
你能做的最基本的甜点。
the most basic dessert you can make.
当然，今天的比赛不是关于基本的。
Of course, this competition today is not about being basic.
事实恰恰相反。我们想要戏剧，我们想要技巧，我们想要惊喜。
It's the opposite. We want drama, we want skills, we want to be amazed.
“哇!”
"Wow!"
它是奶油、浆果和蛋白霜的完美结合，
It is beautifully combined cream, berry, and meringue,
但厨师是如何在这道甜点上烙上印记的呢
but how does the chef put a stamp onto this dessert
把它变成他们自己的?
and make it their own?
它需要是丰富多彩的。
It needs to be colourful.
它需要是动态的。
It needs to be dynamic.
它需要华丽。
It needs to be magnificent.
这些团队现在要建造他们宏伟的展示建筑，
The teams now have to create their magnificent showpiece structures,
伴随着伊顿混乱的甜点…
accompanied by Eton mess-inspired desserts...
静静地自信，但你永远不知道，任何事情都可能发生，真的。
Quietly confident, but you never know, anything can happen, really.
. .这是埃迪和马希德希望通过展示他们的
..which Eddie and Mahshid are hoping to achieve by showcasing their
队长做糖活的天赋。
team captain's flair for sugar work.
你今天要给我们展示什么?
What are you going to present to us today?
每种甜点都有自己的糖球
Each dessert is going to have its own sugar ball
我们要把球绕在展览品周围。
and we're going to build the balls around the Showpiece itself.
所以是把馅料塞进球里?
So it's a filling going inside the ball?
是的。哇，真令人兴奋。哇。
Yes. Oh, wow, how exciting. Wow.
埃迪的吹糖球可以包裹草莓蛋白霜，
Eddie's blown sugar spheres will encase strawberry meringue,
草莓酱和香蒂伊奶油，
strawberry coulis and Chantilly cream,
坐在一个同样完全由糖制成的高耸结构下。
sat beneath a towering structure also made entirely of sugar.
艾德，这是你的工作，对吧，做糖活?
Ed, this is your thing, isn't it, doing sugar work?
是的，我喜欢。你为什么这么喜欢吃糖?
Yeah, I love it. What makes you love sugar so much?
这太专业了。
It's so technical.
你知道，它很美。
You know, it's beautiful.
但制糖业的摊牌即将到来。
But a sugar work showdown is looming.
不顾一切地想要在昨天之后有所改善
Desperate to improve after yesterday,
琳恩和罗曼也想给大家留下好印象
Leanne and Romain are also aiming to impress
用这种出了名的反复无常的技巧。
with this notoriously fickle technique.
你对糖有信心吗?你以前做过很多吗?
So are you confident with sugar? You've done a lot before?
我做的不多。这绝对是一项新技能。
I haven't done much. It's a new skill, definitely.
哇，你真勇敢，敢做糖。
Wow, it's very brave of you to do sugar.
你能给我们介绍一下吗
Would you be able to take us through
你打算怎么建造你的Showpiece?
how you're going to build your Showpiece?
回到伊顿公学混乱的故事。
To go back to the story of the Eton mess.
你知道他们有赛艇队吗?是的。
You know they have a rowing team? Yes.
他们戴着大帽子，上面有很多花。
And they are wearing, like, big hats, lots of flowers on it.
啊。这就是为什么我们要做三个环
Ah. So that's why we're doing three rings
但每一个都有不同的技巧。
but a different technique on each one.
他们的甜品中心将配上两个五层的主菜
Their sugar work centrepiece will accompany two five-layer entremets
内含草莓慕斯、蛋奶冻、果冻和草莓酱。
containing strawberry mousse, set custard, jelly and strawberry glaze.
我不想说进展是否顺利
I don't want to say whether it's going well or not
因为我可能会倒霉的!
cos I might just jinx myself!
我今天不想说得太快，但是
Don't want to speak too fast today but
我们相信此刻会准时到达。
we believe to be on time at the moment.
所有其他球队都不吃糖
All the other teams have shunned sugar
用巧克力来建造。
and are constructing with chocolate.
昨天的微缩模型没能完成，
And after failing to finish yesterday's miniatures,
在今天的表演中，穆斯塔法和凯文全力以赴。
for today's showpiece, Mustapha and Kevin are going all-out.
伊顿的混乱反映在板球上…
Eton mess is reflected to cricket...
. .所以我在做板球拍
..so I'm making cricket bats
加上一些巧克力球，
with some chocolate balls,
就像板球一样。
like a ball for cricket.
在他的球棒和球旁边放着24套草莓慕斯
Alongside his bat and ball will sit 24 set strawberry mousses
含有奶油和油酥饼
containing cremeaux and confit inserts
还有海绵底，上面撒上蛋白霜。
and a sponge base topped off with meringue.
昨天过后，你有多自信?
After yesterday, how confident are you?
我们有信心。好。
We're confident. Good.
这就是我想听的。
This is what I want to hear.
我们很有信心，但我们这里有非常好的厨师
We're confident but we've got really good chefs in here
所以我们要重新集中注意力
so we'll just try to focus again
避免我们昨天犯的错误。
and to avoid the mistakes we did yesterday.
我们会按时完成的。
We'll get right and done on time.
凯文，我希望你今天能和穆斯塔法一起跑步?
So, I hope that Kevin, you're going to run with Mustapha today?
是的。我就在他后面。齿轮6。
Yep. I'm right behind him. Gear six.
超速。公式1。
Speeding. Formula 1.
就是这样。
That's it.
也是为了登上领奖台而全力以赴
Also going full throttle for a podium finish
第一天拖延下来的是格雷厄姆和迪恩。
after stalling on day one are Graham and Dean.
跟我们说说伊顿公学的事吧。
Talk to us about the Eton mess.
我们正在设计24个独立的球体
We are designing 24 individual spheres
我们想要一个背景来配合它
and we wanted a backdrop to go with it
所以我们在银石赛道设计了领奖台。
so we've designed the podium from Silverstone.
伊顿混乱……是的。
Eton mess... Yes.
. .在跑道上。
..on the racetrack.
覆盆子色的白巧克力球，
Their raspberry-glazed white chocolate spheres,
当被打碎时，
when smashed open,
五彩缤纷的蛋白酥
should reveal multicoloured meringues,
覆盆子凝胶和马斯卡彭凝结奶油慕斯。
raspberry gel and mascarpone clotted cream mousse.
马斯卡彭奶油和凝乳奶油。
Mascarpone cream and clotted cream.
你觉得我和伯努瓦会喜欢吃吗?
Do you think so that me and Benoit will enjoy eating it?
我认为……我希望你会喜欢。
I think... I'm hoping you're going to enjoy it.
因为它口感丰富，味道丰富，有很多覆盆子，
Cos it's rich, delicious, loads of flavours, loads of raspberries,
大量的水果。它应该是什么，真的。
loads of fruit. What it should be, really.
昨天，凯利和凯蒂的演讲赢得了掌声
Yesterday, Kelly and Katie won plaudits for their presentation
但今天，这种前景似乎不太可能了。
but today, that prospect seems a little less likely.
所以我们决定还是让它有点乱，
So we've decided to still keep it as a little bit of a mess,
所以它不叫伊顿整洁，所以我们去了一点……
so it's not called an Eton tidy, so we've gone for a bit of a...
. .这就像一个毒菌茶话会。
..well, it's like a toadstool tea party.
在一个两英尺高的巧克力毒菌底部，
At the base of a two-foot chocolate toadstool,
会有装着蛋白霜的巧克力茶杯，
there'll be chocolate teacups containing meringue,
苹果香草果酱和耶路撒冷洋蓟意式奶塔。
apple and vanilla jam and Jerusalem artichoke panna cotta.
你怎么把耶路撒冷洋蓟放进去了?
How come you've put Jerusalem artichoke in that?
所以，臭名昭著的是，在WI上，它被称为果酱和耶路撒冷，
So, infamously, with the WI, it's all renowned as jam and Jerusalem,
所以我们做了草莓酱，草莓和苹果酱。啊哈。
so we've made strawberry jam, strawberry and apple jam. Uh-huh.
我们从耶路撒冷洋蓟中得到了耶路撒冷。
And we've got the Jerusalem from the Jerusalem artichoke.
还有一首歌，不是吗?这是耶路撒冷之歌。
And there's a song, as well, isn't there? It's Jerusalem the song.
是的。这首歌是怎么唱的?
Yeah. How does the song go?
他们哼唱耶路撒冷
THEY HUM JERUSALEM
他们崩溃了
THEY CRACK UP
我想我得停下来了!
I think I've go to stop!
是的，请说。我头疼!
Yeah, please do. I'm getting a headache!
你头疼吗?从你的歌声中!
You're getting a headache? From your singing!
开玩笑!
Kidding!
巧克力专家斯拉芙和玛利亚带着他们的伊顿公学食堂
Chocolate experts Slav and Maria are taking their Eton mess
达到新的高度。
to explosive new heights.
我出生在群山之中，
I was born around mountains, OK,
这给了我一些启发。
so that gives me a bit of inspiration.
我们要用熔岩造一座火山。
We're going to make a volcano with lava.
火山!我们所有的混乱都会消失，就像石头落下一样。啊!
Volcano! And all our mess will be down, like rocks falling down. Ah!
斯拉夫的粉白色蛋白酥熔岩
Slav's pink and white meringue lava rocks
里面有桃子和覆盆子香蒂伊奶油
filled with peach and raspberry Chantilly cream
会坐在他的巧克力火山底部。
will sit around the base of his chocolate volcanoes.
所以这是山脉
So this is going to be the mountains
站在伊顿的食堂后面。
standing behind the Eton mess.
我已经有五座山了。这很好。
So I have five mountains already. That is good.
斯拉夫人可能比计划提前了
Slav might be ahead of schedule
但其他团队仍有巧克力需要回火和发霉，
but the other teams still have chocolate to temper and mould,
他们知道他们必须留出足够的时间让它凝固。
knowing they must leave enough time for it to set.
所以我在做巧克力茶杯
So I am making the chocolate teacups
我们要把布丁放进去。
which is what we're going to put our pudding into.
现在我要把巧克力铺在周围
And now I'm just spreading the chocolate around
所以我也要好好地敲一下。
so I'm about to give it a good banging, as well.
巧克力凝固后，
As their chocolate sets,
团队需要利用每一分钟
the teams need to use every minute
来提供评委们要求的美味馅料。
to deliver the delicious fillings the judges have demanded.
但是，尽管昨天已经没有时间了，
But, despite running out of time yesterday,
穆斯塔法正冒着另一个多层次创作的风险。
Mustapha is risking another multi-layered creation.
这些是插入物。
These are the inserts.
马斯卡彭奶油和草莓酱。
Mascarpone cream and strawberry confit.
我要把海绵放进去，最后再放一些新鲜的蛋白霜。
I'm going to put sponge in there and finish with some fresh meringue.
这是覆盆子凝胶。
This is going to be a raspberry gel.
把它放回冰箱里一会儿。
Put it back in the freezer for a bit.
我觉得很好。很显然，我只是问了我的助理，
I think it's fine. I've just, obviously, asked my assistant, er,
他怎么想的，因为我在想也许再来一张明胶，但是
what he thought, cos I'm thinking maybe another sheet of gelatine but
我想那可能很好。不要让它太粘稠。
I think that might be fine. You don't want it too gelatinous.
琳恩的四道主菜里都有明胶，
With gelatine in every element of Leanne's four entremets,
确保她用的量不会破坏甜点的口感
ensuring the amount she uses doesn't ruin the dessert's texture
是它的四倍难。
is four times as hard.
我已经做出了所有的成分。
So I've made all the components.
在每一层凝固的时候就把它叠起来。
Just building it up when each layer sets.
大厨们，你们已经完成一半了。
Chefs, you are halfway through.
研究巧克力的团队
The teams working with chocolate
现在要面对的是脱模的微妙任务。
now face the delicate task of demoulding.
我试着练习这些球体，每次我都可以。
I like kind of tried to practise these spheres, every time I could.
他们真的很难摆脱。
They are really hard to get out.
我们会尽力的。
We'll try our best.
凯利的杯子和碟子也不容易。
And Kelly's cups and saucers aren't proving any easier.
一个破损!
A breakage!
敲打桌子
BANGING ON TABLE
发出哔哔声
BLEEP
好吧。
All right.
该死的。
Damn.
发出哔哔声
BLEEP
我做噩梦了。
I'm having a nightmare.
我们到底该怎么处理这个该死的…
What the hell are we going to do about this bloody...
发出哔哔声
BLEEP
我们的茶杯是……主要是打破
Our teacups they are... predominantly breaking
所以我们可能得把它换成碎瓷器。
so we might have to change it to broken china.
你想让我打破最后一个吗?
Do you want me to break this last one?
是的。真的吗?
Yeah. Really?
处理巧克力可能有风险……
Working with chocolate might be risky...
解脱。这很好，最好能付诸实践。
Relief. That's good, it's better that it comes in practice.
但制糖业的竞争对手
But rivals in sugar work,
艾迪和罗曼将要表演最难的技巧之一
Eddie and Roman are about to take on one of the hardest techniques
在法式蛋糕店。
in patisserie.
现在，我在吃糖。
Right now, I'm doing all my sugars.
我们要开始把它拉出来，让它有合适的颜色。
We're going to start to pull it to give it the right colour.
这是非常技术性的。
It's very technical.
这不容易做到。
Not easy to do.
糖在170度时融化并变得柔软。
Sugar melts and becomes pliable at 170 degrees.
它粘不住。太冷了。
It won't stick. It's too cold.
然后必须非常迅速地操纵它，
It must then be manipulated very quickly,
使用热块和喷灯来保持高温。
using heat lumps and blowtorches to maintain the high temperature.
快拿喷灯来。快，快，快，快!
Bring the blowtorch quick. Quick, quick, quick, quick!
如果让它冷却几度，
If it's allowed to cool even a few degrees,
糖在几秒钟内就会变脆。
the sugar can become brittle in a matter of seconds.
这行不通。不工作。这行不通。
It's not working. Not working. It's not working.
因为锁住了。给我，给我，给我。
Because it's locked. Give me, give me, give me.
就这样吧，装饰一下。
We'll just keep it like that, for decoration.
别担心，别担心，这是哔哔声。
Don't worry, don't worry, it's BLEEP.
这行不通。
It's not working.
厨师!你还有半个小时!
Chefs! You have half-an-hour left!
这些团队现在面临着组装甜点的艰巨任务。
The teams now face the painstaking task of assembling their desserts.
这是一个可怕的想法。
This is a horrible idea.
是的,哔哔声。这太愚蠢了。
Yeah, BLEEP. This is stupid.
不要破碎，不要破碎，不要破碎……
Don't break, don't break, don't break...
哦，你这个笨蛋。
Oh, you BLEEP.
太热了。
Far too hot.
现在开始进行集会了。
Starting to get the assembly going now.
只要把领奖台就位就行了。
Just need to get the podiums in place.
从这里开始，一切都很合适。
This is where it all starts to fit nicely.
哔哔声!
BLEEP!
来吧。我们走吧，好吗?是的，我们走吧。
Come on. Let's go, yeah? Yeah, let's go.
你要走哪条路?这不是正确的方式。
Which way you going? It isn't the right way.
伙计们，你们还剩15分钟。
Guys, you actually have 15 minutes left.
这是很严肃的。只是说……
That's, like, serious. Just saying...
好的。你可以在那里辞职。
OK. You can quit there.
看起来像个蘑菇。
Looks like a mushroom.
快乐吗?还没有，我想去那里看看。
Happy? Not yet, I want to check in there.
我把这个放在桌子上。
I put this one and I put it on the table.
就是这样。现在把它放在桌子上。现在把它放在桌子上。
That's it. Put it on the table now. Put it on the table now.
安全吗?是的。
Safe? Yes.
去吧，两个都去。我们会。
Go, both now. We're going.
你先来。可爱。
You go first. Lovely.
是吗?对，你先来。
Yes? Yeah, you go first.
两个，两个都看。
Both, both look.
快，快，快，快，快!
Go, go, go, go, go!
请轻轻地碰一下，推一下。
Touch and push a little bit, please.
是的。
Yes.
它必须面向那个方向。
It's got to face that way.
哔哔声!
BLEEP!
我们没有压力。
We are not stressed.
我们就快到了。我们完成了。
We are almost there. We are finished.
我们只需要完成最后的润色。
We just need to finish the last touches.
虽然我们无能为力，但还是有办法的。
There's not much we can do, but, there's something.
我们将礼物。
We'll present.
你满意吗?
Are you happy with that?
我对它很满意。我们都做过厨师该做的事了。
I'm chuffed with it. Hey, we've done what being a chef is.
用脚思考。
Thinking on your feet.
你既是厨师又是老师，不要灰心丧气。
You're a chef and you're a teacher, don't be defeatist.
事情发生。
Things happen.
哦，哔哔!
CLATTERING Oh, BLEEP!
对不起,迪安。就是这样，伙计。
Sorry, Dean. That's it, mate.
我跟丢了，伙计。
I've lost them, mate.
不，我刚掉了十个。
No, I've just dropped ten.
厨师!还剩一分钟!还剩一分钟!
Chefs! One minute left! One minute left!
我怎么了?
What happened to me?
快点，戴上，戴上!
Come on, stick them on, stick them on!
感觉很好，我们不用着急。
Such a good feeling that we didn't have to rush.
不，请不要让我失望。
No, don't let me down, please.
干得好，迪恩。
Well done, Dean.
厨师!你的时间到了!
Chefs! Your time is up!
天啊，我感觉太糟了!
Oh, my God, I feel so bad!
站在柜台后面。
Stand behind your counters.
他吻了他
HE KISSES HIM
六件精心制作的伊顿公学凌乱展示作品
Six elaborate Eton mess show pieces
只用了五个小时。
made in just five hours.
我知道。
I know.
从整体来看，我真的很喜欢这个概念。
Looking at as whole, I really like the concept.
真正让我感兴趣的是，你打碎了茶杯。
What really intrigued me, you break the teacup.
我要整杯喝吗?
Would I like it as a whole teacup?
我不这么想。但当你把它拆开时，我说，“哦，我的天哪，
I don't think so. But when you break it up, I said, "Oh, my goodness,
“这有多神奇?!”
"how amazing is this?!"
唷。
Whew.
还挺管用的，对吧?
It kind of worked, huh?
你觉得呢?
What do you think?
我觉得你适应了，这很好。
Well, I think you adapted, so that is great.
好吗?我们开始吧。
OK? So, here we go.
我喜欢这样。Oh-ho-ho !
I like that. Oh-ho-ho!
我觉得味道很好。
I think flavour-wise, it has worked.
耶路撒冷洋蓟，
The Jerusalem artichoke,
我不太确定。对我来说有点粗糙。
I'm not too sure. It's a little bit grainy for me.
看了这个展示品，我觉得你做得很好。
Looking at the showpiece, I think you did a very good job.
然而，它是非常安全的。
However, it's very safe.
你为这次比赛做得够多了吗?
Have you done enough for this competition?
就技能组合而言，没有优雅可言，
In terms of skill set, there is no elegance,
没有技巧可言。
there is no finesse.
无聊，无聊，无聊。
Boring, boring, boring.
只是奶油和蛋白霜。
It's just cream and meringue.
我真的很喜欢制作一个透明碗的过程，
I really enjoyed the part of creating a clear bowl,
吹得很完美，很难。
perfectly blown, very difficult.
鉴于你的演讲的优雅，
On the general elegance of your presentation,
它有点粗。
it's a little bit chunky.
我很想看到一点拉糖的成分。
I would love to see a little bit of the pulled sugar element.
好的。我们需要尝尝甜点。
OK. We need to taste the dessert.
概念是惊人的!
Concept is amazing!
但当我品尝这个的时候，我很失望。
But when I taste this, I'm disappointed.
只有三个元素。
There's only three element.
你有你的蛋白霜，你有你的香蒂伊，
You have your meringue, you have your chantilly,
这是coulis。
and you have your coulis.
只做三个元素不费力。
It take no effort just to do three element.
我可以看到你用了三种不同的制糖方法。
I can see that you've used three different sugar technique.
有一条漂亮的紫白相间的缎带。
There is the beautiful purple and white ribbon.
我认为你在向我们展示你的潜力。
I think you are showing to us that you've got potential.
你创造了一个由许多技能组成的设计。
You've created a design made of lots of skills.
它是优雅的。是啊，我觉得你今天取得了更大的成就，
It's elegant. Yeah, I think you achieved so much more today,
和昨天相比。
compared to yesterday.
你蛋糕里的明胶太多了。我一点也吃不下。
It's just too much gelatin in your cake. I can't eat it at all.
我想我们必须接受你做了一件
I think we're going to have to accept the fact that you've done a
你的演讲下了很大功夫
great effort on your presentation
带来了很多技能，
and brought a lot of skills to the table,
但甜点，也许只做了一半。
but the dessert, perhaps, half done.
我认为投入在设计上的工作量
I think the amount of work put into the design
比赛期间的展示是相当基本的。
of the showpiece during the competition is pretty basic.
不是说，也许不存在。
Not to say, perhaps, non-existent.
我认为是缺乏刺激。
I think it's lack of excitement.
非常基本的。非常基本的。
Pretty basic. Pretty basic.
好的。
OK.
努力开发
HARD TAPPING
有人在这里吗?他们咯咯地笑
Somebody here? THEY GIGGLE
我很喜欢蛋白霜的味道。
Really like the nice touch of meringue.
但是，我觉得我的味蕾太油腻了。
However, I think it's very fatty on my palate.
就我个人而言，我觉得这一切太甜蜜了。
Personally, I find it all far too sweet.
板球棒，我本可以看到更多的
The cricket bat, I could have seen perhaps a little bit more
用的是白糖，
white sugar had been used,
这会让它更突出一些。
which would have made it stand out a little bit more.
颜色太单一了。
It's all a bit too much one colour.
总的来说，我觉得这里有点不整洁。
As a whole, I think it's a little bit untidy.
你没有给蛋糕完全上釉。
Mm. You did not glaze the cake completely.
是的。
Yeah.
海绵在哪里?你有一个元素海绵，是吗?
Where is the sponge? You have an element sponge, haven't you?
我们没有把它放进去。
We didn't put it in there.
真可惜。蛋白霜怎么了?
What a shame. So, what happened to the meringue?
呃…我们只是…我们把它留在烤箱里了。
Er...we just...we left it in the oven.
没有蛋白霜，没有口感，
It's missing the meringue, it's missing texture,
不过，味道还不错。
though, the flavour, actually, quite nice.
厨师们，谢谢你们。太好了。谢谢你！
Chefs, thank you. Excellent. Thank you.
他叹了口气
HE SIGHS
我来承担责任。不，当然不是。
I'll take the blame. No, of course not.
哦,当然。
Oh, definitely.
Benoit和珍惜现在将对两支球队在这两项挑战中的表现进行排名。
Benoit and Cherish will now rank the teams' performances across both challenges.
最后一名的队伍将不得不退出比赛。
The team in last place will have to leave the competition.
我们有个计划。
Well, we had a plan.
它并没有像我们预期的那样起作用。
It didn't work exactly what we expect.
味道很好，但他们忘记了菜里的两个元素。
The flavour was good, but they forgotten two element in their dish.
格雷厄姆和迪恩，他们犯了不少错误。
Graham and Dean, they've made quite a few mistakes.
我觉得我失去了理智，真的。我刚丢了……
I think I just lost the edge, really. I just lost...
我不知道。没事的，伙计。
I don't know. Eh, it's all right, buddy.
是的。你知道，只是其中一个…无论如何，我们是一个团队，一如既往。
Yeah. You know, just one of those... Anything, ever, we're a team, as always.
Benoit和珍惜已经做出了决定。
Benoit and Cherish have made their decision.
第一名的队伍向军团展示了制作糕点的技巧
The team in first place showed the corps patisserie skills
以及适应和交付的能力。
and the ability to adapt and to deliver.
祝贺你,
Congratulations,
萨沃伊酒店的艾迪和马希德。
Eddie and Mahshid from The Savoy.
他们喘息
THEY GASP
是的!谢谢你！谢谢你！
Yes! Thank you. Thank you.
评委将第二名授予了凯利和凯蒂，
The judges awarded second place to Kelly and Katie,
第三位是斯拉夫和玛丽亚
third to Slav and Maria,
和他们一起进入下一轮，
and joining them in the next round,
琳恩和罗曼，第四名。
Leanne and Romain, in fourth place.
那就只剩下银石镇的格雷厄姆和迪恩，
Which leaves Graham and Dean from Silverstone,
还有来自The Clink的Mustapha和Kevin。
and Mustapha and Kevin from The Clink.
经过深思熟虑，伯努瓦和珍爱做出了决定
After much deliberation, Benoit and Cherish have decided
今晚回家的队伍是…
that the team going home tonight are...
. .穆斯塔法和凯文。
..Mustapha and Kevin.
祝贺你们其他人。
Congratulations to the rest of you.
我们下周见。
We'll see you next week.
低声说谈话
MURMURED CONVERSATION
做得很好。
Well done.
做得很好。很遗憾你要走了。
Well done. Sorry to see you go.
哦,好吧。
Oh, well.
我很想出去。我当然是。但是，公平地说，
I'm gutted to be going out. Course I am. But, I mean, to be fair,
我认为他们都应该留在那里。
I think they all deserved to stay there.
我们现在还没准备好。我们尽量多练习
We're not ready for it at the moment. We try to practise as much
只要我们能在一起，我们明年再来。
as we can together, and we come back next year.
对不起。不用担心。
Sorry. No worries.
迪恩，干得好。
Dean, well done.
我觉得我们非常非常幸运!
Uh, I think we're very extremely, extremely lucky!
难以置信。我真的很惊讶。是的。
Disbelief. I'm amazed, really. Yeah.
谢谢你，大厨。祝贺你。谢谢你！给我一个拥抱。
Thank you, Chef. Congratulations. Thank you. Give me a hug.
一个恰当的拥抱。
A proper hug.
我们在这次挑战中得了第一名。我们想待在那里，
We came first on this challenge. We want to stay up there,
但我们不知道其他队会拿出什么
but we don't know what the other teams are going to pull out the bag
下个星期，所以还是要等着看。
next week, so it's all to play for, still.
恭喜你!做得好!
Congratulations! Well done!
压力是……是关闭的。我们终于可以放松了。
The pressure is...is off. You know, we can finally relax.
它没有关闭!不是关了，只是今晚，关了!
It's not off! It's not off, but just for tonight, it's off!
下一集，剩下的五支队伍……
Next time, the five remaining teams...
怎么样了?!我要倒霉了。
How's it going?! I'm having a disaster.
. .采取多种多层微缩…
..take on a multitude of multi-layered miniatures...
它要散架了，伙计。哔哔声。
It's coming apart, mate. BLEEP.
. .还有美味的泡芙包。
..and a divine Choux bun showpiece.
她完成了第一本巧克力版圣经。
She finishes the first, like, chocolate Bible, ever.
但谁会失宠呢?
But who will fall from grace?
我想，呃，车祸。
I think, er, car crash.
字幕由红蜂传媒制作
Subtitles by Red Bee Media
欢迎来到第五周的专业烘焙大赛。
Welcome to Week Five of Bake Off: The Professionals.
如果你对这个节目有多残酷有任何怀疑，
If you're in any doubt about how brutal this show is,
这就是劣质糕点店的下场。
this is what happens to substandard patisserie.
两种:拉!
BOTH: Pull!
枪火
GUN FIRES
汤姆，你不觉得这有点过分了吗?
Do you think maybe that was a bit harsh, Tom?
你觉得你有点软弱吗，利亚姆?
Do you think you're a bit soft, Liam?
上次，我们遇到了六个全新的队伍…
Last time, we met six brand-new teams...
快，快，快，快，快!
Go, go, go, go, go!
来自萨沃伊的埃迪和马什德的创造力令人眼花缭乱。
Eddie and Mashid from the Savoy dazzled with their creativity...
这就是我们要找的。
This is what we are looking for.
美丽。干得好……得了第一名。
Beautiful. Well done. ..and took first place.
是的!
Yes!
银石的男孩，格雷厄姆和迪恩，
The boys from Silverstone, Graham and Dean,
挣扎着进入状态……
struggled to get into gear...
还不如直接扔进垃圾桶。
Might as well just throw it in the bin.
. .但是来自The Clink的Mustafa和Kevin缺少点睛之笔。
..but Mustafa and Kevin from The Clink lacked the finishing touch.
蛋白霜怎么了?我们把它留在烤箱里了。
So, what happened to the meringue? We left it in the oven.
我很想出去，但公平地说，
I'm gutted to be going out, but to be fair,
我认为他们都应该留在那里。
I think they all deserve to stay there.
本周……它们不好，它们被压扁了!
This week... They are not fine, they're squashed!
. .他们必须掌握多层微缩模型……
..they'll have to master multi-layered miniatures...
没有太大的风险……他们无处可藏。
Not too much risk. ..that leave nowhere to hide.
重新发明一种精神泡芙
And reinvent a spiritual choux...
你觉得这是第一本巧克力圣经吗?
Do you think this is the first, like, chocolate Bible ever?
. .适合糕点之神。
..fit for the pastry gods.
然后我们有一个排气从顶部出来。
And then we have an exhaust that comes out the top.
但谁的祈祷会得到回应…
But whose prayers will be answered...
. .谁会失宠?
..and who will fall from grace?
#每一件小事
# Every little thing
我们会没事的。＃
# Are going to be all right. #
在这场激烈的比赛中还剩下五支队伍。
There are five remaining teams in this heat of the competition.
明天之后，就只剩四个了。
After tomorrow, there will be just four.
厨师们，今天的重点是分层切片。
Chefs, today is all about layered slices.
不就是每天吗?
Well, isn't every day?
评委要求有两种类型，每种24种。
The judges are asking for two types, 24 of each.
那么，伯努瓦，你选择了什么来做第一层?
So, Benoit, what have you chosen for the first layered slice?
我选了一部叫歌剧的法国经典。
I have chosen a French classic called an opera.
我想看到一层又一层的海绵蛋糕，巧克力酱，咖啡奶油，
I want to see layers of joconde sponge, ganache, coffee buttercream,
每一片都必须刻上“歌剧”两个字。
and each slice must have the word "opera" inscribed on it.
我选了有异国水果味的卷饼。
I have chosen roulade flavoured with exotic fruit.
在每个卷片中，我们希望看到至少两种馅料。
In each roulade slice, we would like to see a minimum of two fillings.
每一个都必须是相同的。
And each one must be identical.
我去查一下。
I will be checking.
你有三个半小时。
You have three and a half hours.
你的时间从现在开始。
Your time starts now.
我们正在测试分层切片
We are testing with the layered slice
因为无处可藏。
because there is nowhere to hide.
一切都是可见的，每一个错误都是显而易见的。
Everything will be visible and every mistake will be obvious.
我们已经请厨师用异国水果做了这个卷。
We have asked the chefs to make the roulade with exotic fruit.
我们不期待任何无聊的事情。
We do not expect anything that is boring.
首先，你需要做海绵。
First, you need to make your sponge.
最关键的是要把海绵烤到完美。
The most crucial thing is to bake the sponge to perfection.
然后做一个果冻，
Then make a jelly,
把这个薄薄的放在海绵上。
and put this thinly on the sponge.
在果冻后面裹上漂亮的慕斯，小心地卷起来，
Follow the jelly with a beautiful mousseline, carefully roll it up,
给它们喷上一层淡淡的釉。
spray them with a light glaze.
我想看到的是厨师突破极限
What I want to see is for the chef to push the boundary
向我们展示一些神奇的东西。
to show us something magical.
早上好，WI团队。
Morning, the WI team.
请告诉我们你的行程。
Tell us your roulade, please.
我要做日本抹茶卷。
So, I'm making a Japanese matcha roulade.
啊，抹茶卷!
Ah, matcha roulade!
抹茶到底是什么味道?就像绿茶一样。
What does matcha actually taste like? It's like green tea.
我最喜欢的。
My favourite.
哦,可爱的!
Oh, lovely!
凯利对烘焙的热情始于离家较近的地方
Kelly's passion for baking started a bit closer to home
在她妈妈的厨房里。
in her mum's kitchen.
有很多我站在椅子上的照片
There's loads of photos of me stood on a chair
双手放在碗里。
with hands in the bowl.
他们笑了
THEY LAUGH
她的抹茶味海绵蛋糕会在荔枝果冻上滚动
Her matcha-flavoured sponge will roll around lychee jelly
还有另一种远东风味的馅料。
and another Far Eastern-inspired filling.
我们要做蛋奶冻苹果奶油馅饼。
We're doing a custard apple creme pat.
我也是跟着它长大的。
Which I grew up with as well.
就在我家门外，我们有蛋奶冻苹果。
Right outside my house, we have custard apple.
奶油苹果吗?这很有趣。
Custard apple? It's quite intriguing.
它有乳白色的味道。
It's very milky in flavour.
很有水果味。非常喜欢。
It's very fruity. Absolutely love it.
嗯。尝起来像蛋奶冻。
Mmm. Tastes like custard.
他们笑了
THEY LAUGH
嗯。
Mmm.
凯利和凯蒂往东走的时候
While Kelly and Katie head east,
R巧克力公司的玛利亚和斯拉夫正前往西印度群岛。
R Chocolates' Maria and Slav are heading for the West Indies.
我在做芒果百香果慕斯。
I'm making my mango and passion fruit mousse.
百香果是我最喜欢的水果。
Passion fruit is my favourite fruit, I would say.
它让我振作起来，给我激情。
It lifts me up, it gives me passion.
没有激情和爱，我在生活中寸步难行。
I don't go anywhere in life without passion and love.
下午好。欢迎来到我在伦敦的家。
Good afternoon. Welcome to my home in London.
斯拉夫人12年前从马其顿来到伦敦，
Slav travelled from Macedonia to London 12 years ago,
决心尽他所能学习糕点制作。
determined to learn all he could about patisserie.
他现在有这方面的两个学位。
He now has two degrees on the subject.
这么说，你非常有资格?
So, you're extremely well qualified?
是的,确实。我想说。我有很多帽子。
Yes, indeed. I would say. I have so many hats.
现在他要去加勒比海吃百香果卷
Now he's travelling to the Caribbean for a roulade with passion fruit
还有芒果慕斯，酸橙果冻和椰子松糕。
and mango mousse, lime jelly and a coconut joconde sponge.
这一切都是热带风情——躺在沙滩上，放松，吃，喝。
All this is tropical - lying down on the beach, relax, eat, drink.
鲍勃·马利。
Bob Marley.
格拉汉姆和迪安受到不止一位牙买加英雄的启发——他就是
Graham and Dean have been inspired by more than one Jamaican hero -
1988年冬季奥运会雪橇队。
the island's 1988 Winter Olympic bobsleigh team.
我以Cool runs为蓝本。
I've based my roulade on Cool Runnings.
这是我最喜欢的电影之一。他笑着说
It's one of my favourite films. HE LAUGHS
牙买加人觉得，这对评委来说可能太鲜艳了，
Jamaican feel, it might be too colourful for the judges,
但我们会看到的。
but we'll see.
体育比赛是银石赛道队友们一切的核心
Sporting competition are at the heart of everything Silverstone team-mates
格雷厄姆和迪恩有，包括他们的家庭聚会。
Graham and Dean do, including their family get-togethers.
他们的目标是赢得粉红色海绵螺旋，
They're aiming for a winning spiral of pink sponge,
用椰子和朗姆酒意式奶冻分层，
layered with coconut and rum panna cotta,
裹着百香果芝士蛋糕圆筒。
wrapped around a passion fruit cheesecake cylinder.
他们的“酷跑”卷饼将用冰镇菠萝包裹
And their Cool Runnings roulade will be wrapped in a chilled pineapple
用酸橙和辣椒糖浆浸泡过的意大利烤肉。
carpaccio, soaked in a lime and chilli syrup.
我们今天带来了一台很厉害的切片机。
We've brought a beastie of a slicing machine today.
我喜欢菠萝，所以一定要放进去。
And I like pineapple, so it's got to go in there.
对于第一个挑战，热带臭虫似乎很有吸引力。
For this first challenge, the tropical bug seems to be catching.
我们决定用芒果。
We decided to go with mango.
那么芒果可以…
Then mango can be...
我觉得它很平。我喜欢酸味，
I find it quite flat. I like to have some acidity,
所以我们就在上面涂上了酸橙。
so we just went full-on with lime on it.
很好。但我们将拭目以待。
It's good. But we will see.
我不是法官，所以…
I'm not the judge, so...
罗曼15岁时就在法国开始了他的糕点师生涯。
Romain began his patisserie career in France at just 15 years old.
年仅21岁，
At only 21,
世界著名的皇家咖啡馆酒店发现了他的天赋
his raw talent was spotted by the world-famous Hotel Cafe Royal
他现在是他们有史以来最年轻的首席面包师。
and he is now their youngest ever head baker.
罗曼和琳恩的卷饼会有一层青柠蛋白酥皮
Romain and Leanne's roulade will have a bruleed lime meringue coating
可以把芒果慕斯，酸橙和芒果果冻藏起来。
which will hide mango mousse and lime and mango jelly.
为了确保所有重要的整齐螺旋…
And in a bid to ensure that all-important neat spiral...
现在我要把它们放在托盘上。
I'm now going to put them on the trays.
为了灵活，罗曼选择了经典的瑞士卷海绵。
For flexibility, Romain has chosen to make a classic Swiss roll sponge.
按照食谱，微笑和希望。
Follow the recipe, smile and hope.
我还能说什么呢?
What else can I say?
不管他们选择什么食谱……
Whichever recipe they've chosen...
热那亚是一种无脂海绵，又轻又好。
Genoese is a fatless sponge, nice and light.
这很容易操作。
It's easy to manipulate.
. .做卷饼的海绵是糕点师最善变的情妇。
..the sponge for a roulade is patisserie's most fickle mistress.
我们准备了日本海绵，把它泡进去
We've got the Japanese sponge and we've just infused that
加一些抹茶绿茶。烤箱预热，180度。
with some matcha green tea. Preheated oven, 180 degrees.
只是烤得不够熟，
Just a fraction under-baked,
它的质地也不会和异国的水果馅形成对比。
and its texture won't contrast with the exotic fruit fillings.
稠度看起来不错。
The consistency looks all right.
稍微多一点，就不能滚了。
A fraction over and it will be impossible to roll.
别担心，我会在那里的。好吧!
# Don't worry, I'll be there... All right!
每一件小事都会好起来的。＃
# Every little thing are going to be all right. #
我们希望你在节目结束时也能唱这首歌!
We hope you are going to sing this at the end of the show as well!
但萨沃伊的艾迪和马希德已经放弃了自己
But the Savoy's Eddie and Mashid have given themselves
更让人担心的是。你打算怎么把它卷起来?
even more to worry about. How are you going to roll it up?
我们把它摊开，然后把每一片分开切，
We spread it and then we cut each slice individually,
然后像这样把它们卷起来，这样就能确保
and then we roll them like that, just so we can ensure
每一块都卷得很好。
that each piece is perfectly rolled.
每一个都必须是相同的。
Each one has to be identical.
会好的，主厨。看起来你很自信。
It will be, chef. Looks like you are very confident.
没有恐慌。
There's no panic.
伊朗出生的Mashid的自信让她放弃了13年的职业生涯
Iranian-born Mashid's confidence saw her give up a 13-year career
去追求她对糕点的热爱。
at the Foreign Office to pursue her passion for pastry.
仅仅四年后，
Just four years later,
她正在为伦敦的五星级酒店Savoy完善甜点。
she's perfecting desserts for London's 5-star Savoy.
老实说，我希望我能早点这么做。
I wish I had done it sooner, to be quite honest.
我非常喜欢它。
I love it so much.
她的玻璃卷将以芒果酥为特色，
Her glazed roulades will feature mango confit,
椰子白巧克力甘纳许
coconut white chocolate ganache
还有百香果糖浆，
and passion fruit syrup,
她会用它来浸泡无脂维也纳海绵。
which she'll use to soak her strips of fatless Viennese sponge.
海绵卷很薄，几分钟就能烤好。
Roulade sponges are so thin they bake in only a few minutes.
哔哔声!哔哔声……
BLEEP! BLEEP...
犯错的余地很小。
The margin for error is tiny.
快，快，快。只要30秒就能摧毁整个团队
Quick, quick, quick. Just 30 seconds could destroy the team's
前景在这第一个挑战。
prospects in this first challenge.
美丽。哦，闻起来真香!
Beautiful. Oh, the smell is really nice!
我对这个造型很满意。
I'm very happy for the look.
有多长时间?八分钟。
How long was it? Eight minutes.
是的。如果你把它放在托盘上太久，
Yeah. If you leave it on the tray too long,
然后它就会变脆，你就不能卷了。
then it will crisp up and then you can't roll it.
我要把衣服放在上面。
I'm going to place the cloths on top.
在我把它们卷起来之前，它会让它们保持柔软。
It will maintain them soft until I roll them up.
我觉得它们看起来很棒。漂亮、鲜艳的颜色。
I think they look great. Nice, vibrant colour.
颜色是凯莉和凯蒂最不担心的。
Colour is the least of Kelly and Katie's worries.
我要倒霉了。
I'm having a disaster.
把一切都告诉我。
Tell me all about it.
是在你的个人生活中还是在蛋糕上?
Is it in your personal life or is it with the cakes?
我两方面都很好。她笑着说
I'm good for both. SHE LAUGHS
是蛋糕。
It is the cake.
我的海绵有点粘稠，所以没有煮好，
My sponge is a little bit dense and therefore didn't cook properly,
所以我真的很伤心，但我没有时间重拍，
so I'm absolutely gutted, but I don't have time to remake,
但我只能随波逐流
but I've just got to go with it.
我是说，好像他们从来没有注意到那样的事情。从来没有!
I mean, it's not like they ever notice things like that. Never!
她笑着说
SHE LAUGHS
所以，祈祷吧。
So, fingers crossed.
大厨们，你们已经完成一半了。
Chefs, you are halfway through.
这个分层的微型挑战将变得更加困难。
This layered miniature challenge is about to get much harder.
团队还得送出伯努瓦的歌剧切片。
The teams still have to deliver Benoit's opera slice.
歌剧会出很多问题。
A lot can go wrong with an opera.
蛋糕的层次感完美无瑕
The gateau's immaculately neat layers
据说和大阶梯很像吗
are said to resemble the grand tiers
在令人惊叹的巴黎歌剧院里。
inside the stunning Paris opera house.
我选择这个挑战是因为，首先，我喜欢它。
I have picked this challenge because, first, I like it.
这只是一种享受。
It's just a treat to eat.
从技术上讲，它显示了你的分层技巧。
Technically, it shows your master skills of layering.
你从海绵开始，它必须是joconde。
You start with the sponge, it has to be joconde.
joconde的关键是杏仁成分。
The key with the joconde is the almond element.
所以，你需要让混合物均匀均匀地涂抹，
So, you need to have a perfect even spread of the mixture,
然后在被浓咖啡浸泡之前完美烘焙。
and then baked perfectly before it gets soaked with very strong coffee.
奶油奶油，更多的joconde…
Buttercream, more joconde...
. .甘纳许进来了，优雅，丝质，
..and the ganache comes in - elegant, silk,
再来一个joconde，更多的奶油，上釉，切，
another joconde, more buttercream, you glaze, you cut,
最后，在每一片面包上整齐地刻上“歌剧”二字。
and finish with the word "opera" neatly inscribed on every slice.
伯努瓦期待着这部经典的完全忠实的再现。
Benoit is expecting a totally faithful recreation of this classic.
但这是一个冒险的计划…
But as well as a risky plan for rolling their roulade...
趁它还没凝固，把它们全割了。不要担心把它放在托盘上。
Cut them all now before it sets. Don't worry about putting it on the tray.
我得把它放在托盘上。
I have to put it on the tray.
但之后你可以把它放回冰箱里，对吧?不…
But then you can put it back in the freezer after, can't you? No...
是的，你可以。不。是的。
Yes, you can. No. Yes.
艾迪和马什德又在歌剧院赌了一把
Eddie and Mashid are taking another gamble with the opera's
Hallmark joconde海绵。
hallmark joconde sponge.
我们要做无谷蛋白约康德。
So, we're going to do a gluten-free joconde.
好的。我们觉得它给了我们更多的质感，
OK. We feel that it gives us a little more texture to work with,
再多一点……弹性、灵活性?
a little more of a... Elasticity, flexibility?
是的，或多或少。好的。这很有趣。
Yeah, more or less. OK. That's interesting.
我们可以把食谱用电子邮件发给你。好的!
We can e-mail you the recipe. OK!
还有文字，你打算在什么颜色上写歌剧词?
And the writing, what colour are you going to write the opera word on?
黑巧克力。黑巧克力!
Dark chocolate. Dark chocolate!
应该是这样的。
As it should be.
我以为是白巧克力?
I thought it was white chocolate?
你想错了。
You think wrong.
而萨沃伊人是无谷蛋白的…
While the Savoy go gluten-free...
这个碗可能太小了一点。
This bowl is maybe a bit too small.
. .在皇家咖啡厅酒店
..over at the Hotel Cafe Royal,
他们不小心剪掉了一个至关重要的歌剧部分。
they have accidentally cut out a crucial opera component.
我们没有好好读案情摘要。
We didn't read the brief properly.
评委们期待的是joconde海绵蛋糕，杏仁味更浓，
The judges will be expecting a joconde sponge, where it's more almond-y,
我们用的海绵更柔软。
and the sponge we've got is more spongy.
我们没有时间再做一个了。
We don't have any time to make another one.
他们要说的话让我很紧张。
It's making me really nervous what they're going to say.
我为法国人感到抱歉，如果他们再看我一眼的话。
I'm sorry for French people, if they are looking at me again.
人……人们现在可能只想杀了我!
People... People may just want to kill me now!
这只是歌剧的一个层次。
This is just one of the layers in the opera.
我得让他们扯平。
I've got to make them even.
如果连一圈都没有，
If it's not even all the way round,
它的一半会变成饼干，然后我们就会深陷其中。
half of it will turn out like a biscuit and then we're going to be deep in it.
准备好了。
Ready to go in.
歌剧海绵的烘烤时间将直接影响其整洁程度
The baking time for an opera sponge will directly affect how neatly
完成的蛋糕可以切片。
the finished cake can be sliced.
如果烤得太硬，在切的时候
If over-baked and tough, during cutting
填充物会被迫渗出来。
the fillings will be forced to ooze out.
如果未烘烤，一旦被咖啡糖浆浸透，
If under-baked, once soaked with the coffee syrup,
这些层将会瓦解。
the layers will disintegrate.
我们用的是浓缩咖啡，所以味道很浓。
We're using an espresso, so it is very intense.
这就是歌剧蛋糕的精髓，当你吃它的时候，
That's the idea with the opera cake is that as you eat it,
它应该像咖啡一样。
it should be like coffee.
尽管他把喜欢的新鲜菠萝放进了面包卷，
Despite bringing his love of fresh pineapple to his roulade,
说到格雷厄姆的歌剧，他的咖啡一点也不新鲜。
when it comes to Graham's opera, his coffee is far from fresh.
我们用的是露营咖啡。
We're using a Camp Coffee.
这是咖啡香精，里面有菊苣。
It's coffee essence with chicory in it.
我们用营地咖啡，因为我挺喜欢的。
We use the Camp Coffee because I kind of like it.
但我们要一杯浓缩咖啡，如果你要做的话。
But we'll have an espresso, if you're making.
已经在努力实现雄心勃勃的日本之行了…
Already struggling to pull off an ambitious Japanese roulade...
不要冒太大的风险。
Not too much risk.
. .WI烹饪学校的咖啡风味来源更多一点
..the WI cookery school's source of coffee flavour is a little more
脚踏实地。我们用速溶咖啡。
down-to-earth. We're using instant coffee.
不是每个人都有浓缩咖啡机，
Not everybody has espresso machines,
所以我更喜欢速溶咖啡，因为它很容易买到。
so I prefer instant coffee because it's easily accessible.
看上去不错。看上去不错。
Looking good. Looking good.
时间很短，他们的歌剧片一凉，
With time short, the moment their opera slices are cool,
队伍需要开始浸泡和分层。
the teams need to start soaking and layering.
Joconde、奶油乳酪、
Joconde, buttercream,
joconde,巧克力酱,
joconde, ganache,
乔康得，奶油，乔康得。
joconde, buttercream, joconde.
不…忘了我说的最后一句话吧。
No... Forget the last thing I said.
Joconde海绵非常干燥，它可以吸收大量的水分，
Joconde sponge is very dry and it can absorb a lot of moisture,
所以我总是对玛丽亚说:“把它弄得像个湖区。”
so I am always telling to Maria, "Make it like a Lake District."
湖区!
Lake District!
只是想确保所有地方都浸透了。
Just want to make sure it's well-soaked everywhere.
这是咖啡奶油。确保它是均匀的。
This is the coffee buttercream. Making sure it's nice and even.
它们都要一样，都要完美。
They need to be all the same, all perfect.
但为了追求完美的层次感
But in pursuit of perfect layers,
艾迪和马什德要走另一条复杂的路线。
Eddie and Mashid are taking yet another complicated route.
我们要开始把我们的房子建反了。
We're going to start building ours upside down.
我们还剩多久?大厨们，你们有30分钟。
How long we got left? Chefs, you have 30 minutes.
利亚姆，有点不对劲。
Liam, something's not right.
谢谢你！大厨们，你们还有30分钟!
Thank you. Chefs, you have 30 minutes left!
你有30分钟。
You've got 30 minutes.
这样好多了。
That's much better.
开始滚动海绵。
Going to start rolling the sponge.
希望它能保持得很好。
It's going to hopefully hold itself well.
我要把每一个都单独滚动。
I'm going to roll each one individually.
它显示了一种不同的技能。
It shows a different skill.
我不想像其他人一样。
I didn't want to be like everyone else.
应该没问题。
It should be OK.
现在我只需要挤一下，让它有层次感，甚至。
I just need to squeeze now to have good layers, and even.
先把面包卷拿来，伙计。
Just get these rolls first, mate.
坚持下去。它要散架了，伙计。
Hang on. It's coming apart, mate.
哦，看在上帝的份上!
Oh, for BLEEP sake!
不裂缝。不裂缝。不裂缝。
Don't crack. Don't crack. Don't crack.
我们要把菠萝卷紧。
We are going to get on the pineapple with it rolled up tight.
希望它能保持原来的形状。
Hopefully, it will hold its shape.
我正在为这出歌剧上釉。
I am doing the dark glaze for the opera.
埃迪，你现在要上釉吗?
Are going to glaze that now, Eddie?
不，已经上过釉了。我们把自己的房子建反了。
No, it's already glazed. We built ours upside down.
你把它建反了，就像一场歌剧!
You built it upside down, like a tarte tatin of opera!
你打算在下面放什么?我们要放巧克力之类的东西。
What you going to put underneath? We're going to put, like, chocolate.
这叫长龙。联合国chablon !
It's called a chablon. Un chablon!
抱歉，我要离开你一会儿。
Sorry, I'm just going to run away from you for a second.
每次我跟男人说话，他们都会跑掉。
It's what happens every time I talk to a man - they run off.
我在涂一些金粉，让它看起来更优雅。
I'm applying some gold powder, make it more elegant.
切断它可能是非常关键的。
Cutting it can be very crucial.
我希望我们有足够的时间。
I hope we're going to have enough time.
我唯一担心的是图层，
The only thing that I'm really worried about is the layers,
他们都是一样的。这就是那个时刻。
having them all identical. This is that moment.
真的屏住呼吸。
Literally holding my breath.
歌剧的结果很好。
Opera's coming out really well.
看起来很不错。甚至非常。
Looks very good. Very even.
釉是流动的，如BLEEP。
Glaze is runny as BLEEP.
写，写，写……
Writing, writing, write...
有些压力。
Bit stressed.
我只是在做巧克力叶来装饰卷。
I'm just making the chocolate leaves to decorate the roulade.
它刚出来。
It's just coming out.
因为这里太热了，我的意式奶冻都开始化了。
Cos it's so warm in here, my panna cotta's started to melt.
所以，今天还没有完全解决。
So, it's not quite worked out today.
房间里太热了，奶油都要融化了。
The room is so hot, it's, like, melting all the cream.
没事的，马什德，把它们放进冰箱就行了。
It's fine, Mashid, just put them in the freezer.
五分钟，大厨们。
Five minutes, chefs.
当你开心的时候，时间过得很快。
Time flies when you're having fun.
当你不在的时候。
And when you're not.
只是现在有点发抖……
Just got a bit of the shakes at the moment...
我只是想尽快完成。
Just trying to do it as quick as I can.
这是下降!哔哔声!
It's fallen! BLEEP!
它掉下来了?哔哔声!
It fell down? BLEEP!
不，听着，没事的。这可不好!马希德，马希德，冷静。
No, look, it's OK. It's not OK! Mashid, Mashid, calm down.
艾迪掉了一个托盘在马什德的卷饼上。
Eddie's dropped a tray on a batch of Mashid's roulades.
冷静点，拉希德。没关系。
Calm down, Rashid. It's OK.
看。他们很好。
Look. They're fine.
他们并不好。
They are not fine.
它们被压扁了。
They are squashed.
它根本就不是固定的。
It's not set at all.
是啊，在我手里融化了。
Yeah, just melting in my hands.
我可能不得不离开他们。
I might have to leave them.
你确定你不想喷一下吗?
You sure you don't want to try and spray?
至少喷几个。我不打算喷它们。
At least spray a couple. I'm not going to spray them.
不需要。
Don't have to.
我们能搞定的，马希德。我们能行。
We've got this, Mashid. We've got this.
有些压力。
Bit stressed.
我们要去哪，伙计?
Where we up to, mate?
还剩九个。
Nine to go.
你还有一分钟。
You have one minute left.
接通电源，加糖就行了。
Just power through and put the sugar on.
加糖。
Get the sugar on.
绝对没问题。
It's absolutely fine.
完成了!是的!
Finished! Yes!
绝对的。
Absolutely.
时间到了。
Time is up.
远离你的切片。
Step away from your slices.
BLEEP说对了。
BLEEP nailed it.
我的第一次很完美，你却把它们给毁了。
My first ones were perfect and you squashed them.
破坏。被我自己的队友破坏了!
Sabotage. Sabotaged by my own team member!
我很抱歉。我不知道它会这么做。
I'm sorry. I didn't know it was going to do that.
现在是判断分层微缩模型的时候了。
It's judgment time for the layered miniatures.
她叹了口气，哼着歌
SHE SIGHS AND HUMS
萨沃伊号，请过来。
The Savoy, please come forward.
它们看起来很均匀，非常接近我所希望的
They look pretty even and really close to what I would have hoped an
歌剧的样子。当我举起你的蛋糕，
opera to look like. When I lift up your cake,
你在底部放了一层巧克力。
you actually put a layer of chocolate right on the bottom.
这样做也是非常专业的。
It's very professional to do that as well.
好的。
OK.
毫米。
Mm.
无面粉海绵。
Flourless sponge.
是的。Well-soaked。
Yes. Well-soaked.
我很喜欢你的奶油和你的
And I really enjoyed the balance between your buttercream and your
巧克力酱。我已经尝到了歌剧的味道。
ganache. I've got all the flavour of the opera.
如果你真的写得很好，
If you would have actually nailed the writing,
你会吃到很好吃的。做得很好。
you would have had a very nice slice. Well done.
看着这张卷饼，我希望能有更多的技巧。
Looking at the roulade, I was hoping that there's more finesse.
嗯嗯。釉在哪里?我们出去的时候出了点小问题
Mm-hm. Where's the glaze? We had a slight issue when we were taking out
做卷的海绵。
the sponges for the roulade.
釉已经准备好了，但是我们没时间了。
The glaze was ready but it was just, we ran out of time.
也没时间了。不是釉料就是装饰的问题。
Running out of time as well. It was either the glaze or the decoration.
我决定用装饰。
I decided to go with the decoration.
哦，太遗憾了。是啊，真遗憾。
Oh, that's a shame. Yeah, it's a shame.
我很喜欢你的层次感。
I quite like the layering that you put through.
我觉得做得很漂亮。
I think it's very neatly done.
它非常精确，最重要的是，我真的很喜欢吃它。
And it's so precise and, most of all, I really enjoyed eating it.
平衡刚刚好。
The balance was just right.
我觉得味道好极了。
It tastes sensational to me.
做得很好。谢谢你！味道，非常干净，非常整齐。
Well done. Thank you. The flavour profile, very clean, very neat.
你有椰子，芒果和所有这些。
You've got the coconut, you've got mangoes and all that.
质地方面，我希望海绵是一个法式蛋糕。
Texture-wise, I would have wished that the sponge was a dacquoise.
我不会改变它。
I would not change it.
我不会以任何形式改变它。
I would not change it in any form.
我们要求同存异，对吧?太美了。
We're going to agree to disagree, huh? That is beautiful.
a-mazing。
It's a-mazing.
A-mazing。
A-mazing.
它可能看起来有点像歌剧，但那颗杏仁，
It may look a little bit like an opera, but that almondy,
没有稍微有嚼劲的海绵。
slightly chewy, rich sponge is not there.
看这条面包卷，它们看起来很均匀。
Looking at the roulade, they look quite uniform.
你的巧克力叶怎么了?
What happened to your chocolate leaves?
它们并不完美，我们不想戴上它们。
They were not perfect and we didn't want to put them on.
好的。看起来很简单。
OK. It looks very simple.
海绵很有弹性。
The sponge is very elastic.
天气很干燥。
It's very dry.
我对专业厨师的期望更高。
I would expect more from a professional chef.
从视觉上看，这部歌剧的层次很薄。
Visually, the opera has very thin layers.
所有的东西都切得整整齐齐，白巧克力也完成了，
Everything is neatly cut and it's finished also with white chocolate,
但是你在上面放了一点金粉。
but you've put a little bit of gold powder on it.
你带来了一个小转折。
You've brought a little twist.
巧克力有点多。
A little too much chocolate.
让它有点甜。
Makes it a little bit sweet.
但我有咖啡的余味，而且海绵泡得很好。
But I've got a coffee aftertaste, and the sponge is well-soaked.
看看这个卷饼，很笨重，还有漩涡，
Looking at the roulade, it's quite heavy-handed, and the swirl as well,
它很不整洁。
it is very untidy.
有些地方味道不错，
Some parts of it, the taste is nice,
浓郁的柑橘味，充满异国情调。
the zesty, citrus, exotic taste to it.
但馅料与海绵的比例不对。
However, the proportion of the filling to the sponge is not right.
但我喜欢你海绵里的椰子。谢谢你！
But I like the idea of coconut in your sponge. Thank you.
大厨们，发生什么事了?
Chefs, what happened?
看起来他们好像在呼救。
Look as though they're crying for help.
“救命!”厨房里太暖和了。
"Help!" Just got so warm in this kitchen.
我会说你们选错了食谱，就这样。
I would say you guys chose the wrong recipes, full stop.
其他球队的厨房都是一样的。
The other teams have had the same kitchen.
真遗憾，因为我喜欢粉色海绵的想法。
It's a shame, because I like the idea of the pink sponge.
它的口感很难吃。
The texture is so unpleasant.
事情不像看上去那么糟。
It's not as bad as it looks.
辣椒，我准备好了，味道并不浓烈。
The chilli, I got, and it's not overpowering.
你用了柠檬草，酸橙，椰子，
You used your lemon grass, you used lime, you used coconut,
然后你也有你的激情。
and then you've got your passion as well.
你想把所有东西都放进去，
You are trying to put everything in,
希望有些事情能让彼此开心。
hoping that some things might be happy with each other.
你的歌剧片看起来很有层次感。
Your opera slice actually look quite nice in terms of the layering.
让我们品味。
Let's taste.
你用的是坎普咖啡?
You used Camp coffee?
嗯嗯。我妈妈在咖啡里加了菊苣。
Mm-hm. My mother used chicory to add into her coffee.
这是一个很好的补充，但是，啊，我没有足够的咖啡。
It's a great addition, but, agh, I haven't got enough coffee.
它需要在某个地方有咖啡。
It needs to be coffee somewhere.
呃…
Er...
我离我想要的歌剧还远着呢，伙计们。我很抱歉。
I'm far from the opera I'm looking for, guys. I'm sorry.
我们试着分层。
Well, we've got an attempt at layering.
这些看起来很均匀。
These ones look pretty even.
并不是每个人都是这样。
Not the case for every single one of them.
这大约是3.2。
This about 3.2.
这大约是3.8。
This is about 3.8.
大约5毫米。
About five millimetres.
是的，所以这很不一致。
Yeah, so it's quite inconsistent.
我买了咖啡和巧克力。
I've got the coffee and chocolate.
够香吗?
Is it fragrant enough?
不。我更喜欢烘焙咖啡，
No. I would love a little bit more roasting kind of coffee,
你的海绵有点干。
and your sponge is slightly dry.
看看这个卷，它可以更精确，我能看出来
Looking at the roulade, it can be more precise and I can see that
事实上，你的奶油会让你的切片变重。
actually your cream, it just weighs down your slice.
这不是我见过最吸引人的卷饼，
It's not the most appealing roulade slice I've ever seen,
我就讲到这里。
and I'll leave it there.
海绵很重。
The sponge is very heavy.
还没煮熟。我想尝尝蛋奶冻苹果。
It's not cooked. I was trying to taste the custard apple.
不知何故，它只是迷失在内心。
Somehow, it's just lost inside.
我不会跑着去买那些切片的。
I will not run to buy one of those slices.
从可怕到非常可怕?
On a scale of terrible to really terrible?
糟透了。糟透了。
Terrible. Terrible.
我觉得我让大家失望了，这让我很失望，
I feel like I've let people down, and it's just disappointing for me,
真的。你没有让我失望。
really. You haven't let me down.
我仍然爱你。
I still love you.
经历了劳累的第一天，
After a gruelling first day,
各队现在有黄金时间准备一场更艰巨的比赛
the teams now have a golden hour to prepare for an even more daunting
挑战，明天的展示。
challenge - tomorrow's showpiece.
至于谁在领导，是萨沃伊团队。
In terms of who's leading, it is the Savoy team.
你可以看到埃迪真的在逼自己。
And you can see that Eddie really pushes himself.
是的，他很好胜。
Yeah, he is very competitive.
R巧克力，他们似乎工作效率很高。
R Chocolate, they seem to work very efficiently.
他们工作非常干净，而且很有组织。
They work very, very clean and they organise themselves.
他们甚至有时间打扫厨房。
They even had time to clean the kitchen.
完全正确。非常方便。我是说，令人印象深刻。
Exactly. Very handy. I mean, impressive.
我希望我能那样做。我真的很担心皇家咖啡馆。
I wish I could do that. I'm really worried about Cafe Royale.
他们甚至不会做海绵。
They can't even make a sponge.
但这是年轻人常犯的错误。
But this is the common youngster mistake.
是的。他们没有看简报!
Yeah. They didn't read the brief!
我看到两三支球队在挣扎。
I see two or three teams struggling.
我们来自银石的同事，WI。
Our lovely colleagues from Silverstone, the WI.
我认为他们失去了对野心的控制。
I think they lost control of their ambition.
我有信心。我想他们明天会把它砸了。
I've got faith. I think they're going to smash it tomorrow.
我们不要低估这是一个不容易的挑战。
Let's not underestimate that this is a challenge which is not easy.
哦，不，伯努瓦。
Oh, no, Benoit.
没人想过他们就这么走进去了
No-one was thinking they're going to just be able to have a walk in
明天去公园。
the park tomorrow.
在这五支队伍中有一支必须离开之前，还有一个挑战
One challenge remains before one of these five teams will have to leave
的竞争。早上好，厨师们。
the competition. Good morning, chefs.
是时候进行你的第二场比赛了。
It's time for your second showpiece challenge of the competition.
今天，我们想让你准备一个场合的展示。
Today, we'd like you to prepare an occasion showpiece.
一个人多久会犯一次这样的错误?
How often would one make one of these?
只是偶尔。我明白了。
Just occasionally. I see.
它的灵感来自法国经典的宗教建筑，
It is inspired by the French classic the religieuse,
它包括两个泡芙包，里面装满了法式奶油和
which consists of two choux buns filled with creme patissiere and
上面撒上糖釉。
topped with a sugar glaze.
但我们希望你能更新这部经典，把它变成
But we would like you to update this classic and transform it into a
现代的展示品。
modern showpiece.
展示品必须展示至少两种美味和特色
The showpiece must showcase at least two delicious flavours and feature
特殊的技术。
exceptional technique.
好了，厨师们。他们必须喂饱24个人
There you have it, chefs. They must feed 24 people,
或者一个非常饥饿的人。
or one very hungry person.
现在，你们今天有四个小时来完成你们的现代宗教，
Now, you have four hours today to complete your modern religieuses,
你的时间从现在开始。
and your time starts now.
准备出发!
Ready to go!
Religieuse是法语中修女的意思，
Religieuse is the French word for nun,
据说这种profprofole类型的甜点就像忠实的信徒
and this profiterole-type dessert is said to resemble the faithful
姐妹们还有两个装饰精美的泡芙包。
sisters with two beautifully decorated choux buns.
所以我们在测试他们的能力，让他们把经典变成一个令人惊叹的因素。
So we're testing their abilities to take that classic into a wow factor.
身高、技能。
Height, skills.
它也需要烤得漂亮。
It needs to be baked beautifully as well.
我必须有一个光滑的质地，当我举起来的时候，要有一个好的V形。
I have to have a nice smooth texture to give me a good V when I lift up.
就快到了。我所有的学生都知道什么是flappy V。
It's almost there. All my students know about a flappy V.
呵呵
CHUCKLING
当我咬一口泡芙的时候，它应该很漂亮，
When I bite into the choux, it should be a beautiful,
酥脆的外表和轻盈、通风、柔软的内部，
crispy exterior and a light, airy, pillowy interior,
香味扑鼻而来。
exploding with beautiful flavour.
我们现在处于比赛的这个阶段，你负担不起
We are now at this stage of the competition when you cannot afford
浪费每一分钟。所以他们必须从一开始就全力以赴
to waste any minute. So they have to crack on from the first minute go
确保他们利用每一个可以利用的时间
and make sure they use every available time they've got to
制作一些特别的东西。
produce something special.
大多数团队都在准备经典的泡芙包
While most teams are preparing classic choux buns...
显然，泡芙面点应该有手绘的管道。
Obviously, choux pastry should have freehand piping.
. .希望能改善昨天混乱的表现，
..hoping to improve on yesterday's chaotic performance,
格雷厄姆发明了一种方法可以保证基地的稳定
Graham has developed a method that could deliver stability for the base
他的宗教信仰。我用了约克郡布丁罐头，因为
of his religieuses. I've used Yorkshire pudding tins because
我只想要一个平坦均匀的龙骨，真的，这样它就不会摇晃，
I just want a flat, even keel, really, so it doesn't, urp,
你明白我的意思吗?它不会拉锯。
you know what I mean? It doesn't seesaw.
他希望完美的泡芙会充满土耳其风味
His hopefully perfect choux will be filled with Turkish
奶油蛋糕和巧克力慕斯，
delight flavoured creme patissiere and chocolate mousse,
他们会坐在一个完全由巧克力制成的展览品下面
and they'll sit beneath a showpiece made entirely of chocolate that's
受到他们最喜欢的运动的启发。
been inspired by their favourite sport.
这是一组轮胎。
It's going to be a group of tyres.
你是说轮胎吗?
Did you say tyres?
轮胎。然后我们有一个排气从顶部出来。哇。
Tyres. And then we have an exhaust that comes out the top. Wow.
再加上一点哇，就给你们听。
And a little wow on the top of that, just for you guys.
哦。好的，很好，那么……你想哇，
Oh. OK, great, so... You wanted wow,
所以我们要试着给你wow。好的。
so we're going to try and give you wow. OK.
感激,感激。
Appreciated, appreciated.
我看到你用蛋糕罐做泡芙糕点。是的。
I saw you using a cake tin for your choux pastry. Yes.
这让我想起了约克郡布丁。
Well, this reminds me of Yorkshire puddings.
是的。我喜欢约克郡布丁。
Yes. I love Yorkshire puddings.
在演示中可能会有一个现代的转折。
There may be a modern twist in the presentation.
斯拉夫和玛丽亚也在用巧克力制作他们的展示品，
Slav and Maria are also creating their showpiece from chocolate,
但他们的作品可能更符合宗教主题。
but theirs is perhaps more in keeping with the religieuse theme.
玛丽亚现在正在做一本圣经书。
Maria at the moment is making a Bible book.
噢,是吗?圣经书?
Oh, yeah? A Bible book?
是的。巧克力圣经?
Yes. A chocolate Bible book?
是的。你觉得这是第一本巧克力圣经吗?
Yes. Do you think this is the first chocolate Bible book ever?
他们的巧克力圣经将被经典的宗教信仰包围，
Their chocolate Bible will be surrounded by classic religieuses,
夹心巧克力奶油和榛子果仁，
filled with chocolate creme patissiere and hazelnut praline,
在它们之上耸立着一个巧克力装饰的教堂尖顶
and towering above them all will be a chocolate church spire decorated
配上蜡烛、白巧克力玫瑰和回火巧克力叶。
with candles, white chocolate roses and tempered chocolate leaves.
你能吃叶子吗?
Can you eat the leaf?
不是树叶。但大概一天五次，对吧?
Not the leaf. But it's like five a day, innit?
笑声
LAUGHTER
这可能不是你今天最好的沙拉选择。
It might not be your best salad choice for today.
可能是吧。
Could be.
Leanne和Romain也会用巧克力做建筑。
Leanne and Romain will also be building with chocolate.
我们要做一个巧克力黑森林主题的展示品。
We're making a chocolate Black Forest-themed showpiece.
但是，在用海绵瑞士卷做的卷饼失败后……
But, after a failed roulade made with Swiss roll sponge...
我们对巧克力工作更有信心。
We're more confident with chocolate work.
. .一场没有jaconde的歌剧
..and an opera without a jaconde,
他们现在正在计划一个没有泡芙的宗教仪式。
they're now planning a religieuse without a choux.
我看到你铸造了很多球体。
I saw that you mould a lot of spheres.
那是干什么用的?使它现代化。
What is that for? To modernise it.
我们要做巧克力底。
We're having a chocolate base.
你以前在法国见过宗教吗?
You've seen religieuses before, in France?
我知道。一个大泡芙，一个小泡芙。
I know. It's a big choux and a small choux.
所以底料是泡芙还是不是泡芙?
So the base is a choux or it's not a choux?
不，底座是半个黑巧克力球。
No, the base is half a sphere of dark chocolate.
哦。因为你想要现代的，所以我不想…
Oh. Because you wanted it modern, so I didn't want to be...
好的。泡芙够了吗?
OK. Is that going to be enough choux?
我想是的。
I think so.
他们的半巧克力球基地将容纳黑巧克力外交官
Their half chocolate sphere bases will hold dark chocolate diplomat
奶油中加入酸樱桃。
cream with a sour cherry insert.
他们的泡芙顶部会填上樱桃外交官奶油。
Their choux topping will be filled with a Kirsch diplomat cream.
这些现代宗教将居住在以黑森林为代表的地方
And these modern religieuses will inhabit a Black Forest represented
在一棵华丽的巧克力树旁。
by an ornate chocolate tree.
我总是很关心你
I'm always concerned with you,
你给自己施加了多少压力……
how much you are putting yourself under pressure...
我们很好。你真的有时间完成吗?
We're fine. Will you have the time to actually finish?
让我们开始吧。我们要去泡芙。
Let's choux off. We're going to choux off.
祝你好运。看到的。
Good luck. See.
再见。
Bye.
当三支队伍向巧克力之神祈祷时……
While three teams pray to the gods of chocolate...
毅力，耐心，都是我没有的品质。
Perseverance, patience, all the traits I haven't got.
. .为了展示他们的作品，
..for their showpieces,
WI烹饪学校和萨沃伊人将他们的信仰放在了神圣的地方
the WI Cookery School and the Savoy are putting their faith in the holy
三位一体的烤杏仁，糖和更多的糖。
trinity of toasted almonds, sugar and even more sugar.
我们的展品是用牛轧糖做的，这是一种焦糖。
Our showpiece is made out of nougatine, which is a caramel.
传统上，你会把它放在牛轧巧克力片上。
Traditionally, you would serve it on a nougatine piece.
萨沃伊华丽的三层牛轧巧克力展示架将会
The Savoy's ornate, triple-tiered nougatine display stand will be
上面点缀着优雅的白巧克力。
topped with elegant strands of white chocolate.
他们的宗教信仰会被焦糖奶油和柚子豆腐填满，
Their religieuses will be filled with caramel cremeux and yuzu curd,
用榛子泥和透明糖来装饰
and will be decorated with hazelnut puree hair and transparent sugar
工作的帽子。牛轧糖不是一种很
work hats. The nougatine is not something that gets made very
现在有很多，所以我们想试一试，再逼自己一把。
much nowadays, so we want to give it a go and push ourselves a bit more.
凯利和凯蒂将传统的牛轧糖推向了新的高度。
Kelly and Katie are pushing the traditional nougatine even further.
所以我做了很多婚礼蛋糕和庆祝蛋糕，
So I do a lot of wedding cakes and celebration cakes,
但婚礼蛋糕绝对是我最喜欢做的事情。
but wedding cakes are definitely my favourite thing to do.
我很喜欢传统的堆叠的样子，所以我们要把它堆叠起来。
I do like that traditional stacked look, so we're going to stack it up.
我想我们会有四层。
I think we're going to have four tiers.
为了留在竞争中，他们将看到传统的牛轧糖
Their bid to stay in the competition will see a traditional nougatine
塔上堆满了樱桃、巧克力和樱桃饼，
tower piled with cherry, chocolate and Kirsch-filled religieuses,
但在不太传统的煎饼或甜甜圈上，
but topped with a less than traditional beignet, or doughnut,
由乳清干酪和龙蒿制成。
made with ricotta and tarragon.
昨天，你在舞会上的表现很糟糕
Yesterday, you had a pretty disastrous attempt at the roulade
因为你用的是奇怪的味道。
because you were using kind of odd flavours.
嗯嗯。今天你带来了龙蒿。
Mm-hm. And today you bring tarragon.
是的。有点像大料的味道，对吧?
Yes. It's kind of like an aniseed taste, isn't it?
它是。是的。一切都是关于平衡。
It is. Yes. It's all about balance.
你们要保持平衡
You guys nail the balance,
你有一些潜在的非凡之处。
you've got something which potentially is extraordinary.
大厨们，你们已经完成一半了。
Chefs, you are halfway through.
小心点。还有两个小时。
Watch your backs. Two hours left.
这是热焦糖，170度以上。
This is hot caramel, so 170, above 170 degrees.
超级热。牛轧糖的温度是170度，
Super hot. Nougatine cooks at 170 degrees and,
除非是刚出炉的…
unless it's worked straight from the oven...
嗷，嗷，嗷。
Ow, ow, ow.
. .它不可能被切割或塑形。
..it's impossible to cut or shape.
我戴着手套。
I'm wearing the gloves.
你耍流氓了，是吗?我不听话了。你要小心。
You've gone rogue, haven't you? I've gone rogue. You be careful.
不，不，不。我的头发断裂了。
No, no, no, no. I've got breakage.
牛轧糖，它只是不太适合打球。
Nougatine, it's just not quite playing ball.
哦，那就像……噢!
Oh, that's like... Ow!
哦,哔哔声。
Oh, BLEEP.
凯蒂亲手摸过融化的焦糖。
Katie's touched molten caramel with her bare hand.
真是个白痴。对不起,凯利。
What an idiot. Sorry, Kelly.
没关系，别担心。
It's all right, don't worry.
像往常一样，我们在练习时做得很完美，但在那天…
As per usual, perfect when we did it in practice, but on the day...
燃烧自己永远不会有帮助。
Burning yourself never helps.
凯利现在要靠自己打造他们的样板。
Kelly now faces building their showpiece on her own.
哔哔声。疼吗?有点刺痛，是吗?
BLEEP. Is that hurting? Stinging a little bit, is it?
我不会再做焦糖了。
I am not doing any more caramel.
我就把它留在这里。是的。
So, I'll leave that there for you. Yeah.
她烧伤的手无法继续制作牛轧糖，
Unable to continue nougatine construction with her burnt hand,
凯蒂现在需要把她所有的注意力集中在宗教上。
Katie now needs to focus all of her attention on the religieuse.
正确的。管。
Right. Tube.
填满吗?是的,请。
Fill? Yes, please.
大厨们，你们还有一个小时!你还有一个小时!
Chefs, you've got an hour left! You got one hour left!
我伤害了。
I hurt.
评委要求的是形状完美，酥脆，
The judges have demanded perfectly formed, crisp,
好馅，泡芙包。
well filled, choux buns.
确保它们都被填满了，所有的。
Make sure they're filled, all of them.
是的。不要错过任何一个。
Yes. Don't miss any.
这是一个团队无法完成的任务。
Something that one team aren't quite ready to deliver.
嗯…有些有点平。
Um... Some of them are a bit flat.
说真的，它看起来确实像约克郡布丁!
Seriously, it does look like a Yorkshire pudding!
这可能是他们想要应用的设计的一部分，但这是真的。
It may be part of the design they want to apply, but it's true.
看起来有点奇怪。
It looks a little bit strange.
我想我来管它，伙计。
I think I'll pipe it, mate.
格雷厄姆决定把泡芙作为他的宗教基地
Graham's decided to start the choux for the base of his religieuse
再来一遍。
all over again.
他们有麻烦了。还有土耳其软糖，是玫瑰味的。
They are in trouble. And then they have Turkish delight, which is rose.
我希望他们不会给我一块肥皂。
I hope they're not going to give me a bar of soap.
只需要20分钟就能做好。
It'll only take 20 minutes to cook.
他们不出来了，我不想打他们太多
They're not coming out, and I don't want to bang them too much
因为我不想打散它们。
cos I don't want to shatter them.
咖啡馆皇家。那天他只吃一个泡芙包。
Cafe Royale. He will have only one choux bun on that religieuse.
底座是一个巧克力外壳。
The base will be a chocolate shell.
我希望它不会太重。
I hope it's not going to be too heavy.
我们要把它冷冻起来。
We're going to blast freeze that one.
尝不出焦糖的味道。
Can't taste the caramel.
萨沃伊。做……你可能认为他们遥遥领先，
The Savoy. Do... You could think they are comfortably ahead,
在昨天的挑战之后。
after yesterday's challenge.
但他们在冒险，他们在用牛轧糖。
But they're taking risks, they're working with nougatine.
发出哔哔声
BLEEP
R巧克力。他们已经在修建宗教建筑了。
R Chocolate. They are building the religieuse already.
他们非常有条理。
They are super organised.
它们看起来很漂亮。
They look beautiful.
这是我们的包。
So this is our beignet.
这是白干酪、香草、龙蒿、
So, this is a mixture of cottage cheese, vanilla, tarragon,
还有泡芙糕点。
and choux pastry.
WI。龙蒿吗?
The WI. Tarragon?
意大利乳清干酪吗?和巧克力?
Ricotta? And chocolate?
或者炸鱼薯条?哦啦，哦啦，哦啦。
And maybe fish and chip? Oh la, oh la, oh la.
还有45分钟就能确保在比赛中获得一席之地了。
45 minutes left to secure a place in the competition.
她想要一模一样的，不是吗?
She wants them identical, doesn't she?
不坏。
Not bad.
我太高兴了。
I'm so happy.
随着时间的流逝，
And with time running out,
还有24个精致的宗教用途需要填充和装饰……
there's still 24 delicate religieuse to fill and to decorate...
不…
No...
. .还有令人惊叹的中心装饰。
..and stunning centrepieces to construct.
看那个。好伙计，很好。
Look at that. Good mate, very good.
他笑着说
HE CHUCKLES
我只是要确保所有东西都放平，这样，
I'm just making sure everything's level, so that,
当我们用它建造时，它不会倒塌。
when we build with it, it's not going to topple over.
巧克力建筑……
Building with chocolate...
. .或者牛轧糖，已经足够具有挑战性了。
..or nougatine, is challenging enough.
但是艾迪和马希德……
But Eddie and Mahshid...
. .两者都用。
..are using both.
显然，我们必须确保一切都在那里
Obviously, we've got to make sure that everything is there and that
你可以走了。
you're ready to go.
喷雾。
Spray.
我要把花拿出来。
I'm getting the flowers out.
对吧?是的。我们就快到了。
Right? Yes. And we're almost there.
它看起来像一件艺术品。
It looks like a piece of art.
不是吗?是的。
Does it? Yeah.
我跟你说，毕加索会嫉妒的。
Picasso would be jealous, I'm telling you.
很温柔。
Very gently.
明白了吗?是的。
You got it? Yeah.
准备好了吗?是的。开始吧。
Ready? Yeah. Here we go.
明白了吗?
Got it?
把你的手放在背后。是的。我认为……
Uh, with your hands on the back. Yes. I think...
. .关于在…
..about over...
不，不，不。请后面。哦,好吧。只是…
No, no, no. Behind, please. Oh, OK. Just...
是的。是的。
Yes. Yeah.
厨师!还剩五分钟!
Chefs! Five minutes left!
所以，开始涂你的泡芙吧，我们要离开家了!
So, start putting your choux on, we're going to leave the house!
银石车队在上面。
Team Silverstone on it.
发出哔哔声
BLEEP
快，快，快。我们只有几分钟的时间。
Quick, quick, quick. We only have a few minutes.
开始加糖，留下蘑菇。
Start doing the sugar, leave the mushrooms.
加油，玛丽亚，我们能行的。是的，我们能做到!来吧。
Come on Maria, we can do this. Yes, we can do this! Come on.
发出哔哔声
BLEEP
把喷雾拿来。喷雾,喷雾…哦!
Bring the spray. Spray, spray... Oh!
这个要掉下来了，艾迪。
This one is falling, Eddie.
等一下，大厨们。你还有一分钟。
One minute, chefs. You have one minute left.
把东西穿上，别担心会掉下来。
Just put the things on, don't worry if they fall.
发出哔哔声
BLEEP
一个掉在了上面。
One fell on the top.
厨师!时间到了。
Chefs! Time is up.
发出哔哔声
BLEEP
请远离你的显示器。
Please step away from your displays.
美丽。
Beautiful.
合唱戏剧
CHORAL MUSIC PLAYS
五个辉煌的宗教展示品
Five glorious religieuse showpieces
现在面对最后的审判。
now face the final judgment.
他叹了口气
HE SIGHS
看起来真的很酷。一切看起来都很酷。
That looks really cool. Everything looks really cool.
是的,当然。
Yeah, definitely.
牛轧糖，这是谁的创意?
Nougatine, whose BLEEP idea was that?
我的。
Mine.
她笑着说
SHE LAUGHS
音乐还在继续
MUSIC CONTINUES
音乐渐渐消失
MUSIC FADES AWAY
至少他们不是今天从马戏团来的。
At least they're not from the croque today.
这个结构实际上看起来很有活力。
The structure actually looked alive.
有一根手指在向上抓
There's a finger clawing up
当你看着它的时候，你会觉得它很神奇。
and it's quite magical when you look at it.
但那小泡芙包已经很好吃了。
But that little choux bun is as good as it gets.
从外形和形状来看，
In terms of the way it looks, the shape,
我们应该有两个而不是一个吗?
should we have had two instead of just one?
我们得弄清楚。
Well, we need to find out.
哦。
Ooh.
啊!
Ah!
我相信那个小泡芙包…
I believe that little choux bun...
. .其实很可爱。
..is actually lovely.
樱桃酒喝多了一点
A little too much Kirsch,
但它的质地非常柔滑，
but the texture - very creamy,
和泡芙油酥非常搭。
works very well with the choux pastry.
我不确定巧克力切达干酪怎么样，
I'm not sure about the chocolate cheddar,
与其说是宗教信仰，不如说是宗教信仰。
it's more like profiteroley than religieusely.
不过，我想樱桃酒还行，
The Kirsch I think is all right for me, however,
我觉得杯子里的巧克力太多了。
I think it's too much chocolaty in the cup.
但这…
But this...
. .是一个非常非常漂亮的蛋糕。
..is a pretty, pretty gateau.
快速弦乐演奏
FAST STRING MUSIC PLAYS
我看到的是……
What I see is...
. .很粗糙。
..pretty rough.
而你为了牛轧糖倾尽全力。
And you went all out with nougatine.
这些小山脊也不费力地把它抬起来。
And the little ridges makes no effort either to lift it all up.
我想到了车祸。
Car crash, which comes to mind.
泡芙包，又香又脆。
The choux bun, nice and crispy.
我喜欢香蒂伊。
I like the Chantilly.
有一种奶油味，但焦糖味…正确的。
There's a creaminess to it, but the caramel flavour is... Right.
. .太温和了，尤其是……
..is too mild, especially...
. .当你和柚子一起吃饭的时候。
..when you get to eat with it, the yuzu.
我真希望里面多放点焦糖。
How I wish there was more caramel in there.
它根本就不平衡。
It just doesn't balance well at all.
非常感谢。谢谢你！
Thank you very much. Thank you.
谢谢你！古典音乐演奏
Thank you. CLASSICAL MUSIC PLAYS
她叹了口气
SHE SIGHS
总的来说，它还是很吸引人的。
As a whole, it's quite attractive.
我喜欢你花的手法。
Love the technique of your flower.
我认为做得很好。
I think it's very well done.
谢谢你！
Thank you.
我个人觉得这个主题有点黑暗。
Personally I find the theme a bit dark.
宗教不仅仅是黑暗的一面，
Religion is not just about the dark side,
但在一起有很多快乐。
but there's a lot of joy together.
我希望能看到更多的颜色，
I would have loved to have seen a bit more colour,
但是小修女们呢?
but how about the little nuns?
整天给我买这个。
Buy me this all day.
它是可爱的。谢谢你！
It's lovely. Thank you.
非常柔滑。
Very silky.
我喜欢榛子的味道。
I love the hazelnut flavour.
你可以感觉到泡芙的酥脆。
You can feel the crunchiness of your choux.
我喜欢它。巧克力是非常非常平衡的。
I love it. Chocolate is very, very well-balanced.
你能感觉到所有的泡芙。
You feel all the choux.
我认为做得很好。
I think it's well done.
是的。非常感谢。
Yeah. Thank you very much.
干得好，干得好，漂亮。玛丽亚:谢谢。
Well done, well done, well done, beautiful. MARIA: Thank you.
音乐戏剧
MUSIC PLAYS
音乐褪色
MUSIC FADES
繁荣繁荣?
Boom boom?
两个人:砰，砰。
BOTH: Boom boom.
这是一个非常男性化的展示品。
It's a very masculine showpiece.
轮胎，好的，我知道了。
Tyres, OK, I get the picture.
但作为宗教泡芙，它有点粗糙。
But as a choux religieuse, it's a little bit rough.
圆顶不是很好。
That's not very well domed.
有点平。你把它涂上了颜料之类的东西。
It's a bit flat. You've covered it with colouring powder and stuff.
这很笨拙。
This is clumsy.
当我切开的时候，如果你的馅料不是太浓的话。
When I cut through, it your filling is not overpowering.
然而,厨师……
However, Chef...
关于明胶我提过很多次了，它还是会弹跳的。
I mentioned so many times about gelatine - again, it's bouncing.
如果我往墙上扔，我肯定它们会弹回来的!
If I throw on the wall, I'm sure they will bounce back!
我得到的口感很好，很均衡，
The texture I got is nice, well-balanced,
我喜欢边上的小果冻
I like the little jelly on the side
巧克力慕斯很有味道。
and the chocolate mousse is flavoursome.
所以…
So...
比昨天好一点。嗯嗯。
A bit better than yesterday. Mm-hm.
但这就足够了吗?
But is it enough?
音乐戏剧
MUSIC PLAYS
音乐停止
MUSIC STOPS
这座建筑缺少了很多东西，不能说它是一个展示品。
The structure is missing a lot to be able to say it's a showpiece.
它更像是一个支架，而且是一个做得很差的支架。
It's more like a stand - and a badly made one.
你可以看到你的管道很不一致。
You can see that it's very inconsistent in your piping.
如果我来你的店里买糕点……
If I come to your shop to buy your pastry...
. .我将是一个非常不满意的顾客。
..I will be a very unhappy customer.
哎呦。
Whoops.
我希望里面的馅料能多一些。这是不可接受的。
I would expect more in the filling. It is not acceptable.
如果我去你的店，我有这个…
If I go to your shop, I have this...
. .马上抱怨。
..complain straightaway.
所以，那个小龙蒿煎饼
So, that little tarragon beignet
龙蒿里的味道不会太浓，而且很管用。
actually is not too strong in tarragon and actually works.
实际上，下面还有奶油
And, actually, the cream underneath
和龙蒿也很平衡。
is well-balanced with tarragon, as well.
我的还没煮熟，你也看到了。
Mine is not cooked, as you can see.
我甚至不会为这些宗教人士支付一分钱。
I would not even pay a single cent for these religieuses.
我们仍然从中得到了一些积极的东西。
We've still got a few positives from that.
我们知道那是哔哔声。是哔哔声。嗯嗯。是哔哔声。
We know it was BLEEP. It was BLEEP. Mm-hm. It was BLEEP.
利亚姆:伯努瓦和珍惜现在将对球队进行排名
LIAM: Benoit and Cherish will now rank the teams
基于他们在两项挑战中的表现。
based on their performance in both challenges.
最后一名的队伍将不得不退出比赛。
The team in last place will have to leave the competition.
昨天是美好的一天。今天真是糟糕的一天。
Yesterday was a good day. Today was a bad day.
它看起来确实很有男子气概，
It did look a lot masculine,
但我认为f1是一项非常男性化的运动。
but I think Formula 1 is quite a masculine sport.
我们是男性，不是吗?是的，我们是。
We're masculine, aren't we? Well, we are.
要回家了。我想我们该回家了。
Going home. I think we're going home.
汤姆:伯努瓦和珍爱已经做了决定。
TOM: Benoit and Cherish have made their decision.
第一名的团队完成了所有要求。
The team in first place delivered everything that was asked for.
祝贺你,
Congratulations,
R巧克力店的斯拉夫和玛丽亚。
Slav and Maria from R Chocolate.
你晋级下一轮了。
You are through to the next round.
并列第二的是琳恩和罗曼，
In joint second place are Leanne and Romain,
还有艾迪和马希德。
and Eddie and Mahshid.
那就只剩下银石的格雷厄姆和迪恩了，
So, that leaves Graham and Dean from Silverstone,
还有夏威夷州烹饪学校的凯蒂和凯利。
and Katie and Kelly from the WI Cookery School.
经过深思熟虑，伯努瓦和珍爱已经决定
And after much deliberation, Benoit and Cherish have decided
今晚离开我们的队伍是…
the team that will be leaving us tonight are...
. .格雷厄姆和迪恩。
..Graham and Dean.
祝贺你们其他人。我们下周见。
Congratulations to the rest of you. We'll see you next week.
做得很好。做得很好。
Well done. Well done.
是的，我很难过要离开。
Yeah, I'm sad to be leaving.
我们为此付出了很多努力。
A lot of work, a lot of effort's gone into it.
但我认为这是女生们应得的。是的。
But I think the girls overall deserved it. Yeah.
再见。
See you later.
我们简直不敢相信。
We can't believe it.
我不认为这一定是件坏事
I don't think it's always necessarily a bad thing
也会一点点堕落，从优雅中堕落
to fall, as well, a little bit - fall from grace -
振作起来，让自己变得更好。
and pick yourself up and make yourself better.
干得好，斯拉夫人。给我一个拥抱。
Well done, Slav. Give me a hug.
我为自己感到骄傲，
I am very proud of myself,
但没有玛丽亚，我不可能有今天的成就。
but without Maria, I couldn't be where I am today.
这是我的荣幸。谢谢你，玛丽亚。
It's really a pleasure. Thank you, Maria.
汤姆:下一集，各队将面临秘方挑战。
TOM: Next time, the teams face a secret recipe challenge.
我们都没试过。
None of us have actually tried one before.
并且必须打造一个四季的样板…
And must fashion a four-season showpiece...
我不希望我最大的敌人也这样。
I wouldn't wish this on my worst enemy.
. .除了巧克力什么都没有。
..with nothing but chocolate.
只是内心充满了愤怒。
Just have such a rage inside.
谁将进入最后六强?哎呦。
Who will spring into the final six? Whoops.
还有她的法式蛋糕梦……温柔。
And whose patisserie dreams... Gentle.
. .会落到地球上吗?破解
..will fall to Earth? CRACKING
哦,不!
Oh, no!
字幕由红蜂传媒制作
Subtitles by Red Bee Media
大家好，欢迎回到《职业烘焙大赛》。
Hello, and welcome back to Bake Off: The Professionals.
这场竞争已经到了沸点，
This competition is reaching boiling point,
接下来的两天将决定谁能从预选赛中脱颖而出
with the next two days determining who from this heat will go through
进入最后几轮比赛。
to the final rounds of the competition.
哦，我明白了!沸点!就像你煮蛋糕一样!
Oh, I get it! Boiling point! Like when you boil a cake!
是的，很好。
Yes, very good.
汤姆，你不会煮蛋糕。
Tom, you can't boil cakes.
你是这么说的，但也许这就是你没赢《烘焙大赛》的原因。
Well, so you say, but maybe that's why you didn't win Bake Off.
只是说。加油，利亚姆!我们下楼到厨房去吧。
Just saying. Come on, Liam! Let's go down to the kitchen.
看，糕点师一直在煎。
See with a pastry chef's been frying up.
我不喜欢你，你知道的。
I don't like you, you know.
没人喜欢我，利亚姆，这是我的风格。
Nobody likes me, Liam, That's my thing.
上次，关于泡芙有很多麻烦。
Last time, there was much ado about choux.
R巧克力奴隶和玛丽亚的天堂展示品……
R Chocolate Slave and Maria's heavenly showpiece...
整天给我带这个，很可爱。
Bring me this all day, it's lovely.
. .为他赢得了第一名。非常感谢。
..earned him first place. Thank you very much.
WI烹饪学校的凯蒂和凯利面临着严峻的考验……
WI Cookery School's Katie and Kelly faced nougaty hell...
这个结构缺失了很多。
This structure is missing a lot.
但那是银石的男孩，格雷厄姆和迪恩……
But it was the Silverstone boys, Graham and Dean...
会有一组轮胎。
There's going to be a group of tyres.
. .谁最后一次溜了。
..who slipped one last time.
如果我往墙上扔，我肯定它们会弹回来。
If I throw on the wall, I'm sure they will bounce back.
. .然后就被淘汰了。
..and crashed out of the competition.
是的，我们很难过要离开。我们为此付出了很多努力。
Yeah, we're sad to be leaving. A lot of work, a lot of effort's gone into it.
现在第二轮预赛结束了。
Now the second set of heats come to an end...
凯莉，你能处理这个吗?我来搞定。
Kelly, can you handle this? I've got this.
. .摄制组的食谱完全是个谜
..as the team's taken a recipe that's a total mystery...
我做错了什么?哦……
What am I doing wrong? Oh...
并尝试捕捉四季的魔力在一个宏伟的巧克力展示。
And try to capture the magic of the four seasons in one majestic chocolate showpiece.
一只小鸟在树枝上?为什么不呢?
A bird on a twig in a tree? Why not?
最后六个席位的归属岌岌可危
With the last places in the final six at stake...
哔哔声。
BLEEP.
哪三支球队会向前冲?
Which three teams will spring forward...
哔哔声。
BLEEP.
谁会倒下……全体:哦，不!哦!
And who will fall... ALL: Oh, no! Oh!
退出竞争?
Out of the competition?
我现在只想哭。
I just want to cry now.
今天是巧克力周。
It's chocolate week.
在这四支队伍中，
And of these four teams,
只有三支队伍可以进入决赛。
just three can progress to the final stages of the competition.
为了确保只有最好的人才能通过，
To make sure only the best go through,
评委们提出了一个秘密挑战。
the judges have raised the bar with a secret challenge.
早上好，厨师们!
Good morning, chefs!
考虑到即将发生的事，你们看起来吓坏了。
Given what's about to happen, you all look suitably terrified.
因为今天，你们将面临一个秘方挑战。
Because today, you will face a secret recipe challenge.
评委们将会给你一个惊喜，一个经典甜点的名字，
The judges are about to surprise you with the name of a classic dessert,
然后他们会期望你在没有任何练习或准备的情况下做出决定。
which they will then expect you to make with no practice or preparation whatsoever.
就像一个惊喜派对，但却是有史以来最可怕的惊喜派对!
It's like a surprise party, but the most horrible surprise party ever!
珍惜，请透露今天的秘方。
Cherish, please reveal today's secret recipe.
我们选择了一种经典的奥地利蛋糕。
We have chosen a classic Austrian cake.
随意言论。
Sachertorte.
我们会看到湿润的巧克力海绵和杏酱，
We will expect to see a moist chocolate sponge with apricot jam,
还有光滑的巧克力酱。
and a smooth ganache glaze.
我们希望你能把你的萨赫蛋糕放在巧克力摊上，
We would like you to serve your Sachertorte on a chocolate stand,
顶部是手工制作的双色巧克力花。
and topped with a bicolour, handcrafted chocolate flower.
厨师们，你们有3.5小时的时间来完成今天的秘方挑战。
Chefs, you have 3.5 hours to complete today's secret recipe challenge.
你的时间从现在开始。
And your time starts now.
好的。啊呀。
OK. Blimey.
哇。
Wow.
我从来没尝过沙赫蛋糕。
I haven't tasted Sachertorte before, ever.
所以我有点困惑。
So I'm a little bit confused.
今天，有一点转折。
Today, there is a little bit of a twist.
他们无法为我们的秘方挑战做准备。
They could not prepare for our secret recipe challenge.
我们开始写吧。
Let's get scribing.
他们必须运用自己的知识和本能来完成这项工作。
They have to bring their knowledge and instinct to make this work.
珍惜:在构建结构时，
CHERISH: When building the structure,
我们想看看厨师的创造力。
we would like to see the creativity of the chef.
然而，它需要足够的强度来容纳蛋糕。
However, it needs to be strong enough to hold the cake.
我不想看到崩溃。
I do not want to see a collapse.
这是干什么用的?我们可以用它做证人席。
What's this for? We can use it for the stand.
每个团队都有不同的模具，颜料，
Each team has been given various moulds, paints,
还有帮助他们搭建巧克力摊位的用具。
and utensils to help them create their chocolate stands.
这和……有什么关系?来个萨赫蛋糕?
How is this related...to a Sachertorte?
我是说，我们自己还没有解决这个问题。
I mean, we haven't worked that one out yet ourselves.
来吧。喷，喷，喷，喷，喷。
Come on. Spray, spray, spray, spray, spray.
这是艾迪和马什德的节目!嗨！各位，这是你们的海绵吗?
It's the Eddie and Mashid show! Hi! Guys, is this your sponge?
我担心你可能需要再来一次。
I'm worried you might need to do it again.
我认为这将是非常艰难的……
I think it's going to be very tough...
谁在做结构?我正在修结构。
Who's doing the structure? I'm working on the structure now.
这是我们要做的支架的支架腿。
This is the legs for the stand that we're making.
腿吗?是的。的两条腿!
The legs? Yes. The legs!
就像一个灯台，你知道吗?
Almost like a lamp table, do you know...
三条腿还在吗?
With the three legs going?
哦,耶!然后我们把蛋糕放在上面。
Oh, yeah! And then we'll put the cake on top of that.
埃迪和马什德用一种直截了当的方法来对冲风险。
Eddie and Mashid are hedging their bets with a straightforward approach.
打算把他们的三脚站放低，给它上色
Planning to cast their three-legged stand low and colour it
加深红的可可脂。
with a dark red cocoa butter.
这足以让我们惊叹吗?
CHERISH: Is that enough to wow us?
埃迪:我们的目标就是熬过去。
EDDIE: Our aim is just to get through.
第一名还是第二名并不重要。
Doesn't matter about being first or second.
这是一个好办法吗?我想是的。做你认为最好的事。
Is this a good move? I think so. Do what you think is best.
做你认为对其他三支球队有影响的事情。是的。
Do what you think would make the difference with the other three teams. Yes.
把自己逼得更紧一点……
Pushing themselves a little further...
我需要画一些东西。
I need to draw something.
. .上周的获胜者斯拉夫和玛丽亚，
..last week's winners, Slav and Maria,
我想出了一个更有野心的设计。
have come up with a more ambitious design.
我们在巧克力行业，所以我们很有信心。
We are in the chocolate industry, so we are confident.
所以我要用三个不同的圆柱体做一个支架。
So I'm going to make a stand with three different cylinders.
一个在这里。
So one will be here.
一个在这里。然后，蛋糕在这里。
One here. And then, the cake here.
建造一个高耸的三层建筑足以支撑
Building a towering trio of tiers strong enough to support
一个沙赫蛋糕就可以了
a Sachertorte will take
斯拉夫的专业技能
all of Slav's well-honed expertise.
当我年轻的时候，我曾经是一个木匠。
When I was younger, I used to be a carpenter.
这有点像搭建桌子或厨房。
It's a bit of building a table or kitchen.
所以对我来说，当我完成最终作品时，我真的很开心。
So for me, when I come to the final product, it makes me really happy.
好了，开始吧。
Right, here we go.
开始吧。
Here we go.
各队开始铸造他们的核心。
The teams get to work casting their centrepieces.
如果它们不能迅速起作用……哎呦。对不起。
If they don't work quickly... Whoops. Sorry.
. .他们的架子放不下蛋糕。
..their stands won't set strong enough to hold their cakes.
你能把戒指递给我吗，凯利?
Can you pass me that ring, Kelly?
我可能会放点东西让它保持稳定。
I might put something there to kind of keep it stable.
尽管上周勉强过关，
Despite just scraping through last week,
WI烹饪学校的目标仍然很高。
the WI Cookery School are still aiming high.
凯丽和凯蒂精心打造的摩天石柱就这样诞生了
Kelly and Katie's delicately cast sky-scraping pillar should result
在一个对抗重力的站位上。
in a gravity-defying stand.
我的杆子太大了。我很害怕。
My pole's too big. I'm scared.
哦,不。祝你好运，伙计，你能行的。让我们开始吧。
Oh, no. Good luck, mate, you've got this. Let's go for it.
为了确保自己进入六强，
Determined to secure their place in the final six,
皇家酒店咖啡厅也在冒险。
Hotel Cafe Royal are also taking a risk.
我想画个圈……
I was thinking of just doing a circle...
但我想那就太简单了。
But then I guess it'll be too simple.
以一种本能的方式……
With an instinctive approach...
你的展台有画吗?
Do you have any drawing for your stand?
是的，在那儿。哦，在那儿?
Yes, it's there. Oh, it's there?
噢!琳恩不知道吗?
Ooh! Leanne doesn't know it?
我把它画出来，它会像这样，像这样，像这样。
I draw it, so it's going to be like this and like that, and like this...
然后站起来，可能在这里开花……差不多就是这样。好的。
And then stand, and probably flower here... Something like that. OK.
我想我在医院里见过一个。
Ooh, I think I've seen one of those in hospital.
他还活着吗?
LAUGHTER Was he alive?
如果凭感觉飞行还不够大胆，
If flying by the seat of his pants wasn't daring enough,
罗曼还计划在他的摊位中央挖一个大洞。
Romain also plans to carve a gaping hole in the centre of his stand.
我想到了一个主意，但我知道这要花些时间。
I've come up with an idea, but I know it's going to take me time.
我真的不想惹麻烦，所以…
I really don't want to be in trouble, so...
我遇到了困难。
I'm running into difficulty.
哦……
Oh...
这是可怕的。
That's horrible.
好吧。哔哔声。
All right. BLEEP.
哦……厨师!你还有两个小时，两个小时!
Oh... Chefs! You have two hours left, two hours left!
哦，别这样。
Oh, don't do that.
你可以做下一个。很好。
You can do the next one. Fine.
如果想知道他们的巧克力元素是否会及时凝固
If wondering whether their chocolate elements will set in time
压力还不够大……
wasn't stressful enough...
好了，好了，好了，好了。
Right, done, done, done, done, done.
让我们开始吧。
Let's go for it.
还有一种经典的奥地利蛋糕。
There's also a classic Austrian cake to perfect.
沙赫蛋糕就是海绵蛋糕!
The Sachertorte is all about the sponge!
使用错误的比例，它会变得非常干燥。
Use the wrong ratio, it becomes very dry.
过度烘烤，它会变得很干。
Over bake it, it becomes very dry.
这是关于理解你想用海绵达到什么目的。
It's about understanding what you're trying to achieve with this sponge.
然后移动到果酱。
Then move to the jam.
浓郁新鲜的杏味需要呈现出来。
The strong, fresh flavour of apricot needs to be present.
还有美味的黑巧克力甘纳许，
And there is the glorious dark chocolate ganache,
这样就结束了。
which will finish it off.
厨师掌握基本食谱的知识是非常重要的。
It's very important that the chef has the knowledge to execute the basic recipe.
我希望他们能做对。
I expect them to get it right.
不能犯任何错误。
No mistake should be made.
好了，我要开始用海绵了。
Right, I'm going to start working out the sponge.
好的。
OK.
评委们已经给了每个队他们需要的所有材料。
The judges have given each team all the ingredients they need...
把它们混合在一起，加入到甘纳许中。
We mix these together, and add that to our ganache.
不。
No.
. .但不是方法。
..but not the method.
这就像是一个技术问题，不是吗?
This is pretty much like a technical, isn't it?
差不多。今天有点像猜谜游戏。
Pretty much. It's a bit of a guessing game today.
我从来没试过。
See, I've never tried one.
比如，你知道会有什么样的口感吗，或者……
Like, do you know what to expect in terms of the texture, or...
不知道，我也不知道是怎么回事。
Not really, I don't know really know neither how it is.
我们都没试过。
None of us have actually tried one before.
R巧克力!你觉得秘方挑战怎么样?
R Chocolate! How do you feel about the secret recipe challenge?
感觉很好。你熟悉这个吗?
Feeling very good. Are you familiar with this?
是的，我去过维也纳的萨赫酒店……
Yeah, I've been to the Sacher Hotel in Vienna...
啊,哇!蛋糕的发源地，
Ah, wow! Where the cake originated,
所以我期待着做一些类似的东西。
so I'm looking forward to making something similar.
好吧，我们走着瞧。
OK, we shall see.
利亚姆:为了做出评委们想要的完美轻盈的海绵，
LIAM: In order to create the perfectly light sponge the judges are looking for,
厨师们必须精确地工作。
the chefs must work precisely.
我想先放个蛋黄，然后是面粉，最后再把它拌进蛋白霜里。
I was thinking a egg yolk, then the flour, then fold it into the meringue at the end.
太好了。自从我上次成功以来，我已经有了一个孩子。我生锈的。
Great. I've had a child since I last made it. I'm rusty.
如果顺序不对，它们的混合物就会变得太密，
Get the order wrong, and their mixture will become too dense,
海绵可能会塌陷。
and the sponge could collapse.
有一天，我在看食谱，
The other day, I was just looking through recipes,
我看到了沙赫托蛋糕，我就想，不，他们不会给我们这个的。
and I saw the Sachertorte, and I was like, no, they're not going to give us that.
我只是浏览了一下。
And I just flicked through it.
我希望我所做的是正确的。
I hope it's correct, what I'm doing.
我觉得我需要做一个双重食谱，
I feel like I need to do a double recipe,
因为这个量很小。
because the quantity's quite small.
所有的事情?不，不，我现在要加蛋白霜。
Everything done? No, no, I need to add the meringue now.
是的。是的。褶皱。是的。
Yes. Yes. Fold it. Yes.
这是海绵，可以吗?
Here's the sponge, is it OK?
我想是的。你是这么想的。
I think so. You think so.
烤一下就知道了。
Just bake it and see.
我想我要做一个双重食谱，我要试试。
I think I'm going to make a double recipe, I'm going to go for it.
看起来很乱。没关系。
It looks such a mess. It's OK.
好了，伙计，你觉得这混合物怎么样?是的，去吧。
All right, mate, what do you think of that mixture? Yeah, go for it.
我只希望海绵能达到评委们的期望。
I just hope that the sponge will be what the judges are expecting.
非常好，又轻又湿的海绵。
Really nice, light and moist sponge.
要做出完美的湿沙蛋糕…
To achieve a perfectly moist Sachertorte...
好了，我要进去了。
Right, I'm going in.
各队必须严格控制烘焙时间。
The teams must be exact with their baking time.
我们从15开始吧?然后再检查一下。
Let's start with 15? And then we'll check.
再过一分钟，他们的海绵就干了。
A minute over could leave their sponges dry.
没有犯错的余地。
There's no room for error.
你要做多久的蛋糕?
How long are you cooking the cakes for?
看。
Look.
本来是30分钟的，但是…哦，不，不，不，不。
It was supposed to be 30 minutes, but... Oh, no, no, no, no, no.
她忘了按计时器上的开始键。
She forgot to press start on the timer.
过半了，大厨们，过半了!
Halfway through, Chefs, halfway through!
我在做杏果酱。
I am doing the apricot jam.
我以前在匈牙利经常做果酱。
I used to make a lot of jam before in Hungary.
我们家乡的习俗是，我们有一整个冬天的储备。
Our custom back home was that we have reserves for the whole winter.
有一点压力。我不想失去WI的声誉。
There's a little bit of pressure. I don't want to lose the reputation of the WI.
不会做果酱。
Not being able to make jam.
是的,不是吗?要再来点柠檬汁吗?就碰一下。
Yes, no? Needs a little bit more lemon juice? Just a touch.
哔哔声。
BLEEP.
我想我在里面放了太多果酱。也许再加一些果泥进去。
I think I put too much jam on in. Maybe add some more puree then to it.
果酱很漂亮。哔哔
The jam is beautiful. BEEPING
那是你的计时器。是的!关键时刻到了。
That is your timer. Yes! The moment of truth.
我要打开它。
I'm going to open it.
来吧，我们开始吧。它的风险。
Go on, let's do it. Risk it.
是，不是，也许吧?是的，搞定了。是吗?
Yes, no, maybe? Yeah, it's done. Yeah?
斯拉夫人，这是干净的。
Slav, this is clean.
就这些吗?完美的。
That's it? Perfect.
伴侣……是吗?. .这是完成了。
Mate... Yeah? ..it's done.
嗯?海绵，我觉得太硬了。
Huh? The sponge, I think it's too hard.
我该怎么办，我该怎么办，我该怎么办?
What shall I do, what shall I do, what shall I do?
做一个新的。做一个新的。
Do a new one. Do a new one.
我只是不记得顺序了。
I just don't remember the order.
我做得不对，我还不知道是什么。
Something I'm not doing correctly, I don't know quite what it is yet.
煎饼吗?我们又来了。
Pancake? We're making it again.
你在做海绵，是吗?是的。
You're making your sponge, yeah? Yes.
大厨们，你们还有一个小时!那是一个小时!
Chefs, you have one hour left! That's one hour!
我做错了什么?
What am I doing wrong?
哦，别这样!
Oh, come on!
标准组件…
Standard components...
巧克力已经做好了。
The chocolate's set.
. .准备行动。
..ready for action.
是啊，还不错。
Yeah, not bad.
说实话，你知道这让我想起了什么吗?
Honestly, do you know what it reminds me of?
我明白你的意思。他笑了，走开。
I know what you mean. HE LAUGHS Go away.
现在他们的设计必须接受考验。
Now their designs must be put to the test.
现在我要开始组装支架了。
I'm now going to start assembling the stand.
好了，现在有点吓人了。
All right, scary bit now.
为了避免不可想象的事情……
To avoid the unthinkable...
只是为了确保蛋糕在上面，
Just to make sure the cake and stay on it,
并不是所有的东西都会崩溃。
and not everything will collapse.
. .每一个关节……
..every single joint...
哦!. .一定非常安全。
Oh! ..must be perfectly secure.
不。我要把它摘下来。
No. I'm taking it off.
海绵怎么样了?太浓了，太可怕了。
How's the sponge? Too dense, it's terrible.
我有些地方做得不对。
There's something I'm not doing right.
我的脑子一片空白，我该怎么办?
My mind is blank, what should I do?
这绝对是甘纳许和蛋白霜。
It's a ganache and meringue, definitely.
你有那么多钱吗?
Have you got that much?
是在正中间吗?我不知道，你告诉我。
Is it directly in the middle? I don't know, you tell me.
它不直……
It's not straight...
角。
The angle.
是的,不是吗?是的。我想是的。是的。
Yeah, no? Yeah. I think so. Yeah.
所以蛋糕也要直接放在上面吗?是的。
So, the cake's going directly on top, as well? Yeah.
你认为它会下降吗?不要……不!
Do you think it's going to drop? Don't... No!
不，它不会下降。因为你是建筑女神。
No, it's not going to drop. Because you're a structural goddess.
我做错了什么?快点，快点，集中精神。
What am I doing wrong? Come on, come on, concentrate.
冷静点，马希德，没事的。哦，我想起来了!
Calm down, Mashid, it's OK. Oh, I remember now!
怎么啦？把巧克力拌进去，然后…哦!
What? You fold in the chocolate, and then the... Oh!
从头再来。
Start all over again.
等等，你在做海绵?第三次了。怎么啦？怎么会？
Wait, you're making the sponge? For the third time. What? How come?
所以我第一次做的时候，它变得太稠密了。
So the first time I made it, it became too dense.
然后我又开始了，然后我记起了方法。
Then I started again, and then I remember the method.
这是第三次了，我希望你是幸运的。
So this is the third time, lucky, I hope.
大厨们，你们还有半个小时!
Chefs, you have half an hour left!
我们还有半个小时。来吧，马希德，我们走。
We have half an hour left. Come on, Mashid, let's go.
马希德的海绵才刚刚放进烤箱…
With Mashid's sponge only just in the oven...
我向上帝祈祷这能奏效。
I pray to God this will work.
. .其他队伍已经准备好开始分层了。
..the other teams are ready to begin layering.
最后，最重要的是巧克力甘纳许釉。
And for the final flourish, the all-important chocolate ganache glaze.
要有丝滑的口感非常重要。
It's very important to have a silky and smooth texture to this.
坚持是关键。巧克力和奶油的比例不对，
Consistency is key. Get the wrong ratio of chocolate and cream,
而且釉料太厚，倒不出来，容易裂开。
and the glaze will be too thick to pour and could split.
你相信我能搞定这个吗?伙计，我把生命托付给你。
Do you trust me to glaze this? Mate, I trust you with my life.
我认为……喜欢它，喜欢它，喜欢它。
I think... Like it, like it, like that.
这和我们通常烘焙的釉面很不一样。
This is a very different glaze to what we normally bake.
显然我不知道我们做得对不对。
And obviously I don't know if we made it right.
这个非常非常厚。我们不能有一个良好的流程。
This is very, very thick. We're not able to have a nice flow.
不要脱得太多，因为那样他们会看到层次感。
Don't take off too much, because then they will see the layers.
好了，准备好了吗?
All right, you ready?
它在中间。慢慢来。
It's in the middle. Take your time.
它不在中间。
It's not in the middle.
我再也不碰它了。不。没有?不，它要裂开了。好的。
I'm not touching it any longer. No. No? No, it's going to crack. OK.
准备好了吗?是的。
Ready? Yep.
好吗，好吗，好吗?
Are we good, are we good, are we good?
不。你真的是直接进入了哔哔声。
Nope. You've literally just gone straight into the BLEEP.
它很好。我们还有多长时间?
It's fine. How long have we got?
大厨们，你们还有15分钟!
Chefs, you have 15 minutes left!
加油，加油，加油。这需要尽快公布。
Come on, come on, come on. That needs to come out sooner.
你在干什么?我在做花的中心。
What are you doing? I'm doing the centre for the flower.
各队还需要制作精致的巧克力花……
The teams still have their delicate chocolate flower to cast...
巧克力在凝固，凝固，凝固。
Chocolate is setting, setting, setting.
. .完全用手。
..entirely by hand.
我的手是世界上最辣的，所以只要我一碰巧克力，
I have the world's hottest hands, so as soon as I touch chocolate,
它就这样……他们没那么糟糕!那里像不冷不热。
it just goes... They're not that bad! There like lukewarm.
你觉得呢?好的，谢谢你。
Do you think? OK, well, thank you.
这些叶子好薄啊，马什德。我希望这是正确的。
Oh, these leaves are so thin, Mashid. I hope this holds.
你没事吧?只是出了点小问题。
You all right? Just having a few little, snappy issues.
哦!我们只放一朵花在上面。
Oh! We're only going to have one flower on it.
因为我一转，花瓣就碎了。
Because the little petals are breaking as I was going around.
大厨们，你们还有五分钟。
Chefs, you have five minutes left.
哔哔声。
BLEEP.
怎么样?好。只是需要快速冷却。
How is it? Good. It just needs to cool down fast.
在爆炸中直接摇摆。
Rock it straight in the blast.
哔哔声!把它放下，放下，放下。
BLEEP! Just put it down, put it down, put it down.
哔哔声。
BLEEP.
请留在这里!待在这里，别动。
Please stay here! Stay here, don't move.
大厨们，你们还有一分钟，就一分钟!
Chefs, you have one minute left, that's one minute!
哔哔声。我需要工作。
BLEEP. I need to work.
让我们先做完，然后，如果我们有时间……
Let's finish first, and then, if we have time to do that...
不，不，不。准备好了吗?是的。
No, no, no, no. Ready? Yeah.
树叶,叶子。
Leaves, leaves.
我们需要给它上釉。压下去，压下去，压下去。
We need to glaze it. Push it down, push it down, push it down.
厨师……让我们移动它。你的时间到了!
Chefs... Let's move it. ..your time is up!
你的时间到此为止。
That is the end of your time.
我们可以做得更多。是啊，只是…海绵。
We could've done more. Yeah, it's just...the sponge.
它很好。如果交易中断，
It's fine. If it breaks in transaction,
它在事务中中断。
it breaks in transaction.
四个沙赫蛋糕和四个手工摊位
Four sachertortes and four handcrafted stands
现在面临着珍爱和伯努瓦的审判。
now face the judgment of Cherish and Benoit.
请皇家咖啡厅的Leanne和Romain过来好吗
Would Leanne and Romain from Hotel Cafe Royal please come forward
把你的沙赫蛋糕带到裁判桌上?
and bring your sachertortes to the judging table?
我喜欢整个结构。很不错。
I like the whole structure. It's quite nice.
我想你已经考虑过了。
I think you've thought about it.
小花，你正朝着我们想去的方向走，
The little flower, you were going in the direction we wanted to go,
但我想要更多，伙计们
but I wanted more, guys.
你说的上釉蛋糕是什么意思?
What do you understand when you say a glazed cake?
我会说它是被倒在蛋糕上的地方。
I would say it's where it's been poured on top of the cake.
我有一个涂有涂层的蛋糕，所以我不太确定这是否符合要求。
I have a coated cake, so I'm not too sure whether this met the brief.
我们要尝尝吗?
Should we taste?
这不是我记忆中的那个萨切尔了。
Well, this is not the sacher I remember.
海绵本身很干，果酱对我来说太酸了。
The sponge itself is quite dry, and the jam is too acidic for me.
你在杏酱里放什么东西了吗?
Did you put anything in your apricot jam?
柠檬皮。好吧，这就是我得到的。
Lemon zest. OK, well, that's what I got.
揉面时的柑橘味，
That citrusy flavour when you mix up the dough,
你都快脸红了。
you're almost going orangey.
你在创造别的东西。
You're creating something else.
我觉得我们不能把这个叫做沙赫蛋糕。不。
I don't think we can call this one quite a sachertorte. No.
但还是非常感谢你。谢谢你！
But thank you very much for that. Thank you.
老实说，情况可能会更糟。
Honestly, it could have been worse.
哦，天啊，天啊，天啊。
Oh, dear, oh, dear, oh, dear.
三个半小时，你就给我这个?
With three and a half hours, this is what you give me?
我对此很不高兴。不，我们也不是。
I'm not happy about it. No, neither are we.
首先，我们要求上釉，你给我上釉。
First of all, we asked for a glaze, you give me coat.
你觉得这够漂亮吗?
Do think this is beautiful enough?
说得够多了，我想是时候尝尝了。
Enough said, I think it's time to taste.
我认为有效的原因是海绵没有那么干
I think what works is the fact that the sponge is not as dry
这是可能的。
as it could be.
再说一次，我不认为这是沙赫蛋糕。
Again, I would not call this a sachertorte.
海绵里应该装满了巧克力……
The sponge is supposed to be full of chocolate...
我不明白。
I don't get it in there.
还有，我觉得你的巧克力酱裂开了。
And also, I think your ganache is split.
好的。好吧，明天总会有的。
OK. OK, there is always tomorrow.
是的。谢谢你！谢谢你！
Yes. Thank you. Thank you.
太有趣了!
That was fun!
R巧克力店的斯拉夫和玛丽亚，
Slav and Maria from R Chocolate,
请把你的沙赫蛋糕拿到裁判台来好吗?
could you please bring your sachertorte to the judging table?
小心，小心，小心。
Careful, careful, careful.
大厨，我喜欢你用的颜色，
Well, Chef, I love the way you used the colour,
红色和黄色，但作为一个整体，
the red and the yellow, but as a whole,
最后的收尾很笨拙。
the finishing is heavy-handed.
我以前看过你的一些巧克力作品，
I have seen some of your chocolate work before,
它更精致一些。
it was a little bit more refined.
但它的内部可能依然美丽。
But it may still be beautiful inside.
我有一些湿气，
I've got some kind of moisture,
我更喜欢蛋糕的巧克力味
and I prefer the sacher to taste a little bit more chocolate
而不是杏子，这是事实。
than apricots personally, which is the case.
至于我，我喜欢你的巧克力酱，
Well, as for me, I love your ganache,
它非常光滑和漂亮。
it's very smooth and nice.
好吧，总而言之，我们快到了。
OK, well, all in all, we're getting there.
它尝起来比看起来好。
It's tasting better than it looks.
谢谢你！谢谢大家。
Thank you. Thank you, guys.
来自WI烹饪学校的凯蒂和凯莉，
Katie and Kelly from The WI Cookery School,
请把你的沙赫蛋糕拿到裁判台来好吗?
could you please bring your Sachertorte to the judging table?
她喃喃自语的说了
SHE MUMBLES
哦!哦,不!
Oh! Oh, no!
你是认真的吗?
Are you serious?
解构wienerschnitzel”。
Deconstructed sachertorte.
这就是精神。
That's the spirit.
我很惊讶它是怎么站起来的
I was surprised how it got to stand
这么久了，说实话，但是，嘿!
for that long, to be honest with you, but, hey!
如果你想出这样的设计，
If you come up with a design like this one,
你对结构的理解还有待改进。
your understanding of structure is to be worked on.
对我来说海绵烤得很好。
The sponge to me is baked correctly.
你给蛋糕上了釉，效果就不一样了。
You glazed the cake, it makes a difference.
这果酱是我吃过的最好的，
The jam is the best I've tasted,
但是，看看这里的肿块和凸起。
however, look at the lumps and bumps over here.
如果你能好好执行
If you could have executed nicely,
这可能是一件很不错的作品。
this could be a very nice piece of work.
好的，非常感谢。
Well, thank you very much.
哔哔声。
BLEEP.
我们做了一个可口的沙赫蛋糕。
We made a sachertorte that was palatable.
如果我们出去，我们就出去，
If we go out, we go out,
但至少我们会大干一场。
but at least we'll go out with a bang.
绝对的。字面上。是的。
Absolutely. Literally. Yeah.
我们明天得努力工作，天啊。
We need to work hard tomorrow, my God.
我们今晚得好好谈谈，
We have to really sit down tonight,
谈谈我们的策略和计划。
talk about our strategy, our plan.
把我们的精力和一切都集中在明天的展览上，
Focus our energy, everything we have on the showpiece tomorrow,
希望这能帮我们渡过难关。
and then hopefully that will get us through.
汤姆:在明天的表演挑战之前，
TOM: Ahead of tomorrow's showpiece challenge,
各队有黄金时间准备元素
the teams have been given a golden hour to prepare elements
需要成型或放置过夜。
that need moulding or sitting overnight.
看着裁判，我觉得有点野蛮，
Looking at the judging, I thought it was a bit savage,
但这可能是公平的。
but it was probably fair.
我觉得这是一个灾难性的早晨。
I think it was a disastrous morning.
不是对候选人不敬
No disrespect of the candidates,
这是他们没有预料到的。
it was something they were not expecting to get.
那么，你觉得谁领先?
So, who do you think was in the lead?
可能是R巧克力，因为他们做了一个沙赫蛋糕
Potentially R Chocolate, because they've done a sachertorte
哪个吃起来更舒服。
which is more pleasant to eat.
谁有麻烦了?
And who is in trouble?
艾迪和马希德。
Eddie and Mahshid.
他们显然没有策略，
They clearly went without a strategy,
这就是他们的失败。
and that was their downfall.
你需要退后一步，你需要分析。
You need to stand back and you need to analyse.
那么，让我们来谈谈WI。在它坠落之前，是的，
So, let's talk about The WI. Before it fell, yeah,
我以为巧克力之神和他们在一起。
I thought the chocolate gods were with them.
老实说，他们一直否认这一点。
Let's be honest about it, they lived in denial that this would stand.
不是是否会发生，而是什么时候会发生。
It's not if, but when, this is happening.
我今天看不到他们眼中想要赢的火花。
I cannot see the spark in their eyes today that they want to win.
我希望他们明天能回来战斗。
I hope that they come back fighting tomorrow.
他们能做到吗?
Can they deliver?
希望球队明天能有更好的表现。
Let's just hope the teams have a better day tomorrow.
我相信他们能做到，
I'm sure that they can do it,
他们只需要把功率调大一点。
they just need to turn up the power a little bit.
早....
Morning.
汤姆:最后六强只剩下三个梦寐以求的名额了。
TOM: Just three coveted places in the final six remain.
利亚姆:这是两队最后的机会
LIAM: And this showpiece challenge is the last chance the teams
将不得不声明他们的主张。
will have to stake their claim.
评委们，你们对这个巧克力展示品有什么想法?
So, judges, what have you in mind for this chocolate showpiece?
它能兼作算盘吗?
Should it double as an abacus?
有一个有意识的灵魂?
Have a conscious soul?
吃之前能洗碗吗?
Be able to do the washing up before you eat it?
我们希望你能做一场精彩的表演，
We expect you to make a spectacular showpiece,
身高至少70厘米，灵感来自四季。
standing at least 70cm high and inspired by four seasons.
你的展品必须有特色
Your showpiece must feature
两种不同的模制巧克力，每种24颗，
two different types of moulded and filled chocolates, 24 of each,
你的展品还必须包括一个活动部件。
and your showpiece must also include a moving part.
厨师们，你们昨晚只有一个小时准备，你们有
Chefs, you had one hour last night to prepare, and you have
距离完成今天的挑战还有四小时。
four hours remaining to complete today's showpiece challenge.
你的时间从现在开始。
And your time starts now.
好了，准备好了吗?
Right, are you ready for this?
要想进入六强，
To earn a place in the final six,
各队必须用巧克力来证明他们的实力
the teams must prove their prowess with chocolate
通过让一个展示品栩栩如生地展现出当时的辉煌
by bringing to life a showpiece that captures the splendour
以及我们不断变化的自然世界的复杂性。
and complexity of our ever-changing natural world.
主题是四季，
So, the theme is four seasons,
他们想怎么解释都可以，
and they can interpret it whatever way they want,
但这是一个展示性的挑战，我们想要被惊艳到。
but it's a showpiece challenge, we want to be wowed.
还会有更多的。
There's going to be some more.
他们展示了不同的技术技能，
They showcase different technical skill,
比如造型、手工制作、雕刻。
like moulding, handcrafting, sculpturing.
我们还增加了一个活动部件。
And we have added a moving part.
它可以像一个小抽屉一样简单，也可以更有技术含量，
It could be as simple as a little drawer or more technical,
你在某处有个小马达。
and you've got a little motor somewhere.
为了配合他们的季节性表演，
To accompany their seasonal showpieces,
参赛队伍还必须生产48颗丰盛的糖果。
the teams must also produce 48 sumptuous bonbons.
蛋壳必须做得很薄，
The shell has to be thinly made,
当我掰开巧克力的时候，它就会啪的一声。
and when I break the chocolate, it should snap.
馅料要光滑，要有味道
The filling needs to be smooth and the flavour provided show to us
你了解自己的口味。
that you understand your taste.
我们想看看他们有多强才能成为最好的三支球队
We want to see how good they are in order to be the best three teams
进入下一轮。
to go to the next round.
巧克力一直是我喜欢的东西。
It's always something I've enjoyed, chocolate.
我喜欢有创意，你知道，
I like to be creative and, you know,
这基本上就像雕刻一件艺术品。
this is like carving a piece of art, basically.
而球队可以自由地代表多个赛季
While the teams are free to represent as many seasons
随他们的便，琳恩和罗曼
as they like, Leanne and Romain
把所有的精力都集中在一件事上。
are concentrating all their efforts on just one.
所以你今天打算谨慎行事吗?
So you are going to play safe today?
这不是在保守行事。
It's not playing it safe.
我们正在尝试做更多的技巧。
We're trying to do more finesse.
我们要去春天。
We're going for spring.
我们会有一些不错的，比如，
We're going to have some nice, like,
那里有向日葵，还有大黄蜂。
sunflowers on there, and bumblebees.
我们将有一个会移动的蜂巢。
We're going to have a beehive that will move.
利亚姆:通过制作一套充满覆盆子和柚子的糖果
LIAM: By crafting one set of bonbons filled with zesty raspberry and yuzu
另一种则含有鲜橙和肉桂，
and another containing zingy orange and cinnamon,
他们还希望用自己的口味来捕捉春天
they also hope to capture spring with their flavours
还有他们的设计。
as well as their design.
色彩鲜艳,春天吗?
Colourful, spring?
绿色和黄色。
Green and yellow.
因为一开始我们想的是秋天，
Because at the beginning we were thinking about autumn,
只剩下棕色的叶子之类的东西，
just going to be brown leaves and stuff like that,
我想这并不是很愉快。
which is not very enjoyable, I guess.
艾迪和马希德不这么认为。
A point of view not shared by Eddie and Mahshid.
我们选择了一个秋天的主题。
We chose an autumn theme.
我们想专注于一个赛季，并为你们做得很好。
We wanted to focus on one season and do it nicely for you guys.
我去收集真树叶。
I went and collected real leaves, yeah.
哇!哇!
Wow! Wow!
啊，好的，很好。所以他们会下真正的雨
Ah, OK, nice. So they're going to have the real rain
还有结构。
and the structure on.
汤姆:希望把昨天抛在脑后，
TOM: Hoping to put yesterday behind them,
萨沃伊人会在他们的树下
the Savoy will place under their tree
绿色和白色斑点的黑巧克力
green and white flecked dark chocolates
用结晶的开心果和开心果甘纳许，
with crystallised pistachios and pistachio ganache,
还有金色的牛奶巧克力圆顶
along with gold milk chocolate domes
柚子和杜松子酒。
featuring grapefruit and gin fillings.
给我们介绍一下你的活动部件。所以，在树干里面
Take us through your moving part. So, inside the tree trunk
我们要做一些抽屉，
we're going to make some drawers,
里面也会装满我们的糖果。好的。
and they'll be filled with our bonbons inside there, as well. OK.
你酷吗?
You cool?
必须是。
Have to be.
我们很乐意成为这次巧克力挑战的国王和王后。
We would love to be the king and the queen of this chocolate challenge.
相信他们的经验会给他们带来优势，
Convinced their experience will give them the edge,
巧克力专家斯拉芙和玛利亚不仅要出演一季，
chocolate specialists Slav and Maria are taking on not just one season,
但是四个都是。
but all four.
我们要做一个有四根树枝的树。
We're going to make a tree which will have four branches.
每个分支代表一个季节。有很多事情要做，
Each branch will represent one season. It's quite a lot to do,
所以我认为我们需要努力工作。
so we need to work hard, I think.
白巧克力夹心糖果上点缀着咖啡和爱尔兰奶油
White chocolate bonbons flecked with coffee and filled with Irish cream
而意式脆饼会配上黑巧克力，由
and biscotti will be accompanied by dark chocolates comprised of
百香果焦糖和覆盆子甘纳许。
passion fruit caramel and raspberry ganache.
好的，那你的活动部分呢?
OK, what about your moving part?
我们将有一个秋千。
We're going to have a swing.
一个什么?摇摆。秋千，秋千。
A what? Swing. A swing, swing.
是的。秋千上的东西?
Yeah. Something on the swing?
我要试着做一只鸟。
I will try to make a bird.
一只鸟。是的。一只在秋千上的鸟。
A bird. Yeah. A bird on a swing.
为什么不呢?
Why not?
只是内心充满了愤怒。
Just have such a rage inside.
试图从昨天的迫降中恢复过来，
Trying to recover from their crash landing yesterday,
WI烹饪学校的凯利和凯蒂也是
The WI Cookery School's Kelly and Katie are also
尝试所有的四季。
attempting all four seasons.
如果这还不够，
And if that wasn't enough,
它们将整合多个活动部件。
they will be incorporating multiple moving parts.
我们有两种机制，
We've got two mechanisms that we're going to be doing,
在冬天，我们有一条传送带，
so in the winter part we've got a conveyor belt,
所以我们要在上面放一些巧克力，
so we'll pop some of our chocolates on it,
它们会旋转。
and they're going to be rotating through.
传送带?是的。
A conveyor belt? Yeah.
有趣,有趣。现在我们来谈谈。是啊!
Interesting, interesting. Now we are talking. Yeah!
它是如何供电的?
How is it going to be powered?
所以这是一个马达，机动机械。
So it's a motor, motorised mechanism.
我不得不拆了一辆儿童遥控车。
I had to cannibalise a sort of children's remote-control car.
这是邪恶的。
That is wicked.
他们还计划用他们的糖果开辟一条道路
They also plan to blaze a trail with their bonbons -
黑巧克力味噌焦糖山核桃佛罗伦萨
dark chocolate miso caramel pecan Florentines
还有杏蜜百里香甘纳许牛奶巧克力
and apricot and honey thyme ganache milk chocolates
在他们宏伟建筑的底部呼啸而过。
whizzing around the base of their grand structure.
我们的展品是一棵树。
Our showpiece is going to be a tree.
你要怎么让这棵树看起来像真的树?
How you going to make the tree look like a real tree?
凯蒂将负责所有从顶部伸出来的树枝，
Katie is going to be working on all the branches coming out of the top,
她要手工制作。
which she's going to be hand moulding.
然后我们沿着它走下去
And we're going to then go down it
用笔触营造出粗糙树皮的效果。
with brushstrokes to give that affect of rough bark.
我们知道还有另外两棵树。
We know that there's two other trees being made.
所以这将是一场战斗。是的。
So it's going to be a fight. Yeah.
厨师们，你们已经有一个小时了，所以还剩下三个小时。
Chefs, you've had an hour, so that's three hours left.
它很快就消失了。
It's gone very, very quickly.
现在我要开始做糖果了。
So now I am going to start the bonbons.
精致的优雅是高端糖果的标志。
Finely tuned elegance is the hallmark of high-end bonbons.
这个是开心果。
This one's going to be pistachio.
我会在里面铺上巧克力，放上馅料，然后盖上盖子。
I will line it with chocolate, put the filling, and then cap them.
首先，他们必须抛出他们的箱子，箱子应该薄如游丝。
First, they must cast their cases, which should be gossamer thin.
这是一个非常关键的部分，为了得到美味的糖果。
This is a very crucial part, to get the nice bonbon.
已经落山了，这里太冷了。
It's already setting, it's so cold in here.
不过不会太厚，对吧?不。没有?
Not too thick, though, are they? No. No?
但如果见效不够快，
But if they don't work fast enough,
迅速冷却的巧克力在模具里会凝固得太厚。
the rapidly cooling chocolate will set too thick in the mould.
我对这些壳不满意。
I'm not happy with these shells.
我觉得这些都没用。
I don't think we can use any of these.
这不是我们想要的。
This is not what we want.
我们只需要重做一遍，但这让我退缩了。
We just have to redo it again, but it's set me back.
因为你要打磨模具，
Because then you have to polish the mould,
一切都得重新开始。
everything has to start all over again.
这是黑巧克力的外壳。
This is our shell for the dark chocolate.
我对此很满意，
I'm happy with it,
现在我要往里面填上焦糖。
so now I'm going to start filling them up with the caramel.
除了精致的贝壳，
As well as delicately-cast shells,
他们必须巧妙地制作馅料。
they must create fillings with finesse.
肉馅饺子出来了。
Cantuccini is coming out.
平衡天堂般的质地和令人垂涎的味道。
Balancing heavenly textures and mouthwatering flavours.
我觉得所有的味道都很不错。
I think all the flavours are quite nice.
覆盆子和柚子清新如春，
Raspberry and yuzu is fresh, like spring,
我们还有橘子和肉桂，味道更热一些。
and we have orange and cinnamon, it's a bit more warm.
让我们来看看评委们是怎么说的。
Let's see what the judges say.
再加点百里香，还是闻不出来。
Got some more thyme in there, I still can't get the smell.
真的吗?我们用一些非常香的百里香来练习，
Really? We had some very fragrant thyme that we practised with,
这不是很香。不。
and this is not so fragrant. No.
我在做覆盆子巧克力酱，
I'm piping raspberry ganache,
把它放在焦糖百香果上面。
which is going to sit on top of passion fruit of caramel.
先是甜的，然后是酸的。
It's sweet and then sour.
开心果是世界上最好的开心果，当然产自伊朗。
Pistachios are finest pistachios in the world, from Iran, of course.
当他们咬进去的时候，那不是巧克力酱，
When they bite into it, it's just not ganache,
它们也会有一些嘎吱声。
they're going to have some crunch as well.
马希德，你还没在里面放巧克力呢。
Mahshid, you haven't even lined it with chocolate yet.
至少放点巧克力进去吧。是的。
At least put chocolate in it. Yeah.
所以，我只是盖上松露。
So, I'm just capping the truffles.
然后我们就可以吃柠檬了
So then we can just have, like, lemons
下面是柑橘类水果。
and, like, citrus fruits at the bottom.
糖果密封……
Bonbons sealed...
他们看起来不错。
They are looking good.
. .和设置…在冰箱里。
..and setting... In the fridge.
是时候在黄金时刻发现昨天的辛勤工作了
It's time to discover if yesterday's hard work in the golden hour
有了回报。
has paid off.
这是怎么回事?哦，看起来真漂亮。
How's that? Oh, that looks beautiful.
哪儿也不动。
Not moving anywhere.
恰到好处，恰到好处。
Properly set, properly.
可能是脆弱的。
Can be fragile.
隔夜冷却收缩的巧克力……
Chocolate that's cooled and contracted overnight...
哎呀!
Whoops!
. .是非常微妙的。
..is extremely delicate.
它不会破裂。幸运的是我昨天做了一个备用的，
It cannot crack. Luckily I did a spare one yesterday,
我觉得这是件好事。
I think it was a good thing.
我试着把积木移开，
I'm trying to remove the blocks,
不要认为他们会以某种方式出来。
don't think they're going to come out somehow.
巧克力需要热一下。
The chocolate needs to warm up a bit.
哔哔声。
BLEEP.
是的。哔哔声。
Yeah. BLEEP.
他们的活动部件牢牢地卡住了……
With their moving part firmly stuck...
这是目前可能发生的最糟糕的事情。
It's just the worst thing that could happen right now.
我的天啊。
Oh, my God.
. .艾迪和马希德又落后了。
..Eddie and Mahshid have fallen behind again.
这是一场噩梦。
This is a nightmare.
大厨们，你们还有两个小时!两个小时!
Chefs, you have two hours left! Two hours!
发出哔哔声
BLEEPING
我们要尽快开始组装零件。
As soon as possible, we're going to start to assemble the piece.
这件事越早越好。
The earlier the better on this one.
虽然大多数球队都开始带来他们的四季秀
While most teams are starting to bring their Four Seasons showpieces
在一起…
together...
看起来怎么样?美丽的,伴侣。
How's that looking? Beautiful, mate.
. .埃迪和马希德失去了宝贵的时间
..Eddie and Mahshid have lost valuable time
挣扎在破碎的树干上
struggling with their cracked tree trunk.
我不希望我最大的敌人也这样。
I wouldn't wish this on my worst enemy.
我们在萨沃伊的朋友，他们倾尽全力
Our friends at the Savoy - they're throwing everything
他们已经完成了他们的示范挑战，
they've got at their showpiece challenge and,
嗯，他们最好是!
er, they better be!
埃迪挣扎着把抽屉拿出来，他们可能会发现
Eddie struggled to extract those drawers and they may be finding
他们自己其实有麻烦。
themselves actually in trouble.
我们可以纠正这一点。
We can rectify this.
我真的没有选择。我们必须能够做到这一点。
Don't really have a choice. We've got to be able to do it.
我们来自WI的女士们…
Our ladies from the WI...
它们在一棵树上有四季。我是说，这很有趣。
They've four seasons in one tree. I mean, it's interesting.
我喜欢传送带的想法，
I like the conveyor belt idea,
但他们真的能实现吗?
but could they actually bring it to fruition?
是的。我们不知道。
Yeah. We don't know.
琳恩和罗曼。
Leanne and Romain.
他们在春天工作，他们会带着小蜜蜂和蜂箱来。
They're working with spring and they are going to bring the little bees with the beehives.
哦，我喜欢!Bzzz !
Oh, I like that! Bzzz!
我们保存了它。而且，一旦这一切都安排好了，
We saved it. And besides, once this is all set around here,
然后它会在外面形成结构，然后就没有了
then it'll give it that structure on the outside and there won't be any
更多的错误。
more faults.
我们只能全速工作了。
We'll just have to work at full speed.
大厨们，你们还有一个小时。一个小时。
Chefs, you have one hour left. One hour.
它是碱。它必须支撑其他所有人的重量，
It's the base. It'll have to support the weight of all the rest,
所以它必须足够坚固。
so it needs to be strong enough.
我在上面打了些小结，让树皮看起来更粗糙。
I've carved little knots out, just to give that effect of rough bark.
现在不像电线杆了。
Less like a telegraph pole now.
凯莉，你能处理这个吗?我来搞定。
Kelly, can you handle this? I've got this.
我觉得你处理不了……
I don't think you can handle this...
不，我觉得你能处理好!
No, I do think you can handle this!
为他们的四季展示品注入活力……
Breathing life into their Four Seasons showpieces...
我们使用管道滞后来创建分支。
We're using pipe lagging to create branches.
它撑不住的。这个撑不住。
It won't hold. This one won't hold.
那很好……将取决于他们精确繁殖的能力吗
That's fine. ..will rest on their ability to accurately reproduce
自然界的颜色和纹理。
the colours and textures found in nature.
花是我最担心的事。
The flower's the thing that's worrying me the most.
我们想证明我们可以做到，而且它们看起来很漂亮。
We want to show that we can do them and they do look nice.
这些花看起来很漂亮，各位!
These flowers look beautiful, everyone!
他们也很危险地靠近边缘——我只是想说。
They're also precariously near the edge - I'm just going to say that.
花在边上。它在边缘。
The flowers are on the edge. It's on the edge.
我觉得罗曼也是这样。
I feel like that's the way Romain is as well.
一旦它凝固，你可以很容易地取出真正的叶子。
Once it sets, you can easily remove the actual leaf.
剩下的是叶子的背面，它会给巧克力带来很好的效果。
You're left with the back side of the leaf and it gives a nice effect on the chocolate.
该死的你!
Damn you!
这些花不开花。哔哔声!
These blossoms aren't working. BLEEP this!
我可能会暂时忘记这些。
I might just forget about these for a minute.
大厨们，你们还有30分钟。
Chefs, you have 30 minutes left.
唷!
Phew!
现在我在制作冬天。我觉得我有点紧张，
Now I'm making winter. I think I'm a bit stressed,
因为我们有很多元素要完成。
because we have so many elements to complete.
哦,哔哔声!
Oh, BLEEP!
来吧!
Come on!
你会掉下去吗?嗯?
Are you going to fall? Huh?
不，我在跟这个说话。
No, I was talking to this.
艾迪，你的围裙真棒!
Eddie, great apron!
哔哔声!
BLEEP!
我想我们需要给它涂上一层。否则，它看起来会很奇怪。那么，一切都是绿色的吗?
I think we're going to need to coat it. Otherwise, it's going to look odd. Everything green, then?
好吧，但是请保留……最后是黑色的?最后是黑色。
OK, but just keep the... The end black? The end black.
大厨们，你们还有十分钟。
Chefs, you have ten minutes left.
那是十分钟。
That's ten minutes.
哔哔声!
BLEEP!
不!温柔。这就是为什么我们要温柔。
No! Gentle. This is why we have to be gentle.
哔哔声的缘故!我正在荡秋千，
BLEEP sake! I'm doing the swing now,
也就是我们的移动物体。
which is going to be our moving object.
我没有时间去执行我原来的计划。
I don't have the time to execute what I originally planned.
啊!
Ah!
蜂巢一直在响。
The beehive keeps cracking.
它没有像我们希望的那样平滑地融合在一起。
It's not coming together as smooth as we wanted it to.
我们会有办法的。
We'll manage something.
我很担心这个秋千。小心，它在撕裂。
I'm worried about this swing. Careful, it's ripping there.
哎呀!
Whoops!
报警哔哔声
ALARM BEEPS
等待,等待。先把刀刃戴上。
Wait, wait. Put the edge on first.
温柔。
Gentle.
没关系。
That's OK.
大厨们，你们还有五分钟。
Chefs, you have five minutes left.
那是五分钟。
That's five minutes.
瞧!
Voila!
我对这些照片出来的方式不满意，
I'm not happy with the way that these ones have come out,
但我们没有足够的时间重做。
but we don't have enough time to redo.
看看这些坏男孩!
Look at them bad boys!
把它剪掉。
Just cut it.
春天的草。
Spring grass.
我要把巧克力上面的坚果拧开。
I'm just going to nut the top of the chocolates.
我想我现在没有足够的时间做这件事，但我会努力的。
I don't think I have enough time to do this now, but I will try.
就是这样。好了，我的传送带坏了。
That's it. Right, my conveyor belt, it's not working.
哦,哔哔声!是土壤的问题，是齿轮的问题。
Oh, BLEEP! It's the soil, yeah, it's in the cogs.
只要快点把抽屉收拾好就行了。
Just got to do these drawers quick and that's it.
错误的大小。
Wrong size.
哔哔声!你能用巧克力再做一条吗，
BLEEP! Can you make another strip with the chocolate,
接下来我们可以剪另一个抽屉吗?
so we can cut the other drawer next?
哔哔声!两条巧克力。
BLEEP! Two strips of chocolate.
大厨们，你们有一分钟的时间完成你们的表演。
Chefs, you have one minute to complete your Showpieces.
给我喷雾。
Give me the spray.
有东西咔哒一声响了。
Something just went click.
哦，好了。它看起来像哔哔声，但它是某种东西。
Oh, there we go. It's going to look like BLEEP, but it's something.
至少看看能不能在里面放一个抽屉。
At least see if we can get one drawer in there.
只要合适就行。不适合那里。
As long as it fits. Not fitting in there.
哔哔声!要我帮你吗?
BLEEP! Do you want me to give you a hand?
事实上，不，我很好。你是好吗?是的，我知道了。
Actually, no, I'm good. You're good? Yeah, I've got this.
时间到了，大厨们!
Time's up, chefs!
Showpiece的挑战到此结束。
That is the end of the Showpiece challenge.
做得好!嘿，过来，我们做得很好。
Well done! Hey, come here, we've done all right.
你成功了吗?
Did you manage?
它很好。很好。做得很好。
It's nice. It's good. Well done.
哔哔声!看看其他人的。
BLEEP! Look at everybody else's.
我的天啊!
Oh, my God!
如此美丽。我真的很喜欢这个绿色的。
So beautiful. I really like this green one.
是的。他们的树太美了!我喜欢他们的树。
Yeah. Their tree is BLEEP beautiful! I like their tree.
它甚至比我们在实践中做的还要好。
It's even better than what we did in practice.
我想说，我们的看起来太酷了!
Can I just say, ours looks so damn cool!
他们笑了
THEY LAUGH
四个非凡的四季展示在短短五个小时内完成。
Four extraordinary Four Seasons Showpieces made in just five hours.
但是谁做了足够的努力来赢得他们在6强中的位置呢?
But who has done enough to earn their place in the final six?
建筑本身看起来非常优雅。
The structure itself looks really elegant.
你的花很漂亮
Your flower is very pretty
你的蜜蜂给你的展览带来了一点活力。
and your bee bring a little bit life into your Showpiece.
这对我来说很神奇。我觉得你已经搞定了。
It's very magical for me. I think you've nailed this one.
你交付的东西在视觉上很吸引人
You've delivered something which is visually attractive
和平衡。
and well-balanced.
但是，就在中间，你有橡皮筋，
But, right in the middle, you've got the elastic band,
这对你的演讲有点不利。
which is defeating a little bit your presentation.
不过，还不错。
But, not bad.
巧克力呢?
What about the chocolates?
我真的很喜欢你对细节的关注
I really like the attention to detail
它完成得非常整齐。
and it's very neatly finished.
我们有白巧克力、覆盆子和柚子。
We have a white chocolate, raspberry and yuzu.
我喜欢你做的巧克力的口感。
I like the texture of your chocolate.
我觉得柚子比覆盆子更有味道。
I feel the yuzu more than the raspberry.
这里需要覆盆子吗?不太确定。
Is the raspberry needed here? Not too sure.
当我品尝这个的时候，没有什么能让我兴奋的，
When I taste this, there's nothing to excite me,
这只是一种质地。
it's just one texture.
再提醒我一遍，里面是什么?
Remind me again, what's in there?
橘子和肉桂。你的甘那许完全是颗粒状的。
Orange and cinnamon. Your ganache is completely grainy.
我甚至都不想尝是否有橙子，这让我很反感。
I don't even want to taste whether there's orange, it just put me off.
所以我希望你在饮食元素上多下点功夫。
So I'd like you to put more effort into the eating element.
谢谢你！谢谢你！
Thank you. Thank you.
是我的错，琳恩，对不起!
It's my fault, Leanne, I'm sorry!
又是巧克力酱。
It was the ganache again.
我感觉到了秋天，一些漂亮的小树叶。
I feel the autumn, some nice little leaves.
你给我们展示一些技术。
You show us some technical skill.
然而，我认为它不优雅，不适合我。
However, I think it's not elegant, it's not well done for me.
我们要的是一个活动部件。
We were asking for a moving part.
把它拿出来，里面还有一些糖果。
This comes out and you've got a couple more bonbons inside there.
啊，真感人。是的。
Ah, that's moving. Yeah.
那个洞里是不是还有一个移动的部件?
Was there meant to be another moving part in that hole as well?
是的，但我最后一刻弄坏了一个。
Yes, but I broke one last minute.
所以这是一个。这是一个小鸟巢。
So instead this is a... It's a little bird's nest.
这是一个小鸟巢，啊!我们来尝尝吧?
It's a little bird's nest, ah! Shall we taste?
红色的是柚子果酱
So the red one is grapefruit marmalade
还有葡萄柚和杜松子酱。
and grapefruit and gin ganache.
从视觉上看，我觉得很不错，
Visually, I think that it's quite nice,
但是，我觉得巧克力太浓了。
however, I think the chocolate is too thick.
杜松子酒在巧克力酱里?
The gin is in the ganache?
是的。我只得到柚子。
Yes. I get only the grapefruit.
好的，那另一个呢?
OK, what about the other one?
绿色的是开心果甘纳许，里面有结晶的开心果。
The green one is pistachio ganache with crystallised pistachios inside.
这是一种很好的巧克力。
It's a nice chocolate.
开心果的味道还在。
The pistachio flavour is present.
我也很喜欢你的坚果结晶，
I really like you crystallised your nuts as well,
这是一个不同的维度。
and this give a different dimension.
所以在两个夹心之间，有很好的电位。
So between the two bonbons, good potential.
嗯,是的。
Mmm, yes.
干得好，伙计们。
Well done, guys.
很好。嗯。
It's good. Mmm.
我现在只想哭。
I just wanna cry now.
从视觉上看，我觉得它很停滞。
Visually, it looks very stagnant to me.
没有运动，没有曲线，没有生命。
There's no movement, there's no curve, there's no life in there.
我还希望你在收尾的时候更有技巧呢。
I was hoping that you'd have more finesse in the finishing touch.
活动部分在哪里?
Where is the moving part?
运动的部分在这里。
The moving part is here.
笑声
LAUGHTER
你必须做得更好!
You have to do better than that!
Showpieces只是缺少一点专业技能。
The Showpieces is just lacking a bit of the professional skills.
我们想多看一点。
We want to see a bit more.
小心你的手指。
Careful, your finger.
我们这里有一个白巧克力外壳，
So we have a white chocolate shell here,
还有磨碎的咖啡和爱尔兰奶油甘纳许，还有意式脆饼。
with grinded coffee and Irish cream ganache, and there is biscotti.
最美妙的是你加入了一些磨碎的咖啡
The most beautiful thing is that you incorporate some of grounded coffee
放进你的白巧克力里。
into your white chocolate.
非常漂亮，味道非常棒，
It's absolutely beautiful, the flavour profile is stunning,
但如果你拿出一个有这么厚外壳的糖果，
but if you present a bonbon which has a shell that thick,
乐趣消失了，是吗?
the pleasure is going, yeah?
这个怎么样?百香果焦糖，
What about this one? Passion fruit caramel,
黑巧克力和覆盆子甘纳许。
dark chocolate and raspberry ganache.
味道很浓，很干净。
Flavours really strong, really clean.
我会选择把覆盆子和百香果放在一起吗?
Would I have chosen to put raspberry and passion fruit together?
不。我本可以好好享受的
No. I could have enjoyed it beautifully
只要你的激情焦糖。
just on your passion caramel.
是啊，就像你把两个不同的糖果放在一起。是的。
Yeah, it's like you've got two different bonbons in one. Yeah.
他叹了口气
HE SIGHS
四季在哪里?我在上面只能看到两个季节。
Where is the four seasons? I only can see two seasons up there.
上面只有两个，我们没有时间做另一边。
There's only two up there, we didn't get time to do the other side.
所以它还没完成?
So it's unfinished?
我觉得对我来说有点裸露。
I think it's a little bit bare for me.
里面没有生命。
There is no life in it.
它基本上是一根杆子，上面覆盖着巧克力，
It's a pole, basically, covered with chocolate,
我们不要拐弯抹角了。
let's not beat around the bush.
请带我们去看你们的活动部件好吗?
Could you please take us to your moving parts?
这里有传送带，
So we've got the conveyor belt here,
然后我们在弹簧部分也有转盘。
and then we've also got the turntable in the spring section.
我真的很喜欢这个小家伙。
I really enjoy that little fellow here.
向上、向下。你这样看——砰!
Up, down. You see like that - bop!
哦，他走了。就像……
Oh, he's gone. It's almost like...
防喷器!这是一种努力，你们已经想过了。
Bop! There is an effort, you guys have thought about it.
那么我们可爱的巧克力都有哪些口味呢?
So what kind of flavours do we have in our lovely chocolates?
我们准备了杏果胶，
We've got an apricot gel,
蜂窝状的蜂巢和蜂蜜加百里香的甘纳许。
a clustered honeycomb and a honey and thyme-infused ganache.
好的，从视觉上看，巧克力不是很好调和的，
OK, visually, that chocolate is not well-tempered,
我可以看到这里有很多点。
I can see lots of dots over here.
我喜欢它的质地。
One thing I like here is the texture.
我非常非常喜欢这个蜂巢酥。
That honeycomb crumble I really, really love.
这里有可能做出美味的巧克力
There's potential to do a nice chocolate here
但现在还没有。下一个?
but it's not there yet. Next one?
味噌焦糖，我们还做了佛罗伦萨山核桃。
Miso caramel, and we've also made a pecan Florentine in there.
小心你的手指!选角比补牙更重要。
Careful your fingers! Your casting is more than your filling.
我很难尝出味噌的味道。
I'm struggling to taste the miso.
一切对我来说都不平衡。
Everything just doesn't balance up for me.
你今天已经尽力了
You've done what you could today,
让我们看看这是否足够让你进入下一轮。
let's see if it's enough to take you through the next round.
也许我们应该只拍一季。
Perhaps we should have just done one season.
根据他们在两项挑战中的表现，
Based on their performance across both challenges,
评委们将对参赛队伍进行排名，
the judges will now rank the teams,
只有前三名才能进入六强。
and only the top three will take their place in the final six.
颜色很漂亮，不是吗?是的，你能感受到这首曲子的能量。
Nice colour, isn't it? Yeah, you can feel the energy in the piece.
我们对他们的评论非常满意。
We're actually really happy with their comments.
他们很喜欢我们的巧克力，
They really liked our chocolates,
尽管糖果不是最好的。
even though the bonbon was not the best.
这里……我们希望能走得更远，
And here... We would like to go as far as we can,
但我觉得我们的表演……
but I don't feel like our performance...
是的。. .就是这么高的标准。
Yeah. ..was that high standard.
我们对我们创造的最终结果不是特别满意，
We weren't particularly happy with the end result of what we created,
巧克力，我想大家都知道，
and chocolate, I think everybody knows now,
不是我的强项!
is not my strongest point!
凌乱…你绝对不想参加一场失败的比赛。
It's untidy... You never want to enter a competition to fail.
我们努力工作，度过了许多不眠之夜。
We worked so hard, we have had so many sleepless nights.
我们很乐意经历并展示我们是什么做的
We would love to go through and show what we're made of
展示更多我们能做的事情。
and show a bit more of what we can do.
Benoit和珍惜已经做出了决定。
Benoit and Cherish have made their decision.
第一名的队伍展示了非凡的技术
The team in first place showed exceptional technique
在他们的视觉上引人注目的展示。
on their visually striking Showpiece.
恭喜你……
Congratulations...
皇家咖啡厅的Leanne和Romain。
Leanne and Romain from Hotel Cafe Royal.
你们进入了比赛的最后阶段。哇!
You are through to the final stages of the competition. Woo!
第二名是R巧克力公司的斯拉夫和玛丽亚。
In second place are Slav and Maria from R Chocolate.
恭喜你，我们也会再见到你。
Congratulations, we'll also see you again.
那就剩下WI烹饪学校的凯莉和凯蒂了
Which leaves Kelly and Katie from the WI Cookery School
还有萨沃伊的艾迪和马希德。
and Eddie and Mashid from the Savoy.
经过深思熟虑，
After much deliberation,
伯努瓦和珍爱同意了
Benoit and Cherish agreed
今晚要退出比赛的队伍是…
that the team who'll be leaving the competition tonight is...
. .凯莉和凯蒂。
..Kelly and Katie.
我想我们已经为自己感到骄傲了。
I think we've done ourselves proud.
我为我们所做的一切感到无比自豪。
I'm incredibly proud of what we've done.
对不起!哦，不，不用，没事的。
Sorry! Oh, no, don't be, it's fine.
这是一个非常积极的过程，不是吗?
It's just been such a positive process, hasn't it?
它有。我们曾经是朋友，现在是最好的朋友。
It has. We were mates, we're now best mates.
是啊，我们现在是闺蜜了。所以你还想要什么?
Yeah, we are besties now. So what more can you want?
说法语
SPEAKS FRENCH
做得很好。我们是第一!
Well done. We are first!
我们很高兴。
We are so happy.
我们打败了萨沃伊!我们打败了萨沃伊，对，一周快乐。
And we've beaten Savoy! We beat the Savoy, yeah, happy week.
我喜欢你的幽默……
I like your humour...
在这场比赛中前进是一种奇妙的感觉。
To go forward in this competition is an amazing feeling.
我们会遇到新的朋友，新的竞争对手。
We will meet the new friends, new competitors.
今晚先庆祝一下，然后继续工作。
Quick celebration tonight, and then back to work.
明天回去上班!
Back to work tomorrow!
下次，空气中弥漫着爱。
Next time, love is in the air.
你想把早餐放在床上，是吗?
You want the breakfast in the bed, yeah?
你是说就我们俩吗?
You mean just the two of us?
但有人会羡慕维也纳音乐界的维纳斯吗?
But will anyone wow the Venus of Viennoiserie?
天哪，你能听到吗?
CRACKING Oh, my goodness, can you hear that?
在全糖秀品中闪耀?
And shine in an all-sugar Showpiece?
哪五支球队能进入四分之一决赛?
Which five teams will make it to the quarterfinal...
好了，我们走吧……谁的心会破碎?
Right, let's move. ..and whose hearts will be broken?
它在倾斜，不是吗?
It is leaning, isn't it?
哦，不!
CRASH Oh, no!
字幕由红蜂传媒制作
Subtitles by Red Bee Media
今天真是令人兴奋的一天
It's a super exciting day today
因为每轮预赛的前三名
because the top three teams from each set of heats
将彼此第一次见面，组成最后的六强
will be meeting each other for the first time to form the final six -
这周是浪漫周。
and this week is romance week.
喘气:哦，我的天哪!利亚姆，你觉得他们会坠入爱河吗!
GASPS: Oh, my goodness! Liam, do you think they're gonna fall in love?!
不。这就是挑战的主题。
No. That's just the theme of the challenges.
哦，我打赌他们会的。
Oh, I bet they will, though.
它们有如此多的共同点——然而它们又是死对头。
They've got so much in common - and yet they're deadly rivals.
就像罗密欧与朱丽叶
It's gonna be like Romeo and Juliet -
厨房地板对面的禁忌之爱!
forbidden love across the kitchen floor!
忽略他。因此，我死于一块蛋糕。
Ignore him. Thus, with a cake I die.
欢迎回到《职业烘焙大赛》。
And welcome back to Bake Off: The Professionals.
上一次，两支球队面对的是四个赛季的强队。
Last time, the teams faced the might of the four seasons.
不!
No!
皇家咖啡厅的Leanne和Romain
Leanne and Romain from the Hotel Cafe Royal
使比赛栩栩如生……
brought the competition to life...
这对我来说很神奇。
It's very magical for me.
. .然后得了第一名……
..and took first place...
我在做什么?
What am I doing?
. .而萨沃伊的艾迪和马希德有严重的时间问题…
..whilst the Savoy's Eddie and Mahshid had serious timing issues...
三个半小时，我很不高兴。
With three and a half hour, I'm not happy about it.
. .但是，是夏威夷州烹饪学校的凯蒂和凯利推翻了……
..but it was the WI cookery school's Katie and Kelly who toppled...
啊!
Argh!
从竞争中脱颖而出。
..from the competition.
现在，空气中弥漫着爱的气息……
Now, love is in the air...
因为发出哔哔声。
Cos BLEEP.
绝对的哔哔声。
Absolute BLEEP.
. .但评委们是否会为早餐糕点而倾倒?
..but will the judges fall for breakfast pastries...
. .沉醉于浪漫的糖果秀?
..and swoon over romantic sugar showpieces?
哦，啦，啦，啦，啦!
Oh, la, la, la, la!
只有五个四分之一决赛名额可供争夺……
With only five quarterfinal places up for grabs...
这是唯一的机会。
It's one chance only.
. .谁会承诺…
..who will be on a promise...
你想在床上吃早餐，是吗?
You wanted breakfast in the bed, yeah?
. .谁的心会破碎?
..and whose hearts will be broken?
别操之过急啊。
Don't bloody rush it for the sake of it.
一定是爱，爱，爱。＃
# It must be love, love, love. #
卡嗒卡嗒响
CLATTERING
音乐:威尔第的《安魂曲》
MUSIC: Requiem, Dies irae by Verdi
两组预赛的前三名
The top three teams from both sets of heats
一起组成了最后的六人组……
have come together to form the final six...
. .为了纪念这一时刻，
..and, to mark the occasion,
评委们将把比赛提升到一个全新的水平。
the judges are about to raise the competition to a whole new level.
欢迎回来，大厨们，
Welcome back, chefs,
恭喜你们进入了六强。
and congratulations on making it to the final six.
因为这周的主题是浪漫，
Now, because this week's theme is romance,
评委们决定测试一下你的法式蛋糕
the judges have decided to test you on the patisserie
他们最热衷的。
they are most passionate about.
Benoit和珍惜想让你做两种维也纳杂音
Benoit and Cherish would like you to make two types of Viennoiserie -
或者像大多数人所说的早餐糕点。
or breakfast pastries, as most people call them.
我要你做24个完美的羊角面包。
I want you to make 24 perfectly executed croissants.
它必须是黄油状的，片状的，而且一模一样。
It has to be buttery, flaky and identical.
我非常喜欢牛角面包。
I am very passionate about croissants.
亲爱的，我可以这么叫你吗?
Now, Benoisserie, may I call you that?
不。对不起，伯努瓦。
No. I'm sorry, Benoit.
您想让厨师准备什么?
What would you like the chefs to prepare?
我们从未见过的24件维也纳杂音作品。
24 Viennoiserie creations, that we've never seen before.
一部分是维也纳的喧闹，另一部分是完全不同的东西。
Part Viennoiserie, part something else altogether.
我为维也纳的喧闹而疯狂，我希望你也能疯狂一点。
I'm crazy for Viennoiseries and I'd like you to get a little crazy, too.
厨师们，你们昨晚只有30分钟准备，
Chefs, you had 30 minutes last night to prepare,
你们有三个半小时来完成今天的挑战。
and you have three and a half hours to complete today's challenge.
祝你好运，从现在开始。
Good luck, and your time starts now.
你在用哪个炉子?
Which stove are you using?
第一个炉子是丹麦的。
Stove one is the Danish.
另一个是羊角面包。
The other one is the croissants.
就是这里。我们选出了最后的六支队伍。
This is it. We've got the final six teams.
有了维也纳杂音乐团的创作，
With the Viennoiserie creation,
我们想让他们用经典的维也纳杂音
we want them to use a classic Viennoiserie -
把它和任何你想要的东西混在一起，重新创造一个新的。
mix it up with anything you want, and recreate a new one.
所以，我可以给你，比如，doissant -
So, I could give you, for example, the doissant -
这是一个甜甜圈和牛角包的组合。
which is a combination of a doughnut and a croissant.
你得想个办法
You have to come up with something
我们希望我们能考虑到。
we wished we would have thought about.
除了发明了一种独创的早餐糕点，
As well as inventing an original breakfast pastry,
这些团队还必须应对不断的折叠和冷却
the teams will also have to juggle the constant folding and chilling
这是制作经典羊角面包的必备条件。
required to perfect the dough for a classic croissant.
我在找什么
What I'm looking for
尝起来一定是黄油味的。
is that it has to be buttery when you taste.
它必须是片状的，
It has to be flaky,
层压必须突出和精确
and the lamination has to be prominent and precise -
当我切开羊角面包时，
and, when I cut through the croissant,
我喜欢看到这种美丽的蜂窝状纹理。
I like to see this beautiful honeycomb texture.
这看起来很简单，但要做到完美需要很高的技术。
It seems simple, but it is very technical to get it perfect.
覆膜，定型，发酵和烘烤两种糕点
Laminating, shaping, proving and baking two pastries
只需要三个半小时
in just three and a half hours
将要求团队小心地管理繁重的工作量。
will require the teams to manage their heavy workload carefully.
我只是在分配奶油蛋卷
I'm just portioning up the brioche
这样我就能尽快把它放到证明中。
so I can get this in the prover as quick as possible.
马希德已经开始做羊角面包了。
Mahshid's already started the croissants.
和我们大多数团队一样，
Like most of our teams,
艾迪和马希德来自伦敦举世闻名的萨沃伊酒店
Eddie and Mahshid from London's world-famous Savoy Hotel
我不习惯完美的维也纳音乐。
aren't used to perfecting Viennoiseries.
你们酒店里经常做羊角面包吗?
Do you guys make croissants a lot in the hotel?
不是我们，是面包师。
We don't, no, the bakers do.
怎么啦？怎么啦？还有别的队伍?
What? What? There's another team?
是的。那么，你整天都在做什么?
Yeah. So, what you do all day?
我们做糕点。我不知道这有什么区别。
We do the pastries. I didn't know there was a difference.
维也纳杂音乐团的创作，你为我们准备了什么?
So, Viennoiserie creation, what have you prepared for us?
我们要做一个briole。
We're gonna do a briole.
Briole。一半是奶油蛋卷，一半是泡芙。
Briole. It's half brioche and half profiterole.
艾迪的briole会有奶油蛋糕底，
Eddie's briole will have a brioche base,
泡芙酥皮，
a choux pastry top,
里面有榛子慕斯
filled with hazelnut mousseline
用碎坚果装饰
and decorated with crushed nuts
还有黑巧克力蛋糕。
and dark chocolate craquelin.
你怎么把泡芙糕点放在奶油蛋卷里?
How do you place your choux pastry in your brioche?
我们先证明一下奶油蛋卷，
So, we prove the brioche first,
然后我们要把泡芙糕点拌料倒进去，
and then we're going to pipe in our choux pastry mix,
然后在上面放上一层石蜡。
and then on top, it gets the craquelin.
谁创造了这个?
And who created this?
嗯，是的。你们俩都创造了?
Er, we did. You created, both of you?
是啊，我们只是想出了不同的办法。天啊!
Yeah, we just came up with something different. Gosh!
这可能是个不错的发明，不是吗?
Might be a good invention, isn't it?
这完全是我们想要的——尝试一些不同的东西
It is completely what we were asking for - try something different -
这可能是我们以前从未见过的。
something we potentially haven't seen before.
是的。
Yeah.
虽然想象力是维也纳噪音艺术创作的关键……
While imagination is key for the Viennoiserie creation...
我们需要想出一些不同的办法
We need come up with something different
还没有发明出来。
which hasn't been invented.
. .制作经典羊角面包，必须遵循严格的流程。
..for the classic croissant, a strict path has to be followed.
原料简单，所以过程很重要。
Simple ingredients, so process is important.
你的黄油怎么样?
How is your butter?
看起来有点软。
It seems a bit soft.
如果黄油在揉成面团时太热，
If the butter is too warm when it is folded into the dough,
在烘焙过程中，它会从糕点中漏出来
during baking, it will leak out of the pastry
导致层压坍塌。
causing layers of lamination to collapse.
太冷的话，它不会扩散到面团的边缘，
Too cold and it won't spread to the edges of the dough,
留下没有任何层压的区域。
leaving areas that won't have any lamination at all.
这一点都不好。
This is not good at all.
你量体温了吗?
Did you take the temperatures?
不。我说:“我们需要测量温度。”
No. I said, "We need to take the temperatures."
因为这里有很多面团
Cos there's all this dough here -
所有这些面团，
all this dough here,
黄油没有完全卷进去。我很抱歉。
and the butter's not been folded in properly. I'm sorry.
黄油和面团的温度不一样。
The temperature of my butter and the dough are not the same.
我忘记检查温度了。
I forgot to check the temperature.
我刚开始埋头苦干
I just started folding in,
所以，正如你所看到的，
and so, as you can see,
我们有很多面团，黄油粘在中间。
we have a lot of dough, and the butter's stuck in the middle.
它们不会起作用的。我可以告诉你。
They're not going to work. I can tell you that.
这些会很糟糕。
These are going to be bad.
他们会很哔哔的。
They're gonna be really BLEEP.
因为做得不对，
Because it's not been done properly,
我们没时间再做一个新的了。
and we don't have time to make a new one.
斯拉夫是豪华巧克力制作团队“我们的巧克力”的队长，
Slav, captain of the luxury chocolatier team, Our Chocolate,
也在挣扎。
is also struggling.
我有点担心这个。
I'm a bit worried about this.
看起来有点软。
It seems a bit soft.
我要放到冰箱里。
I'm gonna put in the fridge.
如果每次都让黄油融化，
If the butter is allowed to melt during each time-consuming turn,
一层层的面团会混合在一起，破坏任何分层的机会。
the layers of dough will combine, destroying any chance of lamination.
但是皇家咖啡酒店的首席面包师罗曼
But Romain, head baker of the Hotel Cafe Royal,
他有一种交易技巧。
has a trick of the trade up his sleeve.
罗曼刚刚把压好的面团放进了冰箱。
So, Romain has just put the laminated dough in the freezer.
我会做15分钟。
I would do 15 minutes.
对于他们创造的维也纳噪音，
For their Viennoiserie creation,
希尔顿公园巷五星级酒店的伊曼纽尔和山姆
Emmanuel and Sam of the five-star Hilton Park Lane
他们有自己的技巧。
have a trick of their own.
好吧，你在做什么，萨姆?
OK, so what are you doing, Sam?
crioche。crioche。
A crioche. A crioche.
是饼干，奶油蛋卷，捣碎在一起。噢!
Yeah - it's a cookie, brioche, smashed together. Ooh!
山姆会把香草奶油蛋糕和山核桃曲奇混合在一起
Sam will combine vanilla brioche with pecan cookie dough
把他的发明装满焦糖苹果
and fill his invention with caramelised apple
和一份卡尔瓦多斯奶油冻。
and a Calvados mousseline.
奶油冻，焦糖苹果，
So, Calvados mousseline, caramelised apple,
饼干……还有奶油蛋糕。和核桃吗?
cookie... And the brioche. And pecan?
和蛋糕。毫米。
And brioche. Mm.
他吹口哨
HE WHISTLES
发生了很多事，伙计们?
A lot going on, guys, huh?
你说疯了。疯狂，我想。
You said crazy. Crazy, I want.
伯明翰名胜世界的达里尔和巴雷特
Darryl and Barrett of Birmingham's Resorts World
我对颜色很着迷。
have gone crazy with colour.
我在做粉色的丹麦饼，
I'm making a pink Danish,
试着联系一下
trying to go a bit in touch
用我女性化的一面。
with my feminine side.
他的粉色丹麦糕点盒会被装满的
His pink Danish pastry cases will be filled
搭配白巧克力
with white chocolate
法式奶油，覆盆子凝胶，
creme patissiere, raspberry gel,
还有一份开心果泥。
and a pistachio nut puree.
这些就像volo - auvents。
These are like vol-au-vents.
这是正确的。那是我出生之前的事了。
That's right. Those are before my time.
我想它们在80年代的时候是很火的。
I suppose they were, like, really hot in, like, the '80s.
是的，我们要救活他们。
Yeah - we're gonna revive them.
我们只能拭目以待了。
We'll have to wait and see.
你知道评委是什么样的。他们可能会把它放在石板上。
You know what the judges are like. They'll probably slate it.
但是，你知道。
But, you know.
说到给评委留下好印象，
When it comes to impressing the judges,
一个队将有优势。
one team will have an advantage.
罗曼，我没猜错吧，你是烘焙部的主管?
Now, Romain, am I right in thinking, you are head of baking?
贝克。头贝克!
Head baker. Head baker!
比如谢丽尔·贝克。
Like Cheryl Baker.
皇家咖啡厅的首席面包师。
Head baker at Hotel Cafe Royal.
你觉得这能让你比别人领先一步吗?
So, does that give you a head start on everybody, do you think?
我比谁都紧张。
I'm more nervous than everyone.
为什么?我的命悬一线!
Why? My head is on the line!
罗曼发明了浪漫的丹麦糕点花
Romain has invented romantic Danish pastry flowers
螺旋状的普通和粉色糕点在哪里
where spirals of plain and pink pastry
填满覆盆子果酱会坐
filled with raspberry jam will sit
在开心果黑貂饼干基底上。
on a pistachio sable biscuit base.
这是我们以前从未见过的吗?
Is that something we've never seen before?
你可能以前见过。
You've probably seen it before.
这个形状，我相信你见过。
This shape, I'm sure you've seen.
他不能发明一个新的形状!
He can't invent a new shape!
只有这么多形状。
There's only so many shapes.
丹麦人的身材现在已经很出名了，
The shape of the Danish is always kind of well known now,
但这样做的时候，底部就不会有开心果了。
but then it is not done with a pistachio sable in the bottom.
我们拭目以待。你有足够的创造力吗?
We will see. Have you been creative enough?
这是我的问题，你安全了吗?
That's my question - or have you been safe?
我们拭目以待。
We will see.
Hideko和Teo的情况很不安全
Things are far from safe with Hideko and Teo
来自独立糕点定制公司Sweet Art Lab
from the independent bespoke pastry business, Sweet Art Lab.
虽然是早餐时间，但他们已经开始喝酒了。
It may be breakfast time, but they are already drinking.
你要来杯果汁朗姆酒吗?我喜欢椰子汁朗姆酒。
You like a pina colada? I love pina colada.
他们的朗姆酒糕点
Their pina colada pastries
会看到绿色菠萝形状的奶油蛋卷，
will see green, pineapple-shaped brioche buns,
里面是菠萝果泥
filled with pineapple compote
还有椰子和朗姆酒奶油。
and a coconut and rum cream.
我们要做奶油蛋卷面团。
We are going to make brioche dough.
把它像牛角面包一样叠起来。
Laminate it like a croissant.
然后做出菠萝的效果。
and then making like a pineapple effect.
所以，这是一个椰林酒奶油蛋卷。
So, it's a pina colada brioche.
那么，我们如何缩短它呢?也许喜欢…皮诺什?
So, how do we shorten that? Maybe to like a...Pinoche?
一般Pinoche。
General Pinoche.
这就是你想要的，对吧?
That's what you wanted, right?
美味的皮诺什早餐。
A delicious, breakfast Pinoche.
我…我喜欢它。
I...I like it.
你确定吗?
You sure?
Pinoche。我也是。
Pinoche. Me too.
现在，我要对面团进行第二次折叠。
Now, I am giving the second fold to my dough.
折叠两下，萨沃伊的牛角面包面团…
Two folds in and the Savoy's croissant dough...
发出哔哔声
BLEEP
. .似乎没有好转。
..doesn't seem to be improving.
艾迪想弥补我犯下的错误。
Eddie's trying to recover the mistake that I made.
我对它一点信心都没有。
I'm not confident at all with it.
因为发出哔哔声。哔哔声。
Cos BLEEP. BLEEP.
看在上帝的份上。
For BLEEP sake.
在整个比赛中，
Throughout the competition,
巧克力商斯拉夫和玛丽亚
chocolatiers Slav and Maria
他们的招牌食材——
have impressed with their signature ingredient -
但是，在浪漫周，
but, for romance week,
他们抛弃了他们的初恋。
they have turned their back on their first love.
你打算加入一些巧克力吗
Are you going to incorporate some kind of chocolate
在你的创作中?
into any of your creation?
不是今天。
Not today.
我真不敢相信你!下一个挑战。
I can't believe you! On the next challenge.
你总是做巧克力。
You have always made chocolate.
我们今天不想再吃巧克力了。
We like to have a break from chocolate this day.
他们的无巧克力核桃窝
Their chocolate-free walnut nest
看到奶油蛋卷面团了吗
will see the brioche dough
围绕
swirled around
柠檬核桃蛋白酥。
a lemon and walnut meringue.
听起来不错，但这很有创意吗?
Sounds nice - but is that very creative?
柠檬漩涡?
A lemon swirl?
对我来说，是的。
For me, it is.
现在是最后一次揉面了。
So, now it's the last fold I give to my dough.
在那之后，我会让它休息一会儿
After that, I will leave it to rest for a little bit
然后塑形。
and roll out in shape.
看起来棒极了。看上去不错。
Looking great. Looking good.
牛角面包，我想我可能修好了，我不知道。
So, the croissant, I think I might have fixed it, I don't know.
祈祷。
Fingers crossed.
我在做维也纳杂音的创作。
I'm making the Viennoiserie creation.
确保它是均匀的。
Make sure it's even.
评委们要求几批维也纳杂音
The judges have demanded batches of Viennoiserie
它们完全相同。
that are absolutely identical.
确保他们排好队，然后卡住。
Make sure they're lined up, and they're stuck.
他们必须被困住。
They have to be stuck.
把泡芙泡在奶油蛋卷中间，
Just piping the choux in the middle of the brioche,
然后我们要在上面放上标枪，
and then we're going put the craquelin on top,
然后我们再证明一次。
and then we're going to prove it again.
现在我在做羊角面包。
So, now I'm shaping the croissant.
在这之后，他们将准备好进入证明器。
After this, they will be ready to go in the prover.
实际上一切都很顺利。
It's actually going pretty well.
我画一个三角形，然后把它卷起来。
I do a triangle, and then just roll it.
就这么简单。
Easy as that.
罗曼的经验……
Romain's experience...
我对今天的成果很满意。
I'm quite happy with what we've got today.
. .看到他的两个维也纳噪音首先进入证明
..sees both of his Viennoiserie first into the prover -
而其他的队伍在挣扎。
while the rest of the teams struggle.
我能切吗，你还行吗?我很好。
Can I cut, or are you OK? I'm OK.
9的一半是4.5，不是吗?
Half of 9's 4.5, isn't it?
一个小小的差别最终会产生巨大的差别。
A small difference now make a massive difference at the end.
它们现在越厚，
The thicker they are now,
他们就会证明得越多
the more they are going to prove
之后就会变得越好。
and the more good they are going to be afterwards.
考虑到我给我们带来的麻烦，他们看起来还不错。
Considering the mess I put us into, they're looking OK.
这需要时间。
This is taking time.
和你在一起我很开心!
I'm so happy I'm with you!
我们看看，它还没有被证明。
Let's see - it's not proved yet.
大厨们，维也纳音乐界的挑战已经进行了一半。
Chefs, you are halfway through your Viennoiserie challenge.
我们为什么不直接说早餐点心呢?
Why aren't we just saying breakfast pastries?
你可以。厨师们，你们的早餐点心吃到一半了。
You can. Chefs, you are halfway through your breakfast pastries.
当维也纳杂音乐队的作品准备好烘烤时…
Whilst the Viennoiserie creations are ready for the oven...
. .牛角面包至少要发酵一个小时。
..croissants should be left to prove for at least an hour.
周围有很多人，对吧?
There's loads of, like, hanging around, isn't there?
如果它证明的太多或不够，我的意思是，你真的不能做太多。
If it overproves or underproves, I mean, you can't really do too much.
这是一次机会，只有一次机会。
It's one chance, one chance only.
兄弟，你应该给电影或别的什么画外音。
Bro, you should do some voice-over for films or something.
你眼中的坚定当你说，
The conviction in your eyes when you say,
“一次机会，只有一次机会。”
"One chance and one chance only."
是的。
Yeah.
等待。
Waiting.
只是等待。
Just waiting.
在比赛中第一次，
For the first time in the competition,
球队没有什么可做的。
there is nothing for the teams to do.
是的。
Yeah.
我讨厌这个。
I BLEEP hate this.
大厨们，你们还有半个小时，就半个小时。
Chefs, you have half an hour left - that's half an hour.
现在需要做一个权衡。
Now there is a trade-off to be made.
每一分钟都在证明……
Every minute in the prover...
还需要一点时间来证明。
Still a little bit more time to prove.
. .这意味着更少的时间在烤箱里…
..means less time in the oven...
你需要烤一下。是的。你需要烤一下。
You need to bake it. Yeah. You need to bake it.
是的。让我们的时间。
Yeah. let's time.
. .但他们憋得越久…
..but the longer they hold their nerve...
. .他们就越少冒着吃又重又软的牛角面包的风险。
..the less they risk heavy, doughy croissants.
我们给牛角面包五分钟，然后把它们放进去。
We'll give the croissants five minutes and then we'll pop them in.
目标是15到20分钟。
Aiming for 15 to 20 minutes.
冰镇了，准备好了。
They're chilled and ready.
继续。
Go on.
放进去。
Put it in.
现在几点了?34.
What time is it? 34.
我们现在把它们放进去。
Let's put them in now.
我们对他们无能为力。
There's nothing we can do with them.
就是这样。结果很好，结果很好。
That's it. They come out good, they come good.
结果很糟糕，结果很糟糕。
They come out bad, they come out bad.
他们在吐黄油。
They're spitting butter.
大厨们，你们还有15分钟。
Chefs, you've got 15 minutes left.
还有15分钟。
15 minutes left.
我现在对这些很满意。
These ones I'm quite happy with at the minute.
大胆去做吧。关闭它。
Go for it. Close it.
就像撕和分享奶油蛋卷和饼干一样。
It's going to be like a tear and share brioche and cookie.
这不是我想要的，但情况可能会更糟。
It's not exactly what I want, but it could have been worse.
很好。
It's good.
我们还剩多久?
How long do we have left?
大厨们，你们还有五分钟。
Chefs, you have five minutes left.
我的羊角面包还没做好。
My croissants haven't really gone to plan.
把它们拿出来。
Take them out.
他们准备好了吗?他们看起来怎么样?
Are they ready? How are they looking?
是的，他们准备好了。
Yeah, they're ready.
牛角面包差不多好了。
The croissants are almost ready.
大厨们，你们还有一分钟。
Chefs, you have one minute left.
来吧。
Come on.
我想说，没关系。
It's all right, I would say.
大厨们，你们的时间到了。你的时间到了。
Chefs, your time is up. Your time is up.
它们不好。
They're not good.
我想是回家的时间了。
Home time, I think.
罗曼的是最好的。
Romain's is the best.
你快乐吗?我很高兴。
Are you happy? I'm happy.
我很高兴你开心!
I'm happy you're happy!
我的天啊!
Oh, my God!
是时候评判两队的表现了。
It's judgment time for the teams' viennoiserie.
伊曼纽尔和萨姆，请上前。
Emmanuel and Sam, please come forward.
歌剧音乐
OPERA MUSIC
你可以看到它们实际上是不一致的。
You can see that they are actually quite inconsistent.
这很令人失望。
This is quite disappointing.
看起来不太好。它没有我们想要的蜂巢。
It doesn't look good. It doesn't have the honeycomb that we were looking for.
这是一项正在进行的工作，我只能说这些，
It's a work in progress, that's all I can say,
但这不是它应该在的地方。那你的维也纳杂音创作呢?
but it's not where it should be. What about your viennoiserie creation?
我喜欢饼干和奶油蛋卷的创意，但是制作方法，
I like the idea of the cookie and the brioche dough, but the execution,
你不能只是把东西放在一起就指望它能起作用。
you can't just throw things together and expect it to work.
我很喜欢这个苹果，还有卡尔瓦多斯和
I quite like the apple with the Calvados and the
然而，糕点奶油，
pastry cream, however,
这就是我能说的所有积极的一面。
that's about all that I can say in the positive side.
这是你最大的挑战之一。
This is one of your worst challenges.
你们可以做得更好。
You guys can do better.
对我来说，这里没有足够的工作。
For me, there is not enough work here.
低语:严厉!
WHISPERS: Harsh!
这是非常困难的。
It's very tough.
商店里到处都是。小的，大的。
It's all over the shop. Little ones, big ones.
有些看起来像牛角面包，有些看起来什么都没有。
Some look kind of a croissant and some looks like absolutely nothing.
我觉得有点没煮熟。
I think it's undercooked a little bit.
你觉得有一点没煮熟吗?
You think it's undercooked a LITTLE bit?
我不吃没有烤过的维也纳杂烩。
I am not eating viennoiserie which is not baked.
这是一个核桃窝。
So this is a walnut nest.
它的设计有点简单，
It's a bit of a simple design,
它们看起来相当密集，如果有一件事你不想要的是
and they look fairly dense and if there is one thing you don't want is
吃完早餐后感到沉重。
to feel heavy after you have had your breakfast.
你能提醒我们这里面是什么吗?
Can you remind us what is this inside here?
柠檬核桃蛋白酥。
Meringue with lemon and walnuts.
我们只能说维也纳噪音不是你的菜。
What we can say is that viennoiserie is not your thing.
我能看到一些层压，
There's some lamination that I can see,
但我能看到它很不规则。
but I can see it is very irregular.
它是烤好的，但是……
It is baked, but...
太紧。创意，展示方式，红色，
too tight. Creations, presentation-wise, red,
大量的红色。上色，伙计们，要适度。
a lot of red. Colouring, guys, with moderation.
我吃的时候很干。
It's so dry when I eat it.
我一点也不喜欢吃糕点。
I don't enjoy eating the pastry at all.
嗯。它很重。
Um. It is so heavy.
我们要的是片状，黄油状，一模一样的。
We asked for flaky, buttery, identical.
我必须在所有的方框里划叉。
I have to cross all the boxes.
也许你的创作更走运。
Maybe you got better luck with your creation.
我喜欢这个主意。我喜欢这种执行方式吗?
I like the idea. Do I like the execution?
不。
No.
菠萝的味道还在。
The flavour of the pineapple is present.
它不像看起来那么难吃。
It doesn't taste as bad as it looks.
这是恭维吗?是的!谢谢你！
Is that a compliment? Yes! Thank you!
我担心他们不会发短信不好吃。不。
I fear that they are not going to text not going to taste great. No.
没有?嗯…
No? Well...
嗯，这是什么……事情就是这样。
Well, it is what... It is what it is.
事情就是这样。它很重。它很紧。
It is what it is. It's very heavy. It's very tight.
绝对没有任何瑕疵。
There's absolutely no flakiness whatsoever.
我不打算尝，因为它是生的。
I'm not going to taste it because it's uncooked.
还有你的披肩。
And your briolles.
你已经接受了应有的挑战。
You've taken the challenge as it should be.
你把两种不同的东西合二为一了。
You have combined two different things to make one.
有趣。这就是你想要达到的目标吗?
Interesting. Is that what you were trying to achieve?
是的。好的。
Yes. OK.
这两种味道的结合，真的很不错。
The flavour combination of the two, it's actually pleasant.
我喜欢吃它。
I enjoy eating it.
就味道而言，就你放在上面的坚果而言。
In terms of the flavour, in terms of the nuts that you put on top.
泡芙糕点和奶油蛋卷。噢!有趣。
Choux pastry and the brioche. Ooh! Interesting.
我认为你做得很好。我为你感到骄傲，干得好。
I think you did very well. Very proud of you, well done.
是的，非常感谢。再见。
Yeah, thank you very much. See you later.
毫无疑问，这些是当今最好的牛角面包。
There isn't a shadow of a doubt these are the best croissants today.
它们很脆，烤得很好。
They are flaky, they are baked correctly.
它们看起来膨胀了，所以它们被证明了。
They look like they have expanded, so therefore they were proved.
跟我说话，罗曼。这不是我做过的最好的。
Talk to me, Romain. It's not the best I have done.
它可以更轻，蜂巢的质地需要扩大一点。
It can be lighter and the honeycomb texture needs to expand a bit more.
话虽如此，我认为我们已经有了一个伟大的开端。
Having said that, I think we have the beginning of what should be great.
让我来打开它。哦，我的天哪!你能听到吗?
Let me crack it. Oh, my goodness! Can you hear that?
他们今天卖的牛角面包是最好的。
They are at the best croissants today.
你的维也纳杂音作品。
Your viennoiserie creations.
花的图案，底部有开心果甜面酱。
A flower pattern, which has got a pistachio sweet paste at the bottom.
我们在里面放了覆盆子酱和开心果酱。
We've filled it with a raspberry jam and then also a pistachio paste.
你让我想起了麦当娜。
You remind me of Madonna.
他们笑了
THEY LAUGH
麦当娜和你在一起会很开心的。
Madonna would be so happy with you.
特别为她设计的。
Especially created for her.
我真的很喜欢覆盆子的味道。
I really like the flavour of the raspberry.
真的。这样就行了，所以你的名声暂时是安全的。
I really do. That makes it work, so your reputation is safe for now.
好。听你这么说我很高兴。
Good. I'm glad to hear it.
第一次我们成功了，所以，
For once, we nailed the first challenge, so,
是的…我们提供了一些东西，这是主要的。
yeah... We served something, that's the main thing.
我们提供了24个牛角包。
We served 24 croissants.
很糟糕，但我们提供了24份。是的。是的。
There were terrible, but we served 24. Yeah. Yeah.
你能做什么?
What can you do?
有时候生活很艰难，但你必须坚持下去。
Sometimes life is hard, you have to get on with it.
各队现在有黄金时间准备任何需要设置的元素
The teams now have a golden hour to prepare any elements that need setting
明天的糖果秀。
for tomorrow's all sugar showpiece.
球队明天必须做得很好，因为他们正在为冠军而战
The teams have to do really well tomorrow because they are fighting for a
进入四分之一决赛。今天谁印象深刻?
place in the quarterfinal. So who's really impressed today?
毫无疑问，
There is no shadow of a doubt,
皇家酒店咖啡馆提供了一套漂亮的维也纳杂耍。
Hotel Cafe Royale delivered a beautiful set of viennoiserie.
是的，他非常专注。我能看到他眼中的怒火。
Yeah, he was so focused. I can see the fire is in his eyes.
希尔顿公园巷，他们在预赛中表现很好，
Hilton Park Lane, they've been really good throughout the heats,
但现在到了最后六名，到目前为止，他们还没有真正交付。
but now it's come to the final six, so far, they haven't really delivered.
这是他们今天打出的最差的比赛之一。
This is one of the worst performances they put on the table today.
R巧克力，真的很担心。
R Chocolate, really concerned.
明天是糖的工作，他们被称为R巧克力。
Tomorrow is sugar work and they are called R Chocolate.
让我们希望他们已经在糖的工作上工作了，因为这可能是一个杀手
Let's hope they have worked on sugar work because that could be a killer
为他们吹。展示挑战。
blow for them. The showpiece challenge.
本周的主题是浪漫。
This week it's themed around romance.
那么，你对球队有什么期待呢?
What are you expecting to see from the teams, then?
当我们想到浪漫，我们会想到情人节，想到玫瑰，
When we think romance, we think about Valentine, we think about roses,
我们想想钻石。
we think about diamonds.
我想到了Grindr，但继续。这是怎么形成的呢?
I think about Grindr, but carry on. How does that come together?
待会儿我会告诉你的，珍爱，
I'll tell you about it after this, Cherish,
我觉得我们没时间在蛋糕比赛的时候解释Grindr。
I don't think we've got time to explain Grindr in the middle of a cake competition.
歌剧音乐
OPERA MUSIC
狗哀求
DOG WHINES
直面比赛。
Game face on.
早上好，厨师们。表演时间到了!
Good morning, chefs. It's showpiece time!
这不是我第一次说这种浪漫的话了。
And that's not the first romantic setting I've ever said that in.
这是你们最后一次给评委留下深刻印象赢得下一届比赛的机会
This is your last chance to impress the judges to win a place in next
星期的四分之一决赛。
week's quarterfinal.
我们想让你做一个漂亮的糖陈列品。
We would like you to make a beautiful sugar showpiece.
让你的结构创新，技术上完美无瑕，但别忘了，
Make your structure innovative and technically flawless, but don't forget,
这是浪漫周，所以我们希望在你的设计中看到激情。
this is romance week, so we want to see passion in your design.
你的展示品必须包括30个拉糖糖果和30个设计师
Your showpiece must include 30 pulled sugar sweets and 30 designer
杏仁糖让我们的心砰砰跳。
marzipan to make our heart go boom, boom, boom.
你还有四个小时来完成今天的挑战，现在开始计时。
You have four hours remaining to complete today's challenge and your time starts now.
祝你好运。祝你好运。
Good luck. Good luck.
这是该比赛第一次全糖展示挑战。
This is the competition's first-ever all sugar showpiece challenge.
把它调到160。
Just bring it back here to 160.
参赛队伍必须建造一个令人惊叹的中心建筑，至少有70个
And the teams must construct a stunning centrepiece at least 70
厘米高。吃糖会出什么问题?
centimetres tall. What can go wrong with sugar?
首先，很明显，它会断裂。
Well, the first, obvious, it can break.
如果它不站着，它就会坍塌，但当它坍塌时，
If it's not standing up still it will collapse, but when it collapses,
它打破了。
it shatters.
我们期待看到漂亮的拉糖，吹糖，砂糖，
We expect to see beautiful pulled sugar, blown sugar, cast sugar and,
当然，糖果必须精致。
of course, the confectionery has to be exquisite.
我们的要求比以往任何时候都要高。
We are asking more than ever.
一定是爱，爱，爱……＃
# It must be love, love, love... #
太热了。经过昨天令人心碎的挑战，
That is hot. After a heartbreaking challenge yesterday,
伊曼纽尔和山姆现在希望用更多的东西来修复关系
Emmanuel and Sam are now hoping to patch things up with more than just
爱的力量。展品是浪漫的，
the power of love. The showpiece is romantic,
但它更有异国情调。
but it's more with an exotic touch.
这种花是外来的，是一种外来的天堂鸟，但这正是我们需要的，
The flower is exotic, an exotic bird of paradise, but that's what we need,
你知道吗?来点浪漫，来点阳光。
you know? A bit of romance, a bit of sun.
在一棵浇糖树下，用糖花和吹的
Beneath a poured sugar tree decorated in pulled sugar flowers and a blown
糖鸟，将榛子、果仁、蜜糖和杏子拉下来
sugar bird, will sit hazelnut praline pulled sugar sweets and apricot
调味杏仁糖玫瑰。
flavoured marzipan roses.
一支球队进入四分之一决赛的机会可能得到了急需的提振。
And a team's chances of reaching the quarterfinals may have been given a much-needed boost.
我想展示尽可能多的制糖技巧，
I want to show as many sugar skills as possible,
所以我要用到七八种技巧。
so I must have about seven or eight techniques all going on.
就在十个月前，山姆在英国糖锦标赛中获得第二名。
Just ten months ago, Sam came second in the UK sugar championships.
压力和肾上腺素开始发挥作用，
Pressure and adrenaline has to kick in,
尤其是当你站在一块要把你融化成碎片的糖块面前的时候。
especially when you're standing in front of a sugar lump that's melting you to pieces.
但山姆并不是房间里唯一的糖专家。
But Sam isn't the only sugar expert in the room.
来自萨沃伊的埃迪是同一比赛的少年组决赛选手。
Eddie from the Savoy was a finalist in the junior category of the same competition.
所以，我们已经有了一个漂亮的波浪形状，吹心就要来了
So, we've got a nice way wavy shape and are blown heart is going to come
从后面绕到前面然后爱无处不在。
from the back around to the front and then love is everywhere.
《爱无处不在》，这是中心作品的名字吗?
Love Is Everywhere, is that the name of the centrepiece?
就是现在!埃迪的糖茎模可以支撑一个巨大的吹糖
It is now! Eddie's moulded sugar stem will support a giant blown sugar
心脏将为咸花生果仁糖和
heart that will provide the backdrop for salted peanut praline sweets and
樱桃形状的杏仁糖配开心果核。
cherry-shaped marzipans with pistachio stones.
那颗樱桃，它和那件展品有什么联系吗，因为它很浪漫?
That cherry, does it have anything to link with the showpiece, because it's romance?
你们去浪漫野餐的时候，会互相喂樱桃吗?
You know, when you go for a romantic picnic, you feed each other cherries?
我们认为草莓太常见了。我们想做一些不同的事情。
We thought, you know, strawberries are too common. We wanted to do something different.
所以你有备用的，对吧?
So you have spares, right?
是的。我可以吗?不。
We do, yes. Can I? No.
当艾迪和山姆在冠军级别的时候…
While Eddie and Sam are at championship level...
这就像是一颗美丽的心，或者…
This is like some sort of beautiful heart or maybe a...
这不是一颗心。我只是在工作……也许是肝脏?可能是肝脏?
It's not a heart. I'm just working... Maybe a liver? It could be a liver?
. .这是Maria和Slav第一次只使用糖。
..this is the first time Maria and Slav have worked solely with sugar.
我们要在巴黎搞浪漫。我们做过红心。
We are doing romance in Paris. We've done hearts.
你可以在这里看到。哦!哦!
You can see it here. Oh! Oh!
斯拉夫人的心脏将被三色糖带包裹，而他的
Slav's hearts will be wrapped in tricolour sugar ribbons and his
向巴黎的浪漫致敬，将看到两只吹糖情侣拥抱在一起
homage to the romance of Paris will see two blown sugar lovebirds embrace
上面是橘子和开心果杏仁糖花
over orange and pistachio marzipan flowers
还有榛子果仁填充的糖果。
and sweets filled with hazelnut praline.
我可以问一下，你现在是单身吗?
May I ask, are you single at the moment?
我现在是单身。目前为止。
I am single at the moment. At the moment.
我可以问一下，玛丽亚，你现在是单身还是…?
May I ask, Maria, are you single at the moment or are you..?
我现在也是单身。哦!你觉得你们俩能聚一聚吗?
I am single at the moment, as well. Oh! Do you think you guys could get together maybe?
我们现在根本没有时间。
We don't have time at the moment at all.
“我爱你”用匈牙利语怎么说?
What is, "I love you," in Hungarian?
Szeretlek。Szeretlek。用马其顿语怎么说?
Szeretlek. Szeretlek. And what is it in Macedonian?
Te sakam。Te sakam。
Te sakam. Te sakam.
好吧，我以前还没听说过!
OK, I haven't heard that yet before!
也许有一天你还会听到。不管怎样，我不打扰你了。
Well, maybe you'll hear it again one day. Anyway, I'll leave you to it.
再见!再见!再见!
Bye! Bye! Bye!
画外音:斯拉芙和玛丽亚并不是唯一前往情人之城的人。
VOICEOVER: Slav and Maria aren't the only ones headed to the city of lovers.
所以，这是一部法式罗曼史。是的，这是一部法式罗曼史。
So, it's a French romance. Yes, it's a French romance.
巴黎。巴黎。
Parisian. Parisian.
主要部分是一颗心和一些丝带，
The main part is a heart and some ribbons,
红色，蓝色和白色。
the red and the blue and the white colour.
法国国旗。我明白你的意思了，西奥，
The French flag. Oh, I see what you're doing there, Theo,
我知道你在干什么。
I see what you're doing.
他们的巴黎之旅将以蓝色和白色的风完成
Their Parisian affair will be completed with blue and white blown
甜蜜的情侣，用巧克力和榛子果仁填充的糖果
sugar lovebirds, sweets filled with a chocolate and hazelnut praline
第二天早上，罂粟籽，
and, for the morning after, poppy seed,
芒果和百香果杏仁软糖，不那么浪漫
mango and passion fruit marzipans in the slightly less romantic form
烤面包上放鸡蛋。你知道，在度过一个美好的夜晚之后…
of egg on toast. You know, after a nice night...
哦，啦，啦，啦，啦!你想在床上吃早餐，是吗?
Ooh, la, la, la, la! You want breakfast in the bed, yeah?
你是说就我们俩吗?
You mean just the two of us?
早餐浪漫。你的选择是什么?啊，我们都是。
Breakfast romance. What's your choice? Ah, so all of us.
在皇家咖啡厅的浪漫举动似乎更精致一些。
Romantic gestures at the Hotel Cafe Royal seem to be a little more refined.
我们的展示品会有鲜花，爱心，香槟酒杯，
Our showpiece is going to have flowers, hearts, champagne glasses,
草莓。你知道的，和往常一样。
strawberries. You know, the usual.
他们是唯一一支尝试两层展示的队伍
They are the only team attempting a two-tiered showpiece where an ornate
18件立体展示架将支持他们的香槟
18-piece three-dimensional display stand will support their champagne
还有心形主题的糖雕。
and heart-themed sugar sculpture.
里面会塞满榛子果仁糖和杏仁糖
It will be filled with hazelnut praline sweets and marzipan
用开心果和玫瑰调味的草莓。
strawberries flavoured with pistachio and rose.
我必须试着理解你为什么选择玫瑰来调味
I'm must try to understand why you have chosen rose to flavour a
草莓。因为我们的展品上有玫瑰。
strawberry. Because we have roses on our showpiece.
他今天会给你答案!
The man has answers for you today!
我什么都想。
I think about everything.
罗曼，交给你了。
Romain, you are on it.
爱是你的事。
Love is your thing.
它是。罗曼会有浪漫吗?
It is. Could there be romance for Romain?
罗曼浪漫。
Romain romance.
歌词。哦,是的。
Lyrics. Oh, yes.
哦,是的。虽然罗曼已经考虑到了一切…
Oh, yes. Whilst Romain has thought of everything...
我们来画天鹅……
We'll do swans...
嗯，它们可能是鸭子。
Well, they might be ducks.
看看结果如何。
See how they turn out.
. .Darryl和Bharat的浪漫计划还没有开始
..Darryl and Bharat's romantic plans have yet to be
完全坚定。
fully firmed up.
他们会坐在爱心上面。
They're going to sit on top of the love heart.
就像我和我妻子一样。
Like me and my wife, actually.
嗯…我会为此得到加分的。
Um... I'll get Brownie points for that.
在一颗巨大的糖心和两只尚未命名的鸟的下面，
Below a giant moulded sugar heart and two as yet unnamed birds,
要榛子果仁糖、糖果和心形草莓糖吗
will sit hazelnut pralines sweets and heart-shaped strawberry and
橙色的杏仁蛋白软糖。我相信会有两只天鹅，也许吧。
orange marzipans. I'm confident there's going to be two swans, maybe.
大厨们，你们的浪漫挑战已经进行了一半。
Chefs, you are halfway through your romantic challenge.
我在吹糖心。
I'm blowing a sugar heart.
温度决定一切。为了成功地吹出并塑造融化的糖，
Temperature is everything. To successfully blow and shape molten sugar,
厨师们必须在温度上走钢丝。
the chefs must walk a temperature tightrope.
使用热灯，
Using heat lamps,
他们需要不断确保糖的温度足以操作。
they need to constantly ensure the sugar is hot enough to manipulate.
哎呀!它走了这么远。
Whoops! It went so far.
一旦他们有了满意的形状……
And the moment they have a shape they're happy with...
这很好。
That's good.
. .他们需要用风扇轻轻地冷却糖，直到它凝固。
..using a fan, they need to gently cool the sugar until it sets.
我已经吹好了天鹅，我想让它的脖子开始下垂，
So I have blown the swan, as I want the neck to start to set,
我一直在吹尸体。
I keep blowing the body.
加热或冷却过度，甚至稍微太快，
Heat or cool too much, or even slightly too quickly,
他们精心打造的形体将会破碎。
and their carefully crafted forms will shatter.
它可能会存活下来，但我不确定，因为我需要冷静下来。
It might survive, but I'm not sure because I need to cool down.
但是，虽然大多数团队都在吹较小的装饰物品……
But whilst most teams are blowing smaller decorative items...
少了一个。艾迪的整个展览都是围绕着一个巨人建造的
That's one down. ..Eddie's entire showpiece is built around a giant
心是由两个巨大的吹成的。
heart made with two huge blown halves.
哔哔声!
BLEEP!
有点冷。可能会更热。
It's a bit cold. It could be hotter.
再过10度就没事了。
Another 10 degrees and we'll be fine.
它看起来像一只鸟吗?现在我把它哔哔了一下。
Does it look like a bird? Now I've BLEEP this up.
我要重新开始。
I'm going to start this again.
只是温度太低了。这里的情况并不一致。
It's just the temperatures were off. It's not consistent in here.
是的，我想这样就行了。
Yeah, I think that'll do.
按你想要的方式完成工作总是好的。
It's always nice to finish a job the way you wanted to.
埃迪现在有完成不了的危险。
Eddie is now in danger of not finishing at all...
哔哔声!哔哔声!
BLEEP! BLEEP!
我再来一次。
I'll start again.
. .离开他的浪漫秀…
..leaving his romantic showpiece...
哔哔声!报纸着火了……没有一颗心。
BLEEP! The paper's on fire. ..without a heart.
还有90分钟我们就能确保进入四分之一决赛。
90 minutes left to secure a place in the quarterfinals.
纸被喷灯夹住了。
The paper caught on the blowtorch.
还有其他的展示元素有待构建……
And with other showpiece elements still to construct...
我相当高兴……艾迪的心脏让他慢下来了。
I'm reasonably happy. ..Eddie's heart is slowing him down.
它是半个心形的。
It's half a heart shape.
除了令人惊叹的糖展示，
As well as a stunning sugar showpiece,
法官要求30…
the judges have demanded 30...
三、四、五、六、七、八、九、十……
Three, four, five, six, seven, eight, nine, ten...
. .精致的杏仁糖，看起来和味道一样好。
..exquisite marzipans that look as good as they taste.
我在做西装的蝴蝶结。
I'm making the bow for the suit.
用喷灯，它们看起来真的像一片面包。
With the blowtorch, they really look like a slice of bread.
吐司鸡蛋对你来说是一顿非常浪漫的晚餐吗?
Is egg on toast a very romantic meal for you?
这是狂欢之夜之后，这是美味的早餐。
This is after the wild night, it's the lovely breakfast.
一夜狂欢之后，你居然喜欢给人做鸡蛋吐司?
Wow, after a wild night you like to make someone egg on toast?!
就是这样!到床上去!
That's it! And get into the bed!
他们的30个浪漫杏仁糖必须再加上30个拉出来的果仁糖
Their 30 romantic marzipans must be escorted by 30 more pulled praline
糖果。我们有两个糖，一个银的，一个金的。
sweets. So we've got two sugar, one silver, one gold.
吃点果仁糖。
Pipe some praline.
我们选了咸花生味的。人人都爱吃花生。
We've gone for a salted peanut flavour. Everybody loves a peanut.
会出什么问题呢?有时当你折叠它时，
What could go wrong? Sometimes when you fold it,
到处都在漏。
it's just leaking everywhere.
棘手的是……
The tricky part...
嗯……。我都不知道会发生什么。
Grr. I don't even know what's coming out.
我们得确保这些都密封得很好，
We've got to make sure these are sealed properly,
当你要滚动的时候，你必须要快。
and then when it comes to rolling, you've got to be fast.
如果糖太凉了……哔哔声。
If the sugar becomes too cool... BLEEP.
. .它太脆了，倒不出来。
..it will be too brittle to pour.
冷却得太快了。
That's cooled down too fast.
毁掉了送出薄弱点的机会，
Ruining any chance of delivering the thin,
评委们想要的脆壳。
crisp shell the judges will be looking for.
温度下降了。我们要重新开始。
The temperature's off. We're going to start again.
你想要那种嘎吱嘎吱的感觉。我不想要什么东西
You want that crunch and snap, though. Don't want something where
你吃的时候会咬断牙齿的。
you're going to break your teeth when you eat it.
但扯得太细了，
But pulled too thin,
果仁馅料可能不会停留在糖果的中心。
and the praline filling may not stay in the centre of the sweet.
这个问题非常非常难。
This one is very, very difficult.
我对此非常满意。我是说，这是我工作中最难的部分。
I'm super happy with this. I mean, there was the harder part of my job.
是的，我能看到一些。
Yeah, I can see some here.
大厨们，爱还会在空气中停留一小时。
Chefs, love is in the air for one more hour.
如果我们不动的话，我们就会有点哔哔声了。
We're going to be a little bit in the BLEEP if we don't move.
我们需要继续努力，全力以赴。
We need to crack on, big-time.
我们必须集合，所以时间肯定很紧。
We have to assemble, so definitely going to be tight on time.
为了建造他们的样板，
In order to build their showpiece,
摄制组现在必须重新引入可能致命的高温
the teams will now have to reintroduce potentially lethal heat...
我们完蛋了……快速冷却…
We're doomed. ..and rapid cooling...
. .他们精心构造的糖元素。
..to their delicately constructed sugar elements.
对，很好，很直。等等，不，不，不。哔哔声。
Yeah, that's nice and straight. Wait, no, no, no. BLEEP.
我们还有时间。把它粘上!
We've got time. Stick it on!
它很好。
It's fine.
漂亮的一个。
Nice one.
你说它是直的。
You said it was straight.
看起来……如果你从这里看。
It looks... If you look at it from here.
也许是这里的花，上面的鸟。
Maybe the flower here, the bird on the top.
哔哔声。也许更多一点。是的。
BLEEP. Maybe a bit more. Yeah.
哦，别碰，如果它裂开了…
Oh, don't touch, if it splits...
有点易碎，不是吗?是的，它很脆弱。
It's a bit fragile, no? Yeah, it's very fragile.
我把它放进微波炉。不可能。我来做。
I put it in the microwave. No way. I'll do it.
它一点也不直。
It's not straight at all.
是的，因为它现在在转弯。
Yeah, because it's now turning.
稍等一下。
Just hold on a minute.
因为我举起了它。
Cos I was lifting that.
挑战。这是我今天做的第四次了。
Challenge. The fourth one I've done today.
大厨们，你们还有十分钟。
Chefs, you've got ten minutes left now.
十分钟。小心我的头发。
Ten minutes. Watch out for my hair.
是的。我想把这个摆到桌子上。
Yeah. I want to get this on the table.
哦,上帝。
Oh, God.
把聚苯乙烯靠近点。
Bring the polystyrene closer.
我一点也不喜欢这个。
Don't like this at all.
它在倾斜，不是吗?
It is leaning, isn't it?
比萨斜塔是倾斜的。
Well, the Tower of Pisa leaned.
它还在上面。把它放在上面。
It's still up. Put it on the top.
它会断裂的。是的。
It's going to break. Yeah.
上面放不下。把它放在那里。
Can't fit on top. Put it there.
忘了中间那颗心吧。
You know, forget about the heart in the middle.
忘了那个吧。
Forget about that.
给我大量的胶水。
Just give me loads of glue.
不，它撑不住的。
No, it's not going to hold on.
把胶水给我。把它贴在上面，没事的。
Just give me the glue. Just stick it on that, it's fine.
要么做，要么什么都不做。
It's either this or nothing.
这个怎么样?
What about this one?
别操之过急啊。
Don't bloody rush it for the sake of it.
我们需要一些东西来支撑它。
We need something to lean it on.
你知道吗?一个罐子里。
Do you know what? A jar.
大厨们，你们还有一分钟。
Chefs, you have one minute left.
这是一分钟。
That's one minute.
我觉得看起来不错。是的，很好。
I think that looks good. Yeah, it's good.
这太热了。它把茎融化了。
This is too hot. It's melting the stems.
你把所有的糖果都带上了吗?
Have you got all the sweets on?
好的，让我们移动，把剩下的放在底部。
Right, let's move - hold the rest of it at the bottom of that.
每次我看到它，都会吓到我。
This freaks me out, every time I look at it.
但它没动，对吧?
It's not moving, though, is it?
否则它现在已经倒下了。
Otherwise it would have fallen by now.
哦,不!
Oh, no!
我的天。
My days.
为什么会发生在他们身上?
Why did that happen to them?
哦,不。
Oh no.
时间到了。
Time is up.
该坐下了。
Time for a sit.
五个令人惊叹的浪漫秀
Five stunning romantic showpieces
还有一次毁灭性的分手
and one devastating break-up
现在由珍爱和伯努瓦来评判。
will now be judged by Cherish and Benoit.
你在一个糖的展示中加入了很多技术，这真的是
You put a lot of technique into one sugar showpiece which is really
做得很好。这花真漂亮。
well done. The flower is really attractive.
它是人们关注的中心。
It is the centre of attention.
这条缎带很漂亮。
This ribbon is beautiful.
可爱的曲线。
Lovely curves.
干得好。你的黄玫瑰，告诉我们里面有什么?
So well done. Your yellow roses, tell us what's in it?
杏仁杏仁蛋白软糖。
Almond marzipan with apricot.
我不得不说，它们看起来很漂亮。
I have to say, they look pretty.
杏仁蛋白软糖非常湿润，非常好吃。
Marzipan is really moist and it's really nice.
如果你能在里面多放一点杏，我会更喜欢它。
If you could have put a little bit more apricot in it I would have enjoyed it more.
是的。拉出来的糖甜甜的，有一种美好的优雅。
Yeah. Pulled sugar sweet, there is a good elegance to it.
就味道而言，花粉是可爱的。
Flavour-wise, the pollen is lovely.
伯努瓦说明了一切。我觉得糖有点厚，
Benoit says it all. I think the sugar is a little bit thicker,
然而，我喜欢中间的金色。
however, I like the gold in between.
谢谢你！谢谢,厨师。
Thank you. Thanks, chefs.
没关系。
That was all right.
这件作品向后倾斜，但我认为它很优雅。
The piece is tilting towards the back but I think it's elegant.
不过你做得很好
You did very well, however,
现在它只是堆积起来，我看不到美丽的
at the moment it's just piling up and I cannot see the beauty of the
你送给我们的糖果。
confectionery that you present us.
这是草莓橙杏仁蛋白软糖，配上橘子酱
So this the strawberry and orange marzipan with an orange confit
在中间。
in the centre.
杏仁软糖不太油腻，而且我有你喜欢的橘子味。
The marzipan is not too greasy and I've got your orange flavour.
我根本尝不出草莓的味道，但我不喜欢这种果酱。
I could not taste strawberry at all, but I don't like the confit.
你的拉糖很甜。
Your pulled sugar sweet.
我确实尝出了你放在中间的果仁糖的味道。
I do taste the praline that you put in the centre.
中间有脆脆的口感。
I've got the crunchiness in the middle.
你走的方向是对的。
You are going in the right direction.
把罐子移到一边看看。
Slide the jar to the side and see.
他迅速地呼了一口气
HE EXHALES RAPIDLY
你看起来开心多了。我是。
You look already happier. I am.
每次我看到你的作品都有故事。我知道
There's always a story when I look at your showpiece. I know it's
浪漫，我知道那是情人节，我知道那是爱情。
romance, I know that it is Valentine, I know that it's love.
那辆双门轿车真漂亮。
That coupe is beautiful.
把它放在那上面会是一流的。
This sitting on that would have been top notch.
玫瑰，草莓，开心果。
It's a rose, strawberry with a pistachio top.
配上那些小燕尾服外套看起来很漂亮。
It looks quite nice with those little tuxedo jackets.
玫瑰慢慢绽放，
The rose kicks in slowly,
所以它不会像你吃一块肥皂那样强烈。
so it's not overpowering like you're eating a bar of soap.
糖甜。
Sugar sweet.
对我来说，果仁糖绝对是美味的。
So for me the praline is absolutely lovely.
烤得恰到好处，榛子香味扑鼻。
Perfectly roasted, I got the hazelnut, it's full of fragrance.
非常感谢。两人:谢谢。
Thank you very much. BOTH: Thank you.
你满意吗?是的。
Are you happy with that? Yeah.
你的心脏的形状，嗯，这是一个基本形状，
Your heart shape, well, it's a basic shape,
那么，我们是如何做到不把它弄得很整洁的呢?
so how do we manage to not get it very neat and tidy?
我不知道，至于吹糖，形状完全不对。
That I don't know, and as far as the blown sugar, the shape is all wrong.
对我来说，是鸟嘴。你用手指夹住鸟嘴。
For me, it's the beak. You pinch the beak between your finger flat.
这不是一只天鹅。是的，这更像是达菲鸭的嘴。
This is not a swan. This is more of a Daffy Duck kind of beak, yes.
底部是橙色杏仁软糖。
Orange marzipan on the bottom.
上面是开心果。
On the top, pistachio.
当我看着它的时候，我觉得它没有投入太多的工作。
When I look at it I think there's not much work put into it.
桔子的味道很好。
The taste of orange is quite pleasant.
话虽如此，它还是压倒了其他一切。
Having said that, it takes over everything else.
我已经有了足够的味道，我知道这是果仁糖，但我觉得还不够。
I've got enough flavour, I know it's a praline but I think not enough.
我想我是那个倒霉的人，我没有看到任何填充物。
I guess I'm the unlucky one, I don't see any sort of filling.
哦。我想这是我的错。
Oh. I think it's my fault.
不，别这样。把它加热得太热了，还不够冷。
No, come on. Warm it up too much, and didn't cool enough.
我很喜欢它。你骄傲地站起来说"这就是我，
I quite like it. You stand up very proudly and you say "This is me,
"是我干的"没多少人会这么做。
"I did it," and not many people would do that.
挑战的最后20分钟你一直在加所以基础在哪里
The last 20 minutes of the challenge you keep on adding so the base where
你的心脏还没有完全冷却，
your heart was actually standing wasn't completely cooled,
所以继续前进，继续前进，最终——轰。
so keep on moving, keep on moving and eventually - boom.
你能带我们去拿你的杏仁糖吗?
Could you please take us to your marzipan.
这是一种百香果。
It's a passion fruit.
吐司是用什么做的?
What is the toast made from?
杏仁加罂粟籽。
Almond with poppy seed.
你们这些家伙总是想出一些时髦的设计，这是一个饼干。
You guys always come up with funky design and this is a cracker.
我喜欢这个。
I love this.
百香果和里面的油酥饼
The passion fruit with that little confit you have got inside
简直令人惊叹。做得很好。
is just stunning. Well done.
糖甜。
Sugar sweet.
我很喜欢你揉糖的样子。
Really like the way you twist your pulled sugar.
你能找到果仁糖吗?
Can you find any praline in there?
有一种果仁糖的味道，实际上很不错。
There is a taste of the praline and it is actually quite nice.
我想我是那个倒霉的人，我在里面找不到果仁糖。
I think I've been the unlucky one, I could not find any praline in it.
我很期待吃这些，因为它们看起来很漂亮。
I was so looking forward to eating these because they look so pretty.
谢谢厨师们。谢谢你！
Thank you, chefs. Thank you.
小声说:做个三明治。做一个三明治。
WHISPERED: Make a sandwich. Make a sandwich.
噢，蛋黄掉进我的衬衫里了!
Oh, the yolk's gone down my shirt!
做得很好。做得很好。
Well done. Well done.
你做了一些技巧，
You did a couple of techniques,
然而，我认为它执行得很糟糕。
however, I think it's really poorly executed.
你想做的太多了。你的思维过程是，
You're trying to do too much. Your thought process is,
"我要做一件极其复杂的事"
"I'm going to do something extremely complicated",
但在这种情况下，你无法做到。
but for that instance you can't pull it off.
你的杏仁蛋白软糖。
Your marzipan.
酸樱桃杏仁蛋白软糖。
So, sour cherry marzipan.
里面有一个开心果杏仁糖。
And inside it has a pistachio marzipan.
它还有一个巧克力梗。
It has a little chocolate stem as well.
哦,tra-la-la。今天不是在这里炼巧克力的日子。
Oh, tra-la-la. Today was not the day to temper chocolate in here.
每次我们进来，都有借口。
Every time we come in, there is excuses.
让我们品味。
Let's taste.
我的大脑让我吃樱桃，
My brain is asking me to eat cherry,
但我的味蕾并没有问我里面有樱桃。
but my taste bud is not asking me that there is cherry in there.
好的。
OK.
至于果仁糖，你看到了吗?
As for the praline, do you see any?
不。我在挣扎。
No. I'm struggling.
我也是。我可以舔一点。
Me too. I can lick a little bit.
太遗憾了，这么辛苦
It's a shame, with struggling so much
为了找到咸花生布朗尼，
to find a salted peanut brownie,
因为当我拥有它的时候，它终于变得美丽了。
because when I had it, finally it was beautiful.
非常感谢。
Thank you very much.
我很抱歉。你可以品尝到樱桃的味道。
I'm sorry. You can taste cherry in there.
我不管他们怎么说，你能尝到樱桃的味道。
I don't care what they say, you can taste cherry.
不管怎样，收拾行李，我们要回家了。
Anyway, pack your bags, we're going home.
根据今天的展品和昨天的微缩模型，
Based on today's showpiece, and yesterday's miniatures,
珍惜和伯努瓦现在要给队伍排序，
Cherish and Benoit must now rank the teams,
最后一名将被淘汰。
and those in last place will be leaving the competition.
我们想我们已经出局了。
We think we are out from now.
你在最后一刻才把所有东西凑在一起，
You stick everything together at the last minute,
任何事情都没有时间冷静下来。
nothing has time to cool down correctly.
我不期待下一个挑战，我想。
I am not looking forward to go to the next challenge, I think.
也许我们要退出比赛了。
Probably we are going to leave the competition.
我们接受命运，木已成舟，
We'll accept our fate, what's done is done,
但我认为我们今天没有尽力。
but I don't think we did our best today.
我们有更多的东西可以奉献。我知道我们有。
We have a lot more to give. I know we do.
第一名的队伍在比赛中彻底失败了
The team in first place absolutely blew the competition
带着他们的维也纳音乐从水里出来
out of the water with their Viennoiserie,
恭喜你们，琳恩和罗曼，
congratulations, Leanne and Romain,
来自皇家咖啡厅的选手，你们晋级了四分之一决赛。
from Hotel Cafe Royal, you are through to the quarterfinal.
伊曼纽尔和山姆位居第二，和他们一起进入四分之一决赛
Emmanuel and Sam are in second, and joining them in the quarterfinals
Darryl和Bharat排在第三。
are Darryl and Bharat in third.
第四名是……
In fourth place we have...
来自萨沃伊的艾迪和马希德。
Eddie and Mahshid from the Savoy.
那就只剩下甜蜜艺术实验室的Hideko和Theo，
Which leaves Hideko and Theo from Sweet Art Lab,
还有R巧克力店的斯拉夫和玛丽亚。
and Slav and Maria from R Chocolate.
经过深思熟虑，
After much deliberation,
评委们决定今晚离开我们的队伍是…
the judges decided that the team leaving us tonight are...
R巧克力店的斯拉夫和玛丽亚。
Slav and Maria from R Chocolate.
很遗憾你要走了。
Sorry to see you go.
祝贺你们其余的人
Congratulations to the rest of you,
我们期待下周与您见面。
and we look forward to seeing you next week.
你让我笑了很多。是的。
You've made me smile a lot. Yeah.
我为我们取得的成就感到非常自豪。
I am very proud of what we have achieved.
我们都没想到会走那么远。
We didn't each expect to go that much far.
离开很难过，但我觉得这很棒，
It's sad to go, but I think it has been amazing,
引用这首歌的歌词:“杀不死你的，会让你更强大。”
and to quote the song, "What doesn't kill you makes you stronger."
所以…当然可以。
So... Of course.
HIDEKO:我真不敢相信!
HIDEKO: I can't believe it!
我们又活下来了!
We survived again!
非常高兴。做得很好。
Very happy. Well done.
如果我们在四分之一决赛中出局，那就让我们大干一场吧，
If we go out in the quarterfinals let's go out with a bang,
不管是展品倒下了，还是我们做出了可怕的东西，
whether it's the showpiece falling down or we make something horrible,
让我们轰轰烈烈地结束吧。
let's just go out with a bang.
下次，四分之一决赛。
Next time - the quarterfinals.
就差这么近了。
Getting so close now.
层层叠叠的马卡龙蛋糕……
A towering tiered macaron cake...
希望它不会倒塌。
Hope it doesn't collapse.
. .和一个梦幻般的童话展示…
..and a fantastical fairy tale showpiece...
你相信有仙女吗，珍爱?
You believe in fairies, Cherish?
是的，我当然相信有仙女。
Yes, of course I believe in fairy.
. .意味着一个团队的梦想……发出哔哔声
..means one team's dream... BLEEP
. .会变成一场噩梦。破解是什么?
..will become a nightmare. What's cracking?
哦，拜托，伙计!
Oh come on, man!
字幕由红蜂传媒制作
Subtitles by Red Bee Media
欢迎回到《职业烘焙大赛》，只剩下五支队伍，争夺四个席位
Welcome back to Bake Off: The Professionals, where just five teams remain, battling for the four spaces
在下周的半决赛中。
in next week's semifinal.
不仅如此，本周我们的主题是童年，
And not only that - this week, our theme is childhood,
所以我们的厨师将带我们回到婴儿时期的简单时光。
so our chefs will be taking us back to the simpler times of our infancy.
还记得童年吗，利亚姆?我当然知道。我现在已经是个孩子了，兄弟。
Remember childhood, Liam? Course I do. I'm pretty much a kid now, bro.
他咯咯地笑着玩捉迷藏。玩国际足联。
HE CHUCKLES Playing Hide and Seek. Playing Fifa.
骑着我的小三轮车。穿着高跟鞋嗖嗖地走来走去。
Riding round on my little tricycle. Whizzing around in heely shoes.
唱一圈一圈的玫瑰。看歌舞青春。
Singing Ring a Ring O' Roses. Watching High School Musical.
天啊，我太老了，利亚姆!我太老了!
Oh, God, I'm so old, Liam! I'm so old!
你看起来有点劳累过度。我不累，利亚姆!
You seem a little bit overtired. I'm not tired, Liam!
来吧，我们开始挑战吧，这样你就可以睡个午觉了，好吗?
Come on, let's just start the challenge so you can have a nap, OK?
好的，谢谢，利亚姆。
Yeah, I'd like that, thanks, Liam.
最后一次……
Last time...
哔哔声。. .爱情的光芒在浪漫的糖果展示中暗淡下来。
BLEEP. ..The love light dimmed in a romantic sugarwork showpiece.
因为我是BLEEP。我们提供BLEEP。
Because I was BLEEP. We were serving BLEEP.
绝对的哔哔声。
Absolute BLEEP.
Leanne和Romain的设计和口味…
Leanne and Romain's design and flavours...
它是美丽的。一流的。
It's beautiful. Top-notch.
. .事实证明他们是天作之合。
..Proved to be a match made in heaven.
啊!
Ah!
当灾难袭来时……对不起!
While disaster struck... Sorry!
. .让英子和西奥伤心欲绝。
..Leaving Hideko and Theo broken-hearted.
但是斯拉夫和玛丽亚没有感受到爱……
But it was Slav and Maria who failed to feel the love...
我不会吃的，因为那样会咬断我的牙齿。
I'm not going to eat it because that would break my teeth.
很遗憾你要走了。
Sorry to see you go.
. .成为最后一支退出比赛的队伍。
..and became the latest team to leave the competition.
你让我笑了很多。
You've made me smile a lot.
我为我们取得的成就感到非常自豪。
I'm very proud of what we have achieved.
这一次……哦，它裂开了。
This time... Oh, it's cracking.
. .四分之一决赛……就差这么近了。
..The quarterfinal... Getting so close now.
. .把球队带回到童年……
..takes the teams back to childhood...
只要它不坍塌就行。
As long as it doesn't collapse.
. .作为一个分层的马卡龙蛋糕，引发了愤怒……
..As a tiered macaron cake that sparks a tantrum...
那你来吧。耶稣基督。哔哔声。
You do it, then. Jesus Christ. BLEEP.
. .还有一个规模迷人的童话展示…
..and a fairy tale showpiece on an enchanting scale...
哔哔声。哔哔声。
BLEEP. BLEEP.
. .让他们去面对自己的命运。
..Leave them to face their fates.
我喜欢这个。
I love this.
哪四支队伍会从此幸福地生活在一起?
Which four teams will live happily ever after?
我一点也不喜欢吃。哔哔声。
I didn't enjoy eating it at all. BLEEP.
谁的冒险即将结束?
And whose adventure is about to end?
啊!
Argh!
四分之一决赛周。
Quarterfinal week.
在开始比赛的12支队伍中，只剩下了5支。
Of the 12 teams who started the competition, just five remain.
欢迎回来，大厨们。
Welcome back, chefs.
进入半决赛的机会已经唾手可得了。
A place in the semifinals really is within your grasp.
就差两个挑战了。
Just two challenges away.
评委们，这是多么可怕的噩梦啊
Judges, what terrifyingly nightmarish task
你今天为我们准备好了吗?
have you set for us today?
我想让你做一个马卡龙蛋糕，至少有两种馅料，
I would like you to make a macaron cake, with at least two fillings,
灵感来自你童年的味道。
inspired by flavours from your childhood.
你必须为至少24人服务，
You must serve a minimum of 24 people,
至少有两层。
and feature at least two tiers.
是啊，还记得你小时候要做双层的吗
Yeah, remember when you were a child and you had to make that two-tier
马卡龙展示蛋糕?我想我们在小熊队就做到了。
macaron display cake? I think we did it in Cubs.
还有，珍爱，你想布置什么任务?
And Cherish, what assignment would you like to set?
我想要两种不同的甜品，
I would like to have two different types of sucettes,
都是棒棒糖形状的小四。
all lollipop-shaped petit four.
各18个，总共36个。
18 of each, 36 in total.
厨师们，祝你们好运。你会需要它的。
Good luck, chefs. You are going to need it.
你有3.5小时的时间来完成今天的挑战，
You have 3.5 hours to complete today's challenge,
你的时间从现在开始。
and your time starts now.
现在我们进入了四分之一决赛，显然，压力开始增加。
Now we're in the quarterfinals, obviously, the pressure starts to build.
我和伊曼纽尔都能在压力下茁壮成长，所以我们应该没问题。
Me and Emmanuel both thrive under pressure, so we should be all right.
童年周不会全是娱乐和游戏。
Childhood Week won't be all fun and games.
今天是我们要做的事情最多的一天。
Today's the day when we have the most ever to do.
四分之一决赛选手不仅要合理安排时间，
Not only must the quarterfinalists manage their time properly,
重要的是它们能把味道表现出来
it's crucial they deliver on the flavours
还有他们童年的故事。
and stories of their childhood.
我们让他们做马卡龙蛋糕因为马卡龙已经
We've asked them to do a macaron cake because a macaron is already
做起来很棘手，但在比赛的这个阶段，
tricky enough to do, but at this stage of the competition,
在四分之一决赛中，我们希望他们做一个更大的版本。
in the quarterfinal, we want them to do a larger version of that.
出错的地方可能是用了错误的方法来制作马卡龙。
What could go wrong is use the wrong technique of piping your macaron.
这个小技巧就是不要用管子把贝壳管起来，
The little trick is not to pipe a shell,
但是要把马卡龙做成螺旋状
but to pipe the macaron in a spiral motion
让它更容易切和烤。
and make it easy to cut and to bake.
如果烤得不对，
If it's not baked correctly,
它会裂开，不好看，也不开胃。
it will crack and it's not going to be very pretty or appetising.
将磨碎的杏仁和糖粉折叠成搅打过的蛋白，
Made by folding ground almonds and icing sugar into whipped egg whites,
自16世纪以来，马卡龙一直是法国糕点的主食。
the macaron has been a staple of French patisserie since the 16th century...
我们经常吃的东西。
Something we are used to eating quite often.
基本上就像牛角面包。
It's like croissant, basically.
. .这给了我们海峡对岸的表亲一点优势。
..giving our cousins from across the Channel a slight advantage.
我们确实做了很多，但都是小号的。
We do make a lot of them, but they tend to be petit four size.
我们很少做大的24件，所以，是的，
We rarely made a large 24 pieces, so, yes,
这将会有点挑战性。
it's going to be a bit challenging.
为了纪念伊曼纽尔在法国农村的成长经历，
Paying tribute to Emmanuel's rural French upbringing,
希尔顿公园巷的焦糖香蕉
Hilton Park Lane's caramelised banana
还有白巧克力甘纳许蛋糕
and white chocolate ganache cake
回忆起儿时激发他灵感的味道。
recalls flavours that inspired him as a boy.
我有个朋友从一个岛上来。
I had a friend who was coming from an island.
他的母亲会用很多异国水果，比如香蕉，
His mother would have used a lot of exotic fruit like banana,
在我老家的村子里，我们是不会用这种东西的
which, from the village where I come from, was not something we would use
当时有很多。
a lot of at the time.
控制它们混合物的稠度是至关重要的。
Managing the consistency of their mixture is crucial.
如果折叠得不够充分，马卡龙就会致密且不均匀。
If it's not folded enough, the macaron will be dense and uneven.
放太多，在烤箱里就会塌。
Too much, and it will collapse in the oven.
它们看起来很简单，但做起来却很困难。
They looks simple, but they are quite a hard thing to make.
我只是尽可能地把它敲出来，这样我就能得到一个光滑的
I'm just banging it out as much as I can so I get a nice smooth
一致性。你会看到它创造了一个漂亮的，
consistency. You'll see it creates that nice, like,
丝带的效果。它们会叠在一起，
ribbon effect. It'll sit on top of each other,
这就是我要找的。
that's what I'm looking for.
我们今天要做的是异域风味的马卡龙。
We're going for quite an exotic macaron flavour today.
里面会有一种柑橘味的凝乳。
Inside we're going to have a very, like, citrusy curd.
还有萨沃伊凝乳，柚子和血橙果冻
Along with the Savoy's curd, a grapefruit and blood orange jelly
会坐在一个有灵感的蛋糕里吗
will sit inside a cake that's inspired
马希德在伊朗的成长经历
by Mahshid's upbringing in Iran.
柑橘，坚果，我们在伊朗吃很多水果。
Citrus, nuts, we eat a lot of fruit in Iran.
这个挑战很棒，所以我可以把所有的东西都结合起来
This challenge is great, so I can incorporate everything
从我的童年到这个挑战。
from my childhood into this challenge.
希望评委们会喜欢。
Hopefully, the judges will like them.
虽然每个人都在寻找自己成长时期的灵感，
While everyone is looking to their formative years for inspiration,
“童年周”特别有利于一个团队。
Childhood Week plays into the hands of one team in particular.
英子和西奥!你好，你好，你好，你好!你好!
Hideko and Theo! Hello, hello, hello, hello! Hello!
你的主题常常很幼稚。
Your theme is often very childlike.
这周的主题是童年，
Well, this week the theme is actually childhood,
所以你要做些非常成人的事吗，
so are you going to do something very adult,
比如抵押贷款申请之类的?
maybe like a mortgage application or something?
这是你闪耀的机会。
This is your chance to shine.
甜蜜艺术实验室的机会就在蛋糕上了
Sweet Art Lab's chances will rest on a cake
灵感来自西奥在马赛的童年。
inspired by Theo's childhood in Marseille.
覆盆子马卡龙会被层层的荔枝和覆盆子分开
Raspberry macarons will be separated by layers of lychee and raspberry
克雷默和他精致的木槿果冻。
cremeux and his delicate hibiscus jelly.
你小时候吃过荔枝和芙蓉花吗?
As a child, you had lychees and hibiscus flowers?
对我来说，这听起来很复杂。
To me, it sounds very sophisticated.
我是个世故的孩子!
I was a sophisticated kid!
然而，想到琳恩和罗曼的蛋糕，
What springs to mind with Leanne and Romain's cake, however,
不那么复杂，更简单。
is less sophistication and more snackette.
我们要做我儿时最爱的花生棒。
We're doing my favourite childhood peanut bar.
很有坚果味，
It is very nutty,
所以如果你喜欢花生，你会喜欢它，如果你不喜欢，
so if you like peanuts you're going to like it and if you don't,
你可能不会。我们对这些味道很满意。
you probably won't. We are happy with the flavours.
如果一切按计划进行，那么是的，希望一切顺利。
If everything goes to plan, then yeah, hopefully, it'll all go well.
而其他队蛋糕的糖味应该会让评委们感到满意
While the sugar hit of the other teams' cakes should keep the judges
醒着的时候，名胜世界可以让他们入睡。
awake, Resorts World's could send them to sleep.
我最喜欢的童年记忆之一是麦乳饮料
One of my favourite childhood memories was the malted milk drinks
所以我用的是麦乳精
at bedtime, so I'm using malted milk
还有咸焦糖和一点巧克力。
and salted caramel and a bit of chocolate.
毫米毫米!我今天会觉得很累。
Mm-mm! I'll be feeling tired today.
马卡龙的馅料是杏仁巧克力海绵。
My filling for my macaron, it's an almond and chocolate sponge.
它也会对结构有帮助，所以它不会倒塌在我身上。
It will help with the structure, as well, so it won't collapse on me.
传统上，马卡龙被做成小的管状圆顶，
Traditionally, macarons are cooked as small, piped domes,
但在这么大的规模上，
but on a scale as large as this,
团队必须以不同的方式做事。
the teams must do things differently.
慢慢走，慢慢走。
Go slowly, go slowly.
在薄螺旋盘上加管可以使烤得均匀。
Piping a thin spiral disk allows an even bake.
除此之外的任何东西都可能会留下湿漉漉的底部。
Anything other than this may leave a soggy bottom.
烤好的时候，应该还有螺旋状。
When they're baked, they should still have the spiral.
伯努瓦说得很清楚，这才是他想要的。
Benoit made it clear, actually, that's what he's looking for.
他们想看到螺旋。
They want to see the spiral.
你为什么吹口哨?为了马卡龙蛋糕。
Why are you piping? For the macaron cake.
我知道这不是通常的做法，
I know it's not how it's normally done,
但这是我习惯的做法。
but this is how I'm used to doing it.
放进去五分钟。
Put it in for five minutes.
马卡龙放入烤箱后，精确的时间是至关重要的。
Once the macarons are in the oven, precision timing is essential.
有了这么精致的混合物，
With such a delicate mixture,
煮熟和未煮熟之间的差别可能是几秒钟。
the difference between over and undercooked can be seconds.
他们有十分钟的时间，然后我就去开门。
They're going to have ten minutes, then I'm going to open up the door.
然后我要移动它们，
Then I'm going to move them about,
然后他们还有八到十分钟的时间。
then they're going to have another eight to ten minutes.
把它们取出来太快，它们就会被
Take them out too soon and they'll collapse under the weight of
馅料。放太久会碎的。
the fillings. Leave them too long and they'll shatter.
我花了20分钟，
I've put 20 minutes on it,
很有可能每边都要多花5分钟。
and very likely something like five minutes more for each side.
厨师们，你们已经有两个小时了，还剩下一个半小时。
You've had two hours, chefs, and you've got 1.5 hours left.
团队不仅要制作出完美无瑕、优雅分层的马卡龙蛋糕……
Not only must the teams produce a flawless and elegant tiered macaron cake...
. .它必须附有十六块蛋糕。
..It must be accompanied by trente-six sucettes.
对你和我来说是36个棒棒糖。
That's 36 lollipops to you and me.
现在是四分之一决赛了。
It's the quarterfinal now.
我不想看无聊的棒棒糖。
I do not want to see a boring lollipop.
我想看到乐趣，我想看到色彩，
I want to see fun, I want to see colour,
我想看到美妙的味道。
I want to see fantastic flavour.
我想让他们把童年的一切都展现出来。
I want them to bring out whatever they had in their childhood.
这些团队可以自由地使用任何技术来生产他们的成功产品，
The teams are free to use any technique to produce their sucettes,
然而，Benoit和珍惜不仅会评判味道，
however, Benoit and Cherish will not only be judging flavour,
他们也会评估创新和想象力。
they'll be assessing innovation and imagination, too.
我正在把融资费的混合物塞进模具里。
I'm just piping the financier mix into the flexi-moulds.
它就像一个小蛋糕，一个小蛋糕放在棍子上。
It's just like a small cake, a small cake on a stick.
就像一个华丽的棒棒糖蛋糕。
It's like a fancy cake pop.
除了法式法式蛋糕风格的金融家棒棒糖蛋糕，
Along with their French patisserie-inspired financier cake pops,
艾迪和马希德会献上牛奶巧克力甜糖，里面装满
Eddie and Mahshid will present milk chocolate sucettes filled with
柠檬焦糖咖啡奶油。
a lemon caramel and coffee cremeux.
你的两个棒棒糖会很无聊吗?
Are your two lollipops going to be quite dull?
不，味道会说话的。
No, the flavours will speak for themselves.
味道很好。所以你没看到什么吗?
The flavours are great. So it's nothing on the visual with you?
你已经放弃视觉效果了?
You've given up on the visual?
不，看起来会很漂亮，但不会太夸张。
No, it will look nice, but it won't go over the top.
自信,Mahshid !是的。是啊!
Confident, Mahshid! Yes. Yeah!
艾迪和马希德专注于法国风味，
While Eddie and Mahshid focus on French flavours,
山姆在重现英国经典。
Sam's recreating a British classic.
这只是一件香草色的貂皮
This is just a vanilla sable
苹果大黄碎棒棒糖的外皮。
for the outside of our apple rhubarb crumble lollies.
作为英国人，大多数英国家庭都会这样做
Being English, most English families would have
在星期天的烧烤晚餐后吃苹果酥。
apple crumble on a Sunday after a roast dinner.
它确实给我带来了很多回忆。
It definitely brings back a lot of memories for me.
和Sam一样，Hideko也从家里的舒适中获得灵感。
Like Sam, Hideko's also taking inspiration from the comforts of home.
你小时候吃过胡萝卜蛋糕吗?当然!
You had carrot cake when you were little? Of course!
在日本吗?
In Japan?
牛轧糖好了。
The nougat's ready.
在巴拉特的糖果店，健康的选择更有限。
In Bharat's sweet shop, the healthy options are a little more limited.
当我还是个孩子的时候，我喜欢牛轧糖。
When I was a kid, I used to love nougat.
总是有一个大包装的粉白色牛轧糖。
There was always a pink and white nougat in a big packet.
哦，我喜欢牛轧糖。你今天要做这个吗?
Oh, I love nougat. So are you making that today?
是的。哦，哇，我们正在寻找一个款待!
Yeah. Oh, wow, we are looking up for a treat!
除了爱吃甜食，
As well as a sweet tooth,
巴拉特也迎合了昂贵的口味，
Bharat's also catering for expensive tastes,
配上黑巧克力和橘子软糖
with dark chocolate and mandarin orange gel sucettes
它们被金箔包裹着。
that are encased in gold leaf.
这是最贵的吗?
Is that going to be the most expensive?
可能是吧。
It probably is, yeah.
就像23克拉的金箔。噢!哇!听起来富有。
It's like 23-carat gold leaf. Ooh! Wow! Sounds rich.
我的牙齿能钻过去吗?
Will I be able to get my teeth through it?
是的，你可以有一颗金牙。
Yeah, you can have a gold tooth.
你要完成你的品尝…!
You are going to finish your tasting...!
这个挑战有这么多元素，
With so many elements to this challenge,
琳恩和罗曼可能找到了捷径。
Leanne and Romain may have hit upon a short cut.
我在给其中一个棒棒糖做小马卡龙。
I'm just piping the mini macarons for one of the lollipops.
未曾?我听到的是马卡龙吗?
Macaron? Did I hear "macaron"?
我以为你选的是大马卡龙。
I thought you were picking the big macaron.
我们也在做小的。
We're making small ones, as well.
这算作弊吗?我分两批做。
Is that cheating? I'm making the two separate batches.
琳恩的第二份马卡龙
Leanne's second serving of macarons
会配上几块橙子泡过的“基因之痛”吗
will be accompanied by sucettes of orange-soaked Pain de Genes
还有橘子馅饼，
and mandarin pate de fruit,
最后是黑巧克力橙甘纳许。
finished with a dark chocolate orange ganache.
这是一块海绵，上面有橘子果冻，
So, it's a sponge with basically orange jelly on top,
外层是黑巧克力，对吗，琳恩?
with a dark chocolate covering, is that right, Leanne?
是的。听起来很有创意。
Yeah. That sounds very, um, original.
听起来像雅法蛋糕!嘘!
It sounds like a Jaffa Cake! Shh!
大厨们，你们还有一个小时!
Chefs, you have one hour left!
那是一个小时!目前，一切都很顺利。
That's one hour! For now, it's going all right.
有很多事要做，所以…还有很多事要做。
A lot to do, you know, so... Still a lot to do.
这是现在的一大推动力。
It's the big push now.
这是棒棒糖的小马卡龙。
This is the small macaron for the lollipop.
是的，我对这些很满意。
Yeah, I'm really happy with these.
我只是在填充巧克力壳的底部
I'm just filling the base of our chocolate shells
加上柠檬焦糖，
with the lemon caramel,
最后再淋上咖啡奶油。
and then I'm going to top it off with the coffee cremeux.
只有喜欢咖啡的人才会喜欢这个。
You have to love coffee to love this.
所以它就像24bharat黄金…
So it's like a 24-Bharat gold...
24-Bharat !24-BHARAT黄金!
24-Bharat! 24-BHARAT gold!
当团队构建他们的成功时…
As the teams construct their sucettes...
. .现在是马卡龙的关键时刻。
..It's crunch time for their macarons.
我把这些拿出来。
Let me just take these out.
是的，是的，是的，是的。
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
好吗?看起来不错吧?
Good? They're looking good?
干够了吗?
Dry enough?
哔哔声。伙计，我需要个帮手。
BLEEP. Man, I'm going to need a hand.
拿点调色板。
Just get a little palette.
用小调色板把它刮出来。
Get a little palette to scrape this out.
马卡龙有点过了，
The macarons are slightly under,
所以我要多煮一点。
so I'm cooking them a little bit more.
你有时间吗?是的。
Are you good for time? Yeah.
只剩下做马卡龙了，就这样。
It's just the macaron left to build and that's it.
我们要开始组装了吗?
Are we going to start assembling?
那些烤了马卡龙的人可以继续组装他们的蛋糕。
Those with macarons baked can push on and assemble their cakes.
我只是在粘马卡龙，
I'm just sticking the macarons,
然后把最上面的一块放上去。
and then I'm going to lay the top bit on.
大厨们，你们还有15分钟!
Chefs, you have 15 minutes left!
还剩15分钟!
That's 15 minutes left!
他们需要冰箱。
They need the freezer.
温暖的马卡龙会融化里面的馅料
Warm macarons will melt their fillings
导致他们的蛋糕坍塌。
and cause their cake to collapse.
你能开始吹箫吗?
Can you start piping?
先做这个，这样我就可以用水果装饰了。
Do this one first so I can decorate it with the fruit.
我们现在已经很接近了。
We're getting so close now.
问题只是我们能否及时完成。
It's just whether we can get it done in time.
我希望它不会倒塌。
I hope it doesn't collapse.
不，我是说…漩涡。不要紧。
No, I meant...swirls. Never mind.
这对漩涡来说太大了。没关系，没关系。
It's too big for the swirls. Never mind, never mind.
哔哔声。的缘故!得了吧，伙计!
BLEEP. 'Sake! Oh, come on, man!
那你去吧!耶稣基督。
You do it, then! Jesus Christ.
哔哔声!
BLEEP!
现在看起来还不错。
It looks good at the moment.
我们还剩多久?
How long have we got left?
大厨们，你们还有五分钟，五分钟!
Chefs, you've got five minutes left, five minutes!
直接放进冰箱。
Straight into the fridge.
哔哔声。哎呀!。
BLEEP. Crikey.
希望法官也认为他们很完美。
Let's hope the judge thinks they're perfect, as well.
大厨们，你们的时间到了，时间到了!
Chefs, your time is up, your time is up!
请把你们的马卡龙放在工作台的末端
Please leave your macarons at the of end your workbenches
离他们远点。
and step away from them.
五层马卡龙蛋糕和180个蛋糕
Five tiered macaron cakes and 180 sucettes
只需要三个半小时。
in just three and a half hours.
现在两队等待伯努瓦和珍爱的评判。
Now the teams await the judgment of Benoit and cherish.
甜蜜艺术实验室的Hideko和Theo可以过来吗?
Can Hideko and Theo from Sweet Art Lab please come forward?
他们喘息
THEY GASP
哦，哈哈，哈哈…!
Oh, luh, luh...!
唷!!势如破竹般的增长
Phew! Whoof!
看来你今天过得很愉快啊。
Well, it looks like you've had a good day.
我喜欢你的马卡龙淡淡的颜色。
I like the subtle colour of your macaron.
那么，你能告诉我们我们得到了什么吗?
So, would you be able to tell us what we've have got?
嗯哼。
Mm-hmm.
好的。
OK.
是冻住了吗?是的，冻住了。
Is it frozen? Yeah, it's frozen.
所以你把它冻住了?是的。好的。
So you've built it frozen? Yes. OK.
就像冰淇淋马卡龙。
It's like an ice cream macaron.
真可惜。
What a shame.
味道，我很喜欢。
The taste, I really like.
但我感觉不到它的质地。毫米。
But I can't feel the texture. Mm.
现在，我有一块冰。
At the moment, I've got a block of ice.
如果你能让我相信这是冷冻点心，
If you could have sell me that this is a frozen entremets,
你做到了。
you nailed it.
棒棒糖……
Lollipop...
所以，深色的是橘色的
So, the dark one is a mandarin pain de fruit
配上伯爵茶和黑巧克力甘纳许。
with an Earl Grey tea and dark chocolate ganache.
我的第一印象是它们是巨大的。
My first impression is that they are humongous.
我要试试。不要看。
I'm going to try. Don't look.
它的味道和它的样子一样。它很重。
It tastes as it looks. It's very heavy.
胡萝卜蛋糕……
Carrot cake...
可爱的海绵，不太干，相当轻，
Lovely sponge, not too dry, fairly light,
但是糖霜有点干。
but the frosting is dry a little bit.
我觉得你能给我们更好的。
I think you can give us better than this.
从视觉上看，它很美。
Visually, it's beautiful.
你用巧克力装饰马卡龙真是太好了。
It's quite nice that you decorated your macaron with chocolate.
能给我们介绍一下你的口味吗，谢谢?
Could you take us through your flavour, please, thank you?
这是一种麦乳精奶油，里面有咸焦糖
It's a malted milk cremeux with salted caramel inside
还有巧克力杏仁海绵蛋糕。
and a chocolate almond sponge.
我喜欢它。
I love it.
我真的……它的工作原理。
I'm really... It works.
里面的味道，我不能一整天都吃这个。
The flavour profile in there, I can't have this all day.
我喜欢这个。这是我的一种渴望。毫米!
I love this. It's a craving I would get. Mm!
那棒棒糖呢?这是巧克力和橘子……
What about the lollipops? This is a chocolate and orange...
我吃的时候会紧张吗?
Am I actually nervous to eat it?
我不太确定我要不要金牙。
I'm not too sure if I want golden teeth.
我太年轻了，不会长金牙。
I'm too young for golden teeth.
嗯…太厚了。
Um... That's too thick.
是的。大部分都是一块黑巧克力，可能会很硬。
Yeah. Most of it is a chunk of dark chocolate, which can be very hard.
我喜欢吗?
Did I enjoy that?
毫米…不是真的。
Mm... Not really.
那是覆盆子开心果杏仁牛轧糖。
That's a raspberry, pistachio and almond nougat.
我认为执行力很差。
I think the execution is quite poor.
我们来尝尝吧?
Shall we taste?
我觉得有点软，适合我的口味，
I think it's a little bit soft for my liking,
而且到处都粘着。
and it's sticking everywhere as well.
我觉得我不太喜欢吃这个。
I don't think I really enjoy eating this.
他叹了口气:轮到我们了。
HE SIGHS It's our turn.
轮到我们哔哔声了。
Our turn for a BLEEP.
最后的润色在这里，你匆忙，
The finishing touches here, you rushed,
你是在努力按时完成，还是…?
you were struggling to finish on time, or...?
是啊，这些片段都是临时安排的。
Yeah, the segments were a very last-minute thing.
总的来说，看起来不太好。
Well, overall, doesn't look great.
提醒我们马卡龙蛋糕里有什么。
Remind us what's in the macaron cake.
里面有橙子海绵，柑橘凝乳，
Inside we have an orange sponge, citrus curd,
新鲜葡萄柚血橙果冻
a fresh grapefruit and blood orange jelly
外面是马斯卡彭尚蒂伊奶酪。
and then a mascarpone Chantilly on the outside.
哦!Tshh !
Oh! Tshh!
我不需要这个，因为它看起来更像煎饼。
I would not need this because it looks more like a pancake.
而且非常潮湿。
And it's very soggy as well.
我唯一喜欢吃的就是你的新鲜水果
The only thing that I enjoy eating is your fresh fruit
因为它非常提神。
because it's very refreshing.
除此之外，我一点也不喜欢吃。
Other than that, I didn't enjoy eating it at all.
好了，我们有棒棒糖了。
So, we have got our lollipops.
首先，他们是否过于富有想象力?
First thing, are they overly imaginative?
不。
No.
那么，我们从这个开始吧?
So, shall we start with this one?
这是一个伟大的金融家。
This one is a gianduja financier.
无聊，无聊，无聊。
Boring, boring, boring.
砰，砰，砰!
Boing, boing, boing!
我想要更多!它也是干的。好的。对不起。
I want more! It is dry as well. OK. Sorry.
你能解释一下里面是什么吗?
Could you explain what is inside, please?
柠檬焦糖和咖啡奶油。
Lemon caramel and coffee cremeux.
柠檬，我觉得和咖啡不太搭。
The lemon, I don't think it works with coffee.
巧克力的外壳很厚。
And the chocolate shell is very thick.
我第一次尝到的是苦涩。
The first taste I taste is bitterness.
一切都是苦，苦，苦。
It's all bitter, bitter, bitter.
我一点也不喜欢吃这个。
And just don't enjoy eating this at all.
明天你有很多事要做。
You're going to have a lot to do tomorrow.
这不是苦的。不…
That's is not bitter. No...
我觉得填充物在某种程度上被压扁了。
I think that the filling is quite squashed in a way.
它没有展现出馅料的美。
It doesn't show the beauty of the filling.
提醒我里面有什么味道。
Remind me what the flavours are in there.
香蕉和焦糖甘纳许。
Banana and caramel ganache.
〇先说坏消息
Bad news first -
质地，有点太软了。
the texture, a bit too soft.
好消息，味道很好，我喜欢香蕉，切起来很干净。
Good news - good flavour, loved the banana, it's clean to cut.
做得很好。
Well done.
提醒我一下，这是什么?
Remind me, what is this again?
萨姆:这是香草味的黑貂，上面有一层酥皮，
SAM: It's a vanilla sable with a streusel on top,
外面是大黄果冻，
rhubarb jelly on the outside,
里面是焦糖苹果。
and then inside you have caramelised apple.
我喜欢这个概念。我觉得大黄很酸。
I like the concept. The rhubarb, I think it's very acidic.
然而，我确实喜欢苹果。
However, I do like the apple.
所以，总的来说，还可以。
So, as a whole, it's OK.
我还期待更多呢。下一个。
I was hoping for more. Next one.
这是榛子杏仁巧克力。
It's a hazelnut and almond chocolate.
这真的让我觉得，你知道，“吃了我”。
It really made me feel like, you know, "eat me".
这是个好迹象。
That's a good sign.
我喜欢!
I love it!
:哦…!
ALL: Oh...!
我喜欢它。我本来可以多吃点的。
I love it. I could have eat more.
里面有很多质地，就连涂层都很棒。
There's so many textures in there, and even the coating is sensational.
爱它，爱它，爱它。
Love it, love it, love it.
但是因为我在照顾我的身材……我不会再吃了。
But because I'm looking after my figure...I'm not going to eat more.
如果你事先告诉我，我们就会去那里
If you told me before we'd go out there
如果你这么说，我会把你的手咬下来。
and have that judging, I'd have bit your hand off.
我们已经开始开裂了，所以做马卡龙的技巧是错误的。
We are already starting cracking, so wrong technique to do the macaron.
你能给我们介绍一下味道吗?
Would you be able to take us through the flavour profile, please?
所以，这是花生甘纳许。
So, it's a peanut ganache.
里面有花生慕斯和焦糖花生。
It's got a peanut mousse and then caramelised peanuts inside.
你认为是这样吗?它是熟的吗?这就是问题所在。
Do you think so, it's cooked? That's the problem.
在制作的时候，我们意识到马卡龙还没有煮熟。
When it comes to build it, we realised the macaroon wasn't cooked.
是的。所以我们试着把它放回烤箱，然后…
Yeah. So we tried to put it back in the oven, then...
我们最后不得不把它造得很热。
We ended up having to build it hot.
. .马卡龙太热了，馅都塌了。
..and the macaron was too warm, so all the filling just collapsing.
这正是我们不想要的。
This is exactly what we don't want.
所以你的棒棒糖有很多东西要学——希望如此!
So a lot to pick up with your lollipop - hopefully!
这是一种蛋糕，上面撒上了橘子和香草糖浆。
So it's a pain de Gene sponge topped with a orange and vanilla syrup.
然后你就有了柑橘果馅饼
Then you've got a mandarin pate de fruit
然后是巧克力橙甘纳许。
and then a chocolate-orange ganache.
吉恩的疼痛是干的，不舒服。
The pain de Gene is dry and it's not pleasant.
不是很好。不是很好，伙计们。
Not great. Not great, guys.
罗曼:这是椰子和椰子朗姆酒甘纳许，还有椰子马卡龙。
ROMAIN: So it's coconut and coconut rum ganache with a coconut macaron.
至少这马卡龙是熟的。
At least this macaron is cooked.
我一点也不喜欢吃这个。
I did not enjoy eating this at all.
抱歉，伙计们，没关系的。
I'm sorry, guys, but not at all.
非常感谢大家。我稍后再看。
Thank you very much, guys. I will see later.
这是建设性的批评。
It's constructive criticism.
我们知道他们希望我们做得更好。
We know that they want us to do a lot better.
如果我们明天不催促，我们出去，
If we don't push tomorrow and we go out,
我们会很失望，
we will be like, you know, so disappointed,
因为我们没有尽力。
because we didn't do our best.
所以我们需要保持…是的，我们要保持乐观。
So we need to keep... Yeah, we need to keep positive.
明天的比赛需要两队将两者结合起来
Tomorrow's showpiece will require the teams to combine both
糖工艺品和巧克力首次在比赛中发挥作用。
sugar craft and chocolate work for the first time in the competition.
所以要明智地利用黄金时间来获取大的元素
So using the golden hour wisely to get any large elements
夜间设置将比以往任何时候都更加重要。
set overnight will be more vital than ever.
四分之一决赛上半场结束了，
First-half of the quarterfinal done,
公平地说，这些团队今天并没有真正交付。
and it's pretty fair to say the teams didn't really deliver today.
今天对所有球队来说都是艰难的一天。
It was a difficult day for all the teams today.
其中三家的表现稍好一些。
Three have done marginally better.
度假村的世界。
Resorts World.
希尔顿酒店经营得很好。
The Hilton have done pretty well.
Sweet Art Lab做了一些好吃的东西。
And Sweet Art Lab have done something actually nice to eat.
我看到，现实地说，两支球队明天会有麻烦
I see, realistically, two teams in trouble for tomorrow -
萨沃伊酒店和皇家咖啡厅。
The Savoy and Hotel Cafe Royal.
明天的挑战是
Tomorrow's showpiece challenge is
也许是最具挑战性的一个。
perhaps the most challenging one yet.
他们必须明白这是四分之一决赛
They have to understand that this is the quarterfinal -
下一关他们将进入半决赛。
the next level they are going through is semifinal.
“好”已经不够好了。
"Good" is not good enough any more.
主题是童话故事。
The theme is fairy tales.
让我们希望我们有一个快乐的结局，没有人……死去。
Let's hope we have a happy ending and that nobody...dies.
鸟鸣声
BIRDSONG
早....早晨,早晨。欢迎回来。
Morning. Morning, morning. Welcome back.
厨师们，今天不准把玩具扔出婴儿车，
No throwing your toys out of the pram today, chefs,
但一定要把你的一切都投入到这个挑战中。
but do throw everything you've got at this challenge.
评委们，你们希望今天的队伍创造什么?
Judges, what would you like the teams to create today?
我们希望你能做一个精彩的展示
We would like you to make a spectacular showpiece
灵感来自童话故事和特色巧克力和糖的工作。
inspired by fairy tale and featuring chocolate work and sugar work.
你的作品必须给我们讲个故事，吸引我们
Your showpiece must tell us a story and take us
带着你的设计和色彩回到童年。
back to childhood with your design and colour.
你必须做两个完全一样的主菜蛋糕。
You must make two identical entremet cakes.
你必须给蛋糕上釉，而且必须有巧克力的味道。
You must glaze your cakes and they must include chocolate flavours.
记住，我们期望的是完美无缺。
Remember, we expect nothing less than perfection.
你昨晚有一小时准备时间。
You had one hour last night to prepare.
你今天还有四个小时来完成挑战。
You have four hours left today to complete the challenge.
好的机会。你的时间从现在开始。
Bonne chance. Your time starts now.
我的鸡蛋呢?计时器。计时器，计时器，计时器……
Where's my eggs? Timer. Timer, timer, timer...
这个展示品是迄今为止技术上最具挑战性的。
This showpiece is the most technically challenging yet.
这是四分之一决赛。
Well, this is the quarterfinal.
我们看看他们是怎么处理巧克力的，
We see what they can do with chocolate,
我们看到了它们对糖的作用，
we see what they can do with sugar,
现在是时候把它们放在一起了。
now it's time to put it all together.
把糖和巧克力结合起来困难重重。
Combining sugar and chocolate is fraught with difficulties.
巧克力不喜欢热，需要糖粘合在一起。
Chocolate do not like heat, which sugar need to glue together.
那么这是如何运作的呢?我把这个留给他们。
So how is this going to work? I leave that up to them.
我从来没把糖和巧克力混在一起过，
I've never combined sugar and chocolate together,
我也没见过这种事。
it's not something I've ever really seen either.
对我来说重要的是——它必须是迷人的，神奇的
What's important for me - it has to be enchanting, magical
带我去童话世界。
and take me to the fairy tale world.
他们想让我们创造一个童话
They want us to create a fairy tale
我们觉得没有比厨房更好的地方了。
and we thought there is no better place than the kitchen.
为了童话故事?你要杀了我!
For fairy tales? You're killing me!
好吧，告诉我们你的故事。
OK, tell us your story.
讲的是一位老厨师想要做出一道神奇的菜，
It's about an old chef who wants to create that amazing dish,
完美的食谱。
that perfect recipe.
那是他的食谱书展吗?
Is that his recipe book fair?
这将是他的秘方书。
It's going to be his secret recipe book.
哦，我喜欢，我喜欢，秘方。
CHERISH: Oh, I like that, I like that, secret recipe.
艾曼纽和山姆的恳求
Emmanuel and Sam's entremet
有白巧克力慕斯，
has a white chocolate mousse,
一层层的百香果慕斯
layers of passion fruit mousse,
百香果果冻
a passion fruit jelly
还有一个芒果香草果冻。
and a mango and vanilla jelly.
但尝起来还是巧克力的味道?对我来说，它更有异国情调。
But it will still taste of chocolate? To me, it's more exotic.
必须是巧克力。好的。
It needs to be chocolate. OK.
他们在昨天的比赛中表现出色，
After their performance in yesterday's challenge,
罗曼和琳恩今天要上演一出杰作。
Romain and Leanne needs to deliver a virtuoso showpiece today.
他们选择了一个更传统的童话故事
They've opted for a more traditional fairy tale
那是用有色糖做的。
that will be built from coloured sugar.
作为展示品，我们正在做一个城堡作为背景。
For the showpiece, we are doing a castle on the background.
一整个?!一个整体的一部分。
A whole one?! Part of a whole one.
我们将有一条路，马车将停在上面
We're going to have a road where the carriage will sit on
还有主菜下面的鞋子。
and the shoes under the entremet.
所以这是你的童话，还是罗曼的童话?
CHERISH: So is this your fairy tale, or Romain's fairy tale?
不，这是我的童话!是的，是的。穿着金色的拖鞋!
No, it's my fairy tale! It is, it is. With golden slipper!
这是我的童年。
It's my childhood.
我一直在玩城堡和公主。
I was playing with castles and princess all the time.
哦!
Aw!
酒店皇家咖啡厅的味道会看到童年的层层叠叠
Hotel Cafe Royal's taste of childhood will see layers of
巧克力和焦糖还有
chocolate and caramel and
马斯卡彭蜂蜜慕斯
mascarpone honey mousses
上面撒上一层透明的柠檬釉
topped with a clear lemon glaze
它会在上面
and it will sit above
他们城堡的入口。
the entrance of their castle.
你们是如何团结在一起的
How do you actually stick together
糖和巧克力成分?
the sugar and the chocolate components?
它们是分开的。他们不需要团结在一起。
They will be separate. They are not going to have to stick together.
怎么啦？是的，它们是分开的。
What? Yeah, they will be separate.
这里的技术要点是把两者结合起来。
The technicality in this is try to bind the two together, guys.
不管怎样，如果可以的话，我们希望能看到一点。
One way or another, so we'd like to see a little bit of that if you can.
祝你们好运。谢谢你！
Good luck, guys. Thank you.
尽管上周糖价暴跌，
Despite last week's catastrophic sugar crash,
英子对这种食材的热情并没有减弱。
Hideko's enthusiasm for the ingredient hasn't diminished.
你可以创造任何东西。你也可以把它做得五彩缤纷。
You can create anything. You can make it so colourful as well.
她的五彩糖作品也被用来说明
Her multicoloured sugar work is also being used to illustrate
灰姑娘和她独特马车的故事。
the story of Cinderella and her unique carriage.
南瓜主题在Sweet Art Lab的主菜中延续，
The pumpkin theme continues in Sweet Art Lab's entremet,
和白巧克力甘纳许一起上桌了
for along with a white chocolate ganache, they're serving
松脆的南瓜籽酥饼
a crunchy pumpkin seed streusel
还有南瓜柑橘慕斯。
and a pumpkin and citrus mousse.
主菜上有什么装饰吗?
Is there any decoration on the entremet?
试着做个小南瓜，吹糖。
Trying to make a little pumpkin, blown sugar.
吹糖南瓜?小一。小的。
Blown sugar pumpkin? Tiny one. Tiny ones.
和Hideko一样，Eddie过去也曾与糖作过斗争，
Like Hideko, Eddie has already struggled with sugar in the past,
但他决定把谨慎抛到九霄云外，加入复杂元素
but he's decided to throw caution to the wind by including complex
吹糖使他的童话栩栩如生。
blown sugar work to help bring his fairy tale to life.
我们要找的是灯里的精灵。
We've gone for, like, a genie in the lamp.
我喜欢这样。
I like that.
我们的想法是它有一个很高的结构环。
The idea is it's with a tall structure ring.
巧克力的结构。
Structure with chocolate.
魔毯是一条糖丝带。
And the magic carpet is going to be a sugar ribbon.
哦，魔毯-我喜欢。
Oh, magic carpet - I like that.
所以你也要制作精灵吗?
So are you going to make the genies as well?
是的，我要试着吹灭精灵。
Yeah, I'm going to try and blow the genie.
萨沃伊酒店神奇的巧克力展示品将达到
The Savoy's magical chocolate showpiece will rub up to
塞满了
an entremet packed with
一层层的巧克力海绵，
layers of chocolate sponge,
百香果果冻，
passion fruit jelly,
百香果奶油蛋糕，
passion fruit cremeux,
黑巧克力慕斯，
a dark chocolate mousse,
最后是一盏巧克力灯。
topped off with a chocolate lamp.
马什德，你在许什么愿?希望我们能赢。
Mashid, what are you wishing for? Wishing we win.
对，很好。我喜欢你想赢。
Right, that's good. I like you wishing to win.
我们参加比赛不是为了输球，而是为了赢球。
We didn't enter to lose - we entered to win.
巴拉特和达里尔也希望有一个童话般的结局
Bharat and Darryl are also hoping for a fairy tale ending
一件展品的故事始于一个亲戚的后院。
with a showpiece whose story began in a relative's backyard.
我和我妹妹过去常去我阿姨家，
Myself and my sister used to go to my auntie's house,
在她的花园尽头有一棵树，
and at the bottom of her garden she had a tree,
在那棵树的底部，曾经有一扇小门
and at the bottom of that tree, used to have a little door
她总是说那扇门里有仙女。
and she always used to say that it was fairies in that door.
你相信有仙女吗?我做的事。我现在有点老了。
Do you believe in fairies? I do. I'm a bit old for that now.
你相信有仙女吗，珍爱?我当然相信有仙女!
You believe in fairies, Cherish? Of course I believe in fairies!
它有草莓凝胶，橙子和牛奶巧克力慕斯，
With its strawberry gel insert, orange and milk chocolate mousse,
香草橙海绵蛋糕
vanilla and orange sponge
还有大理石釉，
and marble glaze,
名胜世界丰富多彩的主菜
Resorts World's colourful entremet
会依偎在心脏吗
will nestle at the heart
他们的童话秀。
of their fairy showpiece.
我们会有一个树桩，显然有一个小门。
We're going to have a tree stump, obviously with a little door.
在它后面，我要画一个月亮，我们会让仙女进来
Behind it I'm going to do a moon, and we'll have the fairy in
月亮的中心
the centre of that moon
我要给她的翅膀做一些丝带。
and I'm going to do some pulled ribbon for her wings.
你是怎么把巧克力混合在一起的
How did you manage to combine the chocolate
和糖一起吗?
and the sugar together?
我们还没到那一步，但我有一些想法。
We haven't got that far yet, but I've got a few ideas.
你知道，它还在开发中。
You know, it's still in development.
参赛队伍不仅要制作出完美无瑕的精彩表演，
Not only must the teams produce a flawless and fantastical showpiece,
他们还必须确保他们的恳求是完美的构造。
they must also ensure their entremets are perfectly constructed.
主菜是多层慕斯蛋糕。
An entremet is a multilayer mousse cake.
每一层都要告诉我一个故事。
Every layer has to tell me a story.
这是白巧克力。
This is white chocolate.
我们小时候不怎么吃黑巧克力。
We didn't really eat dark chocolate as a kid.
这些团队制作了他们多层主菜的一些元素
The teams made some of the elements of their multi-layered entremet
在昨天的黄金时刻。
in yesterday's golden hour.
他们真的很好。我对他们很满意。
They're really nice. I'm happy with them.
但厨师们仍然需要调味并将它们混合起来。
But the chefs still need to flavour and combine them.
我要把蛋糕浸在橙汁里。这就是底。
I'm just going to soak this cake in orange. This will be just the base.
我觉得主菜看起来不错。
I think our entremet is looking good.
只需要把白巧克力慕斯涂在上面
Just need to do the white chocolate mousse to go over the top
然后放进冰箱。
and then that can go in the freezer.
这是巧克力慕斯。
This is the chocolate mousse.
我把我的建反了。
I built mine upside down.
你会在顶部有一个漂亮的平面
You will have a nice flat surface on the top
然后，当你倒上釉料的时候，它就会变得又漂亮又均匀。
and then, when you pour your glaze, it will be nice and even.
为了保持它的形状，摩丝必须完全定型。
To hold its shape, the mousse must be perfectly set.
一片明胶在里面。
One leaf of gelatine in there.
明胶太多，吃起来会不舒服。
Too much gelatine and it will be unpleasant to eat.
测试几次以确保它不会太紧实
Test it a few times to make sure it is not too firm
给评委的，因为我知道他们不喜欢明胶。
for the judges, cos I know they don't like gelatine.
对琳恩来说，这意味着再次面对她的宿敌。
For Leanne, it means facing her nemesis once again.
是的，这是明胶。
Yeah, this is gelatine.
我们在这个食谱里把它调淡了。
We've toned it down in this recipe.
是不是太浓了?
Is it not too liquid?
上次是不是厚了很多?
Was it a lot thicker last time?
有一点。我不会说它更厚。
A little bit. I wouldn't say it was much thicker.
加两倍的明胶。是吗?
Double the amount of gelatine. Yeah?
大厨们，你们的童话已经讲了一半了，已经讲了一半。
Chefs, you are halfway through your fairy tale, halfway through.
随着慕斯的设置，团队将注意力转向糖。
With entremets setting, the teams turn their attention to sugar.
哔哔声。这里太热了。制糖的温度适宜。
BLEEP. It's scorching round here. Temperature for sugar work is fine.
不过这里太热了，不适合吃巧克力。
It's very warm in here for chocolate, though.
有这么多糖元素要构建，
With so many sugar elements to construct,
这对团队来说是至关重要的，他们开始了炎热而艰苦的转弯过程
it's vital the teams begin the hot, arduous process of turning
这是他们童话装饰的日常食材。
this everyday ingredient into their fairy tale decorations.
我第一次看到糖加工的时候，
The first time I ever saw sugar work done,
我觉得这很神奇。
I thought it was pretty magical.
当你拿起糖的时候，你不会觉得它是
When you pick up sugar, you don't see it as
变成鲜花之类的东西。
turning into flowers and stuff.
我做了一些带叶子的小玫瑰
I've done some little roses with a leaf
我做了一个球体，里面有玫瑰。
and I did a sphere with the roses inside.
我要把这四个都算出来。我觉得这是个不错的主意。
I'm going to do all four of them. I think it's a nice touch.
吹糖是一个繁琐而耗时的过程
Blowing sugar is a fiddly and time-consuming process
这很容易损坏。
that's prone to breakages.
我对制糖工作没有多少经验。
I have not much experience with sugar work.
我知道它很脆弱!
I know it's fragile!
糖碎
SUGAR WORK SHATTERS
把它弄坏了。
Broke that one.
尽管如此，埃迪又一次制造出了复杂的糖
Despite this, Eddie's once again making complex sugar work
他的展品的焦点。
the focal point of his showpiece.
我们有灯，有魔毯，
We've got the lamp, we've got the magic carpet,
这就是精灵。
and this is the genie.
我把这个放在灯下，
And I'll put this under the lamp,
我要把它塑造一下，让它看起来更像精灵。
and I'll just shape it, you know, to give it more that genie look.
这是一个冒险的决定。
It's a risky decision.
如果没有精心设计的精灵，他的童话就会落空。
Without a well-crafted genie, his fairy tale will fall flat.
糖工作粉碎哔哔!哔哔声!
SUGAR WORK SHATTERS BLEEP! BLEEP!
我需要重新开始。
I need to start this again.
我现在要拉一条缎带，那是为翅膀准备的。
I'm going to pull a ribbon now, and that's for the wings.
当其他团队继续他们的糖工作时，
While the rest of the teams move on with their sugar work,
埃迪落后了。
Eddie has fallen behind.
他还没有成功地吹灭他的精灵。
He's yet to successfully blow his genie.
艾迪和马什德，我很喜欢这个概念
Eddie and Mashid, I really like the concept
他们投入了他们的精灵。
they've put into their genies.
灯和魔毯。
Lamp and a magic carpet.
我们只需要看到一个完成的，熟练的展示
We just need to see a finished, skilful Showpiece
让他们摆渡出去。我们有巧克力块
for them to ferry out. We've got the chocolate piece
现在还没有和糖混合。
which at the moment is not combined with the sugar.
我需要看到他们付出了努力
I need to see that they've made the effort
把糖和巧克力混合在一起。
of combining sugar and chocolate together.
Hideko和Theo，我很喜欢南瓜的主意
Hideko and Theo, I really like the idea of the pumpkin
加入到主菜中
to be incorporated into entremet.
话虽如此，这是一个巧克力蛋糕，
Having said that, it is a chocolate cake,
所以我们需要感受巧克力的味道。
so we need to feel the chocolate.
哔哔声!哔哔声!
BLEEP! BLEEP!
哔哔声!
BLEEP!
那是魔毯。
That's the magic carpet there.
我不确定下一个会不会这么薄。
I'm not sure the next one's as thin.
艾迪拼命抢救更多的制糖工作
As Eddie races to salvage yet more sugar work...
啊!这只是在浪费时间。
Argh! It's just wasting time.
. .具有完整组件的组件
..those with completed components
现在面对技术上最复杂的建筑…
now face the most technically complex construction...
这是一个错误。
That was a mistake.
. .这是前所未有的竞争。
..the competition has ever seen.
正确的。冻结。
Right. Freeze.
喘息声
GASPS
猪。
Pig.
天气很冷，不是吗?
It's cold, isn't it?
凝固巧克力的冷喷雾可以打碎糖。
The cold spray that sets chocolate can break sugar.
以及糖融化所需的高温
And the extreme heat that sugar requires to melt
和巧克力不搭。
doesn't sit well with chocolate.
你有什么问题吗?
Are you having trouble sticking it together?
这要花很长时间。
That's going to take forever.
哇，哇，哇。
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
对不起，对不起。
GASPS Sorry, sorry.
你还好吗?是的。
Are you OK? Yeah.
我是边做边练，你懂吗?
I'm building it as it goes, you know?
辉煌。
Brilliant.
大厨们，你们还有十分钟。
Chefs, you have ten minutes left.
现在时间紧迫。
Pushed for time now.
十分钟。给童年的自己写封信，
Ten minutes. Write a letter to your childhood self,
告诉他们你没有搞砸这个挑战。
tell them you didn't mess up this challenge.
哦，发生什么事了?
Oh, what happened?
哔哔声。我的天啊。
BLEEP. Oh, my God.
参赛队伍不仅要完成他们的展示作品，
Not only must the teams construct their Showpieces,
他们还必须给主菜上釉
they must also get their entremets glazed
及时让它们凝固。
in time for them to set.
伙计，白的颜色不够亮。
Man, the white's not coming out enough.
格莱兹看起来不错。真的闪闪发光。
Glaze looks all right. Really shiny.
哦!
Oh!
慢慢来。我没有时间做更多的事情了。
Take your time. I won't have time to do more.
学了很多东西。
Leaning a lot, that.
哦,巴拉特。
Oh, Bharat.
是啊，但你一把它放上去…
Yeah, but soon as you put it on there...
哇，哇，哇。你必须非常小心
Whoa, whoa, whoa. You have to be really careful
否则它就会打散。不要这样做。
otherwise it'll just shatter. Don't do it.
哔哔声。
BLEEP.
先放一个在上面。
Put one of them on top there for now.
是的。什么在开裂?
Yeah. What is cracking?
破解不!
CRACKING No!
快，快，快。
Quick, quick, quick.
我们没有放足够的明胶。不会持续太久的。
We didn't put enough gelatine in. Not going to last.
哔哔声。
BLEEP.
哦，你这个笨蛋。
Oh, you piece of BLEEP.
咆哮
GROWLS
我要穿上它!
I want it on!
大厨们，你们还有一分钟。
Chefs, you have one minute left.
这是一分钟。
That's one minute.
哔哔声。
BLEEP.
哔哔声!
BLEEP!
大厨们，你们的时间到了!
Chefs, your time is up!
哔哔声。
BLEEP.
钟在报时。
The clock is chiming.
您的马车在等您。
Your carriage awaits.
希尔顿酒店看起来棒极了。
The Hilton's looks fantastic.
对此我很难过。
So gutted about this.
五部奇幻童话，
Five fantastical fairy tale showpieces,
还有他们的巧克力点心，
and their accompanying chocolate entremets,
但哪一项将为他们的球队赢得半决赛席位呢?
but which will earn their team a place in the semifinal?
这就是我所说的展示品。
That is what I call a showpiece.
我们看到的每一个地方都有故事。
Everywhere we look there is a story in there.
我真的很喜欢你秘方里的泡泡。
I really like the bubble that you incorporate to the secret recipe.
当你看到这小小的关注时，
When you see the little attention here,
那个锅和下面的火焰，我真的很喜欢。
that pot and the flames underneath, yeah, I really like that.
当然，你的策略是对的，也就是
Of course, you got with the right strategy, which is
用巧克力使其达到最大的高度，体积和强度
work with chocolate to get maximum height, volume, strong
结构和带来更轻，更精致的糖元素之后。
structure and bring your lighter, more delicate sugar element after.
你的主菜里有什么?
What's inside your entremets?
芒果香草果冻白巧克力慕斯，
White chocolate mousse with mango and vanilla jelly,
百香果果冻和香草海绵。
passion fruit jelly and vanilla sponge.
繁荣。
Boom.
真的很喜欢吃巧克力慕斯。
Really enjoy eating the chocolate mousse.
我喜欢你放新鲜芒果进去。总的来说，还不错。
I like it when you put the fresh mango in. Overall, it's nice.
这是个美味的蛋糕，有百香果和芒果。
It's a pleasant cake, you get the passion fruit, you get the mango.
就像我吃的是水果点心，而不是巧克力蛋糕。
It's like I've got a fruit entremets, not a chocolate cake.
哦，亲爱的上帝，救救我们吧。
Oh, dear God, help us.
我不知道他们当时是怎么做到的。
I don't how BLEEP they got that done in the time.
我真的不知道。
I really don't.
就这样，四分之一决赛的准备工作都完成了吗?嗯嗯。
This is it, all your work for the quarterfinal is done? Mm-hm.
看起来像你想要的吗?事情没有按计划进行。
Does it look like you wanted? Things didn't go to plan.
这是一种视觉效果，颜色的对比很好
Well, there is a visual, there is a nice contrast of colour which
带来了一点童话的元素。
brings a little bit of the fairytale element.
我们有一些糖，一些缎带。
We've got some sugar work, some ribbon.
显然，我们看到那里发生了一些事情。
Clearly, we see that something has happened there.
当然，我希望再高一点。
Of course, I would have hoped a little bit of height.
我认为这个概念是存在的。
I think the concept is there.
当我看到蘑菇的时候，感觉很粗糙，
When I look at the mushroom it's quite heavy-handed,
但是那边的蘑菇，我觉得它们看起来很可爱。
but the back mushrooms over there, I think they look really cute.
蛋糕是牛奶巧克力和橘色海绵蛋糕，
The cake is milk chocolate and orange sponge base,
浸泡在橙汁中。
soaked in orange syrup.
最上面的一层是草莓凝胶，
A layer on top of that is the strawberry gel,
还有一份白巧克力甘纳许。
and a white chocolate ganache.
我能感觉到白巧克力奶油冻。
I can feel the white chocolate cremeux.
我得到了橙色和草莓果冻的对比。
I get the contrast of the orange and strawberry jelly.
口感对我来说很棒。
The texture, for me, is great.
它摸起来很像奶油，但是釉有点粘。
It does feel very creamy but the glaze is a bit sticky.
明胶，你可以再加一点，
The gelatine, you could have added maybe just a touch more,
再加几克，这样蛋糕就撑起来了。
a few grams more, so that the cake is propped.
现在蛋糕正在下垂。巧克力慕斯还可以。
At the moment the cake is sagging. The chocolate mousse is OK.
然而，海绵并不令人愉快。
However, the sponge is not enjoyable.
你是否与时间作斗争?
Did you struggle with time?
我们差不多都搞定了，
Oh, we got everything pretty much done,
但是我们发生了一些事故，我们必须解决一些问题。
but we had a couple of accidents and we had to fix a couple of problems.
我记得你跟我提过飞毯。是的。
I remember you mentioned a flying carpet to me. Yes.
飞毯在哪里?
So where is the flying carpet?
嗯，最上面的几块巧克力掉下来碎了
Well, the top pieces of chocolate had fallen down and broke
那个大的，我已经做了一半。好的。
the big one that I had done in half. OK.
我会来到这张桌子上，把它当作一个展示品吗
Will I come to this table and see this as a showpiece
哪个是直的，灯里的精灵?
which is straight, the genie in the lamp story?
不。
No.
这是一盏灯，可能是一个茶壶，
This is a lamp, could be a teapot,
蓝色的部分是平的，没有字符。
and that blue thing here is flat, there is no character.
剩下的只是一个球，一个圈，几个漩涡。这是不够的。
The rest is just a ball, a loop, a few swirls. It is not enough.
我真心希望你的蛋糕好吃。
I really hope your cake tastes amazing.
底部是巧克力海绵，里面是百香果
On the bottom is a chocolate sponge and then inside is a passion fruit
凝乳，异国果冻和巧克力慕斯。
curd, exotic jelly and chocolate mousse.
巧克力慕斯口感很顺滑。
Chocolate mousse is quite smooth and nice.
我很喜欢百香果凝乳，非常柔滑。
Really like the passion fruit curd, it's really creamy.
我唯一不喜欢的是海绵。
The only thing that I don't really enjoy is the sponge.
我认为那里非常非常干燥。
I think it's very, very dry.
马希德，你的巧克力慕斯做得很好，做得很好。
Your chocolate mousse, Mahshid, is well done, well executed.
它是美丽的。谢谢你！
It's beautiful. Thank you.
百香果和它一起可以起作用。对我来说，太多了。
The passion fruit with it can work. For me, there is too much of it.
缺少的是质地。
What's missing is texture.
所有东西都是软的，所以有点无聊。是的。
Everything is soft and for that, it's a bit boring. Yeah.
你能告诉我巧克力在哪里吗
Would you be able to show me where the chocolate
这些糖实际上是一起起作用的吗?
and the sugar has actually been working together?
是的，我用巧克力画了城堡的屋顶
Yes, so I've done the roof of the castle in chocolate
还有巧克力城堡的入口。
and a sort of entrance for the castle in chocolate.
这是入口吗?我以为是月亮。
Is that an entrance here? I thought it's a moon.
这可能是一个烟囱。
And this could be a chimney.
或者是城堡，烟囱，城堡。
Or, yeah, it's a castle, chimney, castle.
但这很好。谢谢你！
But this is nice. Thank you.
罗曼就是罗曼，一点糖不会害死人的，
Romain being Romain, a little bit of sugar doesn't kill anyone,
我看到了你工作的技巧
and I see the finesse in your work.
当你说公主的时候，我看到了很多潜力。
I see a lot of potential when you said princess.
但是钻石在哪里?皇冠上的闪光在哪里?
But where's the diamond? Where's the glitter on the crown?
让我们看看蛋糕能不能送货。
Let's see if the cake delivers.
丽安:这是一块巧克力海绵，上面有一层巧克力脆皮。
LEANNE: So it's a chocolate sponge, got a chocolate crunchy layer.
在上面有一层焦糖。
On top of that it's got a caramel layer on.
上面是巧克力慕斯，上面是柠檬汁。
It's got a chocolate mousse and then on top of that it's got a lemon glaze.
我喜欢你平衡蛋糕的方式。
I like the way you balance your cake.
里面有很多口感。我喜欢它。真的。
There's plenty of texture in there. I like it. I really do.
我很喜欢底部的海绵，
I really like the sponge at the bottom,
焦糖和脆脆的元素，一切都在一起。
the caramel and the crunch element, everything goes together.
非常愉快。
It's very pleasant.
我要说的第一件事是，注意你的明胶。
The first thing I'm going to say is, watch your gelatine.
然而，它尝起来真的很好吃。两人:谢谢。
However, it tastes really nice. BOTH: Thank you.
非常感谢。
Thank you very much.
它非常迷人，非常迷人，非常神奇。
It's very enchanting, it's very fascinating, it's very magical.
你有橙色的，蓝色的，粉色的。
You've got orange, you've got blue, you've got pink.
巧克力的成分，现在我正在努力寻找。
The chocolate element, at the moment I'm trying to look.
巧克力，那是巧克力吗?是的。下面呢?
Chocolate, is that chocolate? Yeah. Underneath?
但这对我来说不算是装饰。
But that doesn't consider as the decoration for me.
马车，我很喜欢它的设计。
The carriage, I really like the design.
很明显，你有问题，但这件事本来可以做得很好
You had issues, clearly, but this could have been done neatly
它会完美地工作。
and it would have worked perfectly.
尝尝你的主菜。
Taste your entremets.
下面是一层南瓜籽，
It's a pumpkin seed streusel on the bottom,
然后是杏仁巧克力Moelleux白巧克力
and then it's almond and chocolate Moelleux, white chocolate
kabsu namelaka和南瓜白巧克力kabsu慕斯。
kabosu namelaka and a pumpkin white chocolate kabosu mousse.
南瓜吗?是的。尝不出南瓜的味道。
Pumpkin? Yes. Can't really taste the pumpkin.
黑巧克力海绵蛋糕是布朗尼型的吗?
The black chocolate sponge is a brownie type?
在巧克力Moelleux上。
On the chocolate Moelleux.
我喜欢它。我非常非常喜欢这种口感。
I love it. I really, really like that texture.
不干，口感丰富，还有巧克力的味道。
It's not dry, it's rich and there is the chocolate flavour.
你有很棒的想法，
You have brilliant ideas,
但有一些最后的修饰显然是你无法做到的。
but there is some finishing touches you clearly can't manage to achieve.
我希望如果你们继续前进，你们能解决这个问题。
I hope if you are moving forward, that you can address this.
根据他们在两项挑战中的表现，
Based on their performance in both challenges,
Benoit和珍惜现在将对球队进行排名。
Benoit and Cherish will now rank the teams.
最后一名的队伍将无缘半决赛。
The team in last place will miss out on the semifinal.
哦，我喜欢。
Oh, I like that.
当珍爱站出来说，哇，
When Cherish stepped up and was just like, wow,
我就想这就是我一直在等待的
and I was like, this is what I've been waiting for.
我一直在等待一个惊喜的时刻!
I've been waiting for a wow moment!
伊曼纽尔:我们希望它足够好，可以进入半决赛。
EMMANUEL: We hope it's good enough to get to the semifinal.
啊，太不整洁了。
Ah, it's very untidy.
我对我们的现状很满意，
I'm content with where we've got,
但我们仍然渴望继续前进。
but we still have that hunger to keep going forward.
在这场比赛中，你永远不会安全。
You're never safe in this competition.
如果我们必须出去，那就是游戏，你懂吗?
If we have to go out, then that's the game, you know?
Benoit和珍惜已经做出了决定。
Benoit and Cherish have made their decision.
第一名的队伍昨天送了一份漂亮的蛋糕
The team in first place delivered a lovely sucette yesterday and
在今天的挑战赛中，我们完全处于自己的水平。
were in a complete league of their own in today's showpiece challenge.
恭喜你们，希尔顿公园巷的伊曼纽尔和山姆，
Congratulations, Emmanuel and Sam from Hilton Park Lane,
你们晋级半决赛了。
you are through to the semifinal.
并列第二的是……
In joint second place are...
. .甜蜜艺术实验室的Hideko和Theo，
..Hideko and Theo from Sweet Art Lab,
还有来自名胜世界的Darryl和Bharat。
and Darryl and Bharat from Resorts World.
恭喜你们，你们俩也都通过了。
Congratulations, you are both also through.
那就只剩皇家咖啡馆酒店的琳恩和罗曼了
Which leaves Leanne and Romain from Hotel Cafe Royal
还有萨沃伊酒店的艾迪和马希德。
and Eddie and Mahshid from The Savoy.
今晚将退出比赛的队伍是……
The team who will be leaving the competition tonight is...
. .艾迪和马希德。
..Eddie and Mahshid.
我很享受在这里的时光，但压力也很大，
I have enjoyed my time here but it has been very, very stressful,
我不得不说。你们应该为自己感到骄傲。
I have to say. You should be proud of yourselves.
你应该为自己感到骄傲。最后伯努瓦向我们走来。
You should be proud of yourself. Benoit came up to us at the end.
他知道我们能做什么。他知道我们能做什么。
He knows all we can do. And he's seen what we can do.
他们仍然知道我们能做什么。
They still know what we can do.
祝贺你。
Congratulations.
伊曼纽尔:首先，我们非常高兴。
EMMANUEL: In first place, we are more than happy.
这种感觉真的很好，我迫不及待地想要进入画板
It does feel really good, can't wait, to get to the drawing board
看看我们要为半决赛设计什么。
and see what we are going to design for the semifinal.
真是难以置信。我一点也不相信。不，我以为我们要去。
It's quite unbelievable. I didn't believe that at all. No, I thought we was going.
我们相信你。
We believe in you.
半决赛!
Semifinal!
下次……天气很热，不是吗?. .这是半决赛。
Next time... It's very heated, isn't it? ..it's the semifinal.
时不再来。
Now or never.
一个有转折的秘方挑战…
A secret recipe challenge with a twist...
哦,哔哔声。
Oh, BEEP.
. .还有现场电镀的美食戏剧……
..and the gastronomic drama of live plating...
他们想要戏剧。今天是你们的舞台。
They wanted theatre. You own the stage today.
. .随着一支队伍进入决赛的机会落下帷幕。
..as the curtain falls on one team's chance of reaching the grand final.
欢迎回到《职业烘焙大赛》，
Welcome back to Bake Off: The Professionals,
现在只剩下四支队伍争夺三个名额了
where we're down to just four teams battling it out for the three places
在下周的决赛中。太让人兴奋了,
in next week's final. So exciting,
真不敢相信已经进入半决赛了，利亚姆，
I can't believe it's the semifinal already, Liam,
我不知道该穿什么!兄弟，没事的，你看起来很好。
I don't know what to wear! Bro, it's OK, you look good.
利亚姆，谢谢你，这对我意义重大。我想知道厨师们会穿什么?
Oh, Liam, thank you, that means a lot. I wonder what the chefs will wear?
汤姆，他们差不多每周都穿同样的衣服。
Er, Tom, they kind of wear the same thing every week.
他们吗?是的。天啊，这太缺乏想象力了。
Do they? Yeah. Jeez, that's so unimaginative.
我想知道他们会创造什么?毫无疑问，有些事很疯狂。
I wonder what they'll create, though? Something insane, no doubt.
海绵，焦糖，巧克力漩涡。
Mm, sponge, infused caramel, chocolate swirls.
鸡蛋花。利亚姆，求你了，别这么叫我，别当着这些人的面。
Frangipani. Liam, please, don't call me that, not in front of these guys.
最后一次……
Last time...
. .四分之一决赛使两队回到了童年时代。
..the quarterfinal took the teams back to childhood.
哇哇哇!
Aww!
对于希尔顿公园巷的伊曼纽尔和山姆，一个迷人的创作…
For the Hilton Park Lane's Emmanuel and Sam, an enchanting creation...
这就是我所说的展示品。
That is what I call a showpiece.
. .意味着童话般的结局。
..meant a fairy tale ending.
第一名，伊曼纽尔和萨姆，你们晋级半决赛了。
First place, Emmanuel and Sam, you are through to the semifinal.
但对萨沃伊的埃迪和马希德来说，前景不容乐观。
But for the Savoy's Eddie and Mahshid, the outlook was grim.
他们的半决赛希望……
And their semifinal hopes...
这个，作为一个展示品，不。
This, as a showpiece, no.
. .消失在一缕烟雾中。
..vanished in a puff of smoke.
我祝愿所有其他球队在这方面好运。
I wish all the other teams the best of luck in this.
这一次……欢呼。. .最后四支球队……
This time... Cheers. ..the last four teams...
天气很热，不是吗?
It's very heated, isn't it?
. .为进入决赛决一死战。
..battle it out for their place in the final.
机不可失，时不再来。
It's now or never.
他们将面对一个秘密配方，还有一个转折……
They'll face a secret recipe, with a twist...
她现在压力太大了。
It's a lot of pressure on her, at the moment.
. .还有美食剧场
..and the gastronomic theatre
带电电镀。
of live plating.
跳伞，高空绳索。
Parachuting, zip wiring.
火,烟。
Fire, smoke.
谁值得再来一次?
Who will deserve an encore?
他们想要戏剧。哇!
They wanted theatre. Woo!
和谁
And who
会被嘘下台吗?
will be booed offstage?
只有四支有天赋的队伍留在比赛中，
Just four talented teams remain in the competition,
但决赛只能有三名选手。
but there can only be three finalists.
我们现在都在努力赢得比赛，每个人都和我们一样努力训练。
We're all in it to win it now, and everyone's training just as hard as us.
我们走了那么远并不只是为了进入半决赛。
We didn't come that far just to finish in the semifinal.
在内心深处，我们想进入决赛，这是肯定的。
Deep inside, we want to be in the final, that's for sure.
我们要战斗到底。是的。毫米。
We're going to fight to the finish. Yep. Mm.
他们的第一个试验是一个独一无二的秘方。
Their first test is a secret recipe, like no other.
这是什么?也许他们只是想让我们放松。
What is this? Maybe they want us just to relax.
两队关系中的任何弱点都将暴露出来。
Any weaknesses in the teams' relationships are about to be exposed.
欢迎来到半决赛，大厨们。
Welcome to the semifinals, chefs.
这是一条漫长而艰辛的道路
It's been a long and arduous road to get
为了这个阶段的比赛，为了我们所有人。
to this stage of the competition, for all of us.
我秃顶了，利亚姆开始刮胡子了，
I've gone bald, and Liam's started shaving,
但今天，它将变得更加艰难。
but today it's about to get even tougher.
没错，厨师们，因为今天你们将面对另一个秘方
That's right, chefs, because today you'll be facing another secret recipe
挑战。只是，对于这个，
challenge. Only, for this one,
评委们发明了一个新的难度等级。
the judges have invented a new level of difficulty.
我们想让你做一道法式甜点，浮叶。
We would like you to make a French dessert, ile flottante.
它必须包含某种形式的英式奶油，一种煮熟的蛋白霜，
It must include some form of creme anglaise, a cooked meringue,
至少吃一种水果，最后加糖。
at least one fruit element, and finish with sugar work.
你们中只有一个人可以做今天的秘方。
Only one of you will be allowed to make today's secret recipe.
怎么啦？哔哔声。
What? BLEEP.
恐怕另一个人只能袖手旁观了，
The other one will have to sit this one out, I'm afraid,
而且只能作为旁观者提供建议。
and only be able to advise from the sidelines.
哔哔声。
BLEEP.
现在你们有两分钟的时间来决定今天谁来做
Now you have two minutes to decide which of you will be making today's
秘方，现在就开始这两分钟。
secret recipe, and those two minutes start now.
哦,哔哔声…你想做饭吗?
Oh, BLEEP... You want to cook?
还是我做饭?
Or I cook?
我不介意。如果我指导你，你会不会感觉好点，
I don't mind. Would you feel better if I directed you,
还是你在指挥我?
or you directing me?
要确保进入决赛，不仅要看你有多好，
To guarantee a place in the final, it is not just about how good you are,
这是关于团队合作，他们必须完全信任彼此。
it is about teamwork, and they will have to trust each other completely.
这个挑战是非常技术性的。
This challenge is very technical.
他们的知识至关重要。
Their knowledge is crucial.
选错了人会导致他们的失败。
Choosing the wrong person will be their downfall.
大胆去做吧。
Go for it.
是吗?是的。
Yeah? Yeah.
随它去吧。
Let it be.
大厨们，你们的两分钟时间到了。
Chefs, your two minutes is up.
不参加的厨师会吗
Would the chef who is not taking part
在今天的秘方挑战中，请
in today's secret recipe challenge, please
在工作站尽头的凳子上坐下?
have a seat on the stool at the end of your work station?
我好怕!
I'm BLEEP scared!
大厨们，你们有两个半小时的时间来完成这个挑战，
Chefs, you have two and a half hours to complete this challenge,
你的时间从现在开始。
and your time starts now.
我的天啊。
Oh, my God.
让我们来看看。
Let's see.
Benoit和珍惜给了团队最少的指导。
Benoit and Cherish have given the teams minimal guidelines.
我们必须想出我们自己的食谱?
We have to come up with our own recipes?
主厨，有食谱吗?
Chef, was there a recipe?
好吧，只是问问。好的,很酷。
OK, just asking. OK, cool.
这就是你得到的。浮岛，或浮岛，
That's what you get. The floating island, or the ile flottante,
用法语说就是蛋白霜
as we say in French, is meringue,
浮在英式奶油上。
which will float on a creme anglaise.
最重要的是，我们加入了水果元素，
Crucially, we've added a fruit element,
这需要结合起来。
which needs to be incorporated.
总会有一点焦糖在上面。
There is always a little bit of caramel spun sugar on it.
有了它，你可以创造体积，你可以创造形状。
With that you could create volume, you could create shape.
它必须是美味和精致的。
It has to be delicious and exquisite.
他们必须把所有的味道混合在一起，为我们做出一种wowser。
They have to combine all the flavours together to make it a wowser for us.
有了各种各样的食材
With an array of ingredients at their disposal...
. .他们可以是传统的……
..they can be as traditional...
我要做一个樱桃树莓果冻。
I'm going to do a cherry and raspberry jelly.
树莓泥……或者发挥他们的创造力。
Raspberry puree. ..or as creative as they like.
对于Sweet Art Lab的Hideko和Theo，
For Sweet Art Lab's Hideko and Theo,
这意味着又一次试验的机会。
this means another chance to experiment.
你放的是什么利口酒?
What liqueur are you putting in?
我们要在里面放一点朗姆酒。
We're going to put a little bit of rum in there.
这将是异国情调的水果。
It's going to be exotic fruit ile flottante.
冰镇果汁朗姆酒。你已经完成了你的涂鸦，
Pina Colada. And you've done your little scribbling,
所以你是负责把食谱写下来的人，对吗?
so you are the one in charge of writing the recipe down, are you?
是的。Hideko，一个人的感觉如何?
Yeah. How does it feel, Hideko, to be by yourself?
超级高压，不是吗?
Super high pressure, isn't it?
只是一点点压力!
Just a little bit of pressure!
只有一点点!
Just a tiny bit!
蛋白霜在机器里。
The meringue's in the machine.
这是最重要的部分。
It's the most important part.
浮岛是一种蛋白派。
A floating island is a meringue.
不出所料，flottante是由，
An ile flottante, is made, unsurprisingly,
配法式蛋白酥皮。
with French meringue.
但是名胜世界的Darryl和Bharat……
But Resorts World's Darryl and Bharat...
我们用的是意大利蛋白霜，因为它能让蛋糕更饱满。
We're using Italian meringue, because it gives it a bit more body.
. .把规则手册扔出窗外。
..are throwing the rule book out of the window.
意大利蛋白霜，我们加热糖
The Italian meringue, we heat the sugar
然后倒入搅打好的蛋白霜中。它更健壮。
and then pour it into the whipped meringue. It's more robust.
Darryl,巴拉特……
Darryl, Bharat...
你好。显然，因为你对鸡蛋过敏…
Hello. Obviously, because you have an egg allergy...
是的。所以我尝不出这个。
Yes. So I can't taste this.
这就是为什么我要信任我忠实的伙伴。
This is why I'm putting my trust in my faithful sidekick.
你觉得当我的跟班怎么样?
How do you feel about being a sidekick?
我以为你们是两个英雄。
I thought you were like two heroes.
因为你留着布鲁斯·韦恩式的发型，
Because you've got the, like, Bruce Wayne kind of haircut,
你绝对是超人。
and you're definitely Superman.
用氪石。氪石就是蛋。
With the kryptonite. The kryptonite is the egg.
鸡蛋，对!
The egg, yeah!
不像名胜世界，他们的团队里有法国人，
Unlike Resorts World, with a Frenchman on their team,
皇家咖啡厅酒店应该有优势。
Hotel Cafe Royal should have an advantage.
但罗曼选择了袖手旁观。
But Roman has elected to sit on the sidelines.
你感觉怎么样?嗯…
How are you feeling? Well...
. .为她感到紧张。为她吗?
..stressed for her. For her?
我们很惊讶你是坐在这里的人。
We are surprised you are the one sitting down here.
你已经吃遍了法国的所有美食很多年了。
You've eaten all of France has to offer for many, many years.
是的。你今天尝不出它的味道。
Yes. And you can't taste it today.
不。我真希望当时在那里。
No. I would have preferred to have been there.
但罗曼并没有让我选择!
But Roman didn't really give me a choice!
你们要为进入决赛而战。
You're fighting for a space in the final.
你有多自信?
How confident are you?
信心就像漂浮的岛屿!
The confidence is floating like the island!
布丁是最好的证明!
The proof is in the pudding!
大厨们，你们还有一小时，还有一个半小时。
Chefs, you've had one hour, you've got an hour and a half left.
我现在要吹箫了。
I'm going to pipe now.
选择正确的方法来制作蛋白霜是至关重要的。
Choosing the correct way to cook their meringue is essential.
这将决定他们的岛屿是漂浮还是沉没。
It will determine whether their islands float or sink.
蛋清非常蓬松，就像吃空气一样。
It's very fluffy, the egg white, it's like eating air.
Hideko和Theo选择了一条捷径…
While Hideko and Theo have opted for a short cut...
试着用微波炉做饭。
Trying to cook in a microwave.
越来越大!. .其他球队则坚持传统。
Getting bigger! ..the other teams are sticking with traditions.
我们要蒸蛋白霜，慢慢煮蛋白霜，
We are going to steam the meringue, so slowly cooking the meringue,
很好，加了水。
nicely, with water.
希望这能给它增加一些高度和结构。
Hopefully that will give it some more height and structure.
但希尔顿公园巷的伊曼纽尔和山姆已经决定担心
But Hilton Park Lane's Emmanuel and Sam have decided that worrying about
一个蛋白霜是不够的。
one meringue isn't enough.
你打算怎么烹饪你的浮岛?
How are you going to cook your floating island?
经典的风格，就是挖走十件。
The classic style, which is to poach ten pieces.
那么，煮你的蛋白霜需要多长时间?
So, how long will it take to poach your meringue?
这是我们必须凭感觉去做的事情。
That's something we're going to have to go by the feeling.
我妈妈过去常常在半小时内完成。
My mum used to do that in half an hour.
你妈妈很好。整个浮岛。
Your mother was very good. The whole floating island.
我希望你妈妈能来帮我们一把!
I would love your mother to be here and give us a hand!
大厨们，你们还有一个小时。
Chefs, you have one hour left.
厨师们，你们得站好。
Chefs, you've got to stay on your stools.
是我。
It's me.
压力中心。
Stress central.
参赛队伍必须包含至少一种水果元素。
The teams must include at least one fruit element.
山姆可能会在蛋白霜里做果冻。
Sam's might going to make fruit jelly to go inside the meringue.
百香果和芒果凝胶，蛋白霜放在凝胶上，
Passion fruit and mango gel, so the meringue sits on the gel,
它不会变得那么湿。
and it doesn't get that soggy.
流动的果冻会导致甜点潮湿。
Runny jelly will result in a damp dessert.
我们用覆盆子，
We're using raspberry,
希望我们能把它设置好。
so hopefully we can get it set.
这还不是他们要担心的全部。
And that's not all they have to worry about.
英式奶油也需要在冰箱里放上一段时间。
The creme anglaise also needs time in the chiller...
. .但伊曼纽尔和山姆必须等待。
..but Emmanuel and Sam have to wait.
我们要用之前煮过的牛奶来做英式奶糊。
We're going to use the milk that we used to poach to make the anglaise.
很明显我们在做这个，我们不能做英式英语，
We are obviously doing that, and we can't do the anglaise,
所以我们显然在减速。
so we are obviously slowing down.
本来就应该是这样吗?
Is that how it's supposed to be?
它是用微波炉煮的。
It is microwave cooked.
快，快，快!完美的蛋白霜应该是雪白的……
Move, move, move! A perfectly cooked meringue should be snowy white...
闻闻，闻起来很有鸡蛋味，不是吗?
Smell it, it smells very eggy, no?
. .稍微收缩一下……
..and shrink slightly...
哦，是的，那很好。
Oh, yeah, that's good.
. .所以它很容易从模具中滑落。
..so it slides easily from the mould.
它粘住了吗?
Did it stick to it?
哦!
Oh!
哔哔声。哦，喷雾剂，
BLEEP. Oh, the sprays,
我们不能一直用喷雾剂，对吧?
we can't do stick with the spray, no?
好的，我们再做一个蛋白霜。
OK, let's do another meringue.
是的。另一个酥皮。
Yep. Another meringue.
我们有多久了?大厨们，你们还有半个小时，
How long have we got that? Chefs, you have half an hour left,
那是半个小时。
that's half an hour.
带上所有的部件。
Bring all the components.
我们正在改变一切。
We are changing everything.
当琳恩和罗曼开始做蛋白霜的时候…
While Leanne and Roman start meringue number two...
. .伊曼纽尔和萨姆在追赶他们的英式奶油。
..Emmanuel and Sam play catch up with their creme anglaise.
他必须很快地把它冷却下来。
He's going to have to cool it down very, very quickly.
如果不凉……
If it doesn't cool...
冰箱，冰箱，冰箱，冰箱。
Freezer, freezer, freezer, freezer.
萨姆从现在起就得赶紧了。
Sam's going to have to rush from now.
他们的蛋白霜也会崩溃。
Their meringue will also collapse.
我把它分成了四个碗，我把它分成了四个碗。
I've split it into four bowls, I've split it into four bowls.
不够的。加油，加油，加油，加油。
Not enough. Come on, come on, come on, come on.
还是没设置好。那你想做什么?
It's still not set properly. Well, what do you want to do?
也许放进裱花袋里。
Maybe into a piping bag.
是的。把它舀出来。你还有，大概半小时吧?
Yeah. Scoop it out. You've still got, what is it, half an hour left?
我想20分钟吧。大厨们，你们还有15分钟，就15分钟。
20 minutes, I'd say. Chefs, you have 15 minutes left, that's 15 minutes.
我们走，我们走，我们走。
Let's go, let's go, let's go.
走，走，走，走，走。在侧面，对吗?
Go, go, go, go, go. In the side, yeah?
侧边哔哔。
BLEEP the side.
怎么样?没有完成。
How is it? Not done.
为了完成他们的漂流计划，各队必须面对最后一个障碍……
To complete their ile flottante, the teams must face one final hurdle...
你能说多少就说多少，巴拉特。
As much of that as you can, Bharat.
. .糖的工作。这是……
..sugar work. This is...
哔哔声。抱歉，它滑得到处都是。
BLEEP. Sorry, it slides all over the place.
加油，甜心!
Come on, sugar!
小心你的手指!
Watch your fingers!
她现在压力太大了。
It's a lot of pressure on her at the moment.
大厨们，你们有十分钟的时间完成你们的浮船。
Chefs, you have ten minutes to finish off your iles flottantes.
这是怎么回事?
How is this?
它上升了一点。是吗?
It's come up a little bit. Yeah?
那就不要煮过头。
Then don't overcook it.
哦!
Oh!
哔哔声。加油，Hideko，你能做到的!
BLEEP. Come on, Hideko, you can do it!
这是煮熟的。它脱落了吗?
It's cooked. Is it coming off?
是吗?
Is it?
它不会一起出来。
It's not coming out together.
怎么样?喜欢,坏的。
How is it? Like, bad.
嗯?坏的。
Huh? Bad.
坏的?
Bad?
就是这样。但是我们可以把它切开。
That is what it is. But we can cut it up.
大厨们，你们还有五分钟。
Chefs, you have five minutes left.
没关系。
It's OK.
小心!
Watch your backs!
好了，停下，哇，哇，哇。不要让它流血。
Right, stop, whoa, whoa, whoa. Don't let it bleed.
如果他们想要更多的话，可以在旁边放一些。
Maybe put some on the side, if they want more.
我想这就够了。这是足够的。
I think this is enough. It's enough.
再放一个进去。快点，快点，
Put another one in there. Make it quick, make it quick,
你还有一分钟，伙计。你要把你的岛放在上面。
you've got one minute to go, mate. You've got your island to go on the top.
蛋白糖饼……把它往下推一点。
Meringues... Just push it down a little bit.
不要太多，不要太多。越高越好。
Not too much, not too much. As high as you can.
也许是上下颠倒。
Maybe upside down.
来吧……
Come on...
是的，是的，是的。
Yes, yes, yes.
7点就可以了，不是吗?7点就可以了。
Seven's fine, no? Seven is fine.
用力推……
Give a good push...
是的，看起来不错。
Yeah, looking good.
大厨们，你们的时间到了。
Chefs, your time is up.
就是这样。
That's it there.
请把您的彩带到展示台。
Please bring your iles flottantes to the display table.
哔哔声。
BLEEP.
半决赛选手们现在面临着评判
The semifinalists' iles flottantes now face the judgments
伯努瓦和珍爱。
of Benoit and Cherish.
这是给你的。哦。
This is for you. Oh.
贿赂。这就是贿赂。
Bribery. That is called bribery.
我没有什么可做的，所以我就带了我有的。
I had nothing to cook, so I just bring what I've got.
所以我得到了浮岛，而珍爱得到了花。是的,抱歉。
So I got the floating island and Cherish got the flower. Yeah, sorry.
好吧,表示。
OK, presentation.
到处都是大块的焦糖。
There's big blocks of caramel everywhere.
棉花糖试图避免这些小珍珠。
Spun sugar is trying to avoid all those little pearls.
它的边缘有点粗糙。
It's a little bit rough around the edges.
果盘是一种百香果芒果。
Compote is a passion fruit mango.
摸起来柔软一点。
Feels a bit softer.
嗯，浮岛已经沉入海底了。
Well, the floating island has sunk under the sea.
微波蛋白霜的质地非常湿润，
The microwaved meringue is very watery kind of texture,
虽然我觉得果冻很好吃，你不这么认为吗?
although I think the jelly is really tasty, don't you think so?
但是没有浮岛。
But there is no floating island.
还没烤好。所以零，零。
It's not baked. So zero, zip.
不管怎样，非常感谢。
Anyway, thank you very much.
再见。谢谢你！
See you later. Thank you.
谢谢你！把你的花拿回去，西奥。但没有成功。
Thank you. Take your flowers back, Theo. It didn't work.
嗯，我们可以看到桌子上有一个很高的浮岛。
Well, we can see a floating island on the table that is high.
有棉花糖。你有一些音量。
There is spun sugar. You got some volume.
水果做得不错。
Nice work with the fruit.
它是五彩缤纷的。
It's colourful.
我们有芒果菠萝果汁，覆盆子果汁。
We have mango and pineapple compote, raspberry compote.
选错蛋白霜了。意大利蛋白霜，让它变得很粘稠。
Wrong choice of meringue. Italian meringue, makes it very moussy.
没有那种胶状的烹饪方法。
You haven't got that gelatinous kind of cooking.
与蛋清相比，糖的含量太高了，
The sugar content is too much compared to the egg white,
所以它很甜。
so as a result it is very sweet.
然而，如果我把它和水果一起吃，它就会平衡。
However, if I ate it together with the compote it sort of balances it.
水果的味道很好。
The fruit element is nice.
非常感谢大家。
Thank you very much, guys.
干杯，谢谢。
Cheers, thank you.
糖出了什么问题?
What went wrong with the sugar?
太迟了。对我来说，这是未完成的事业。
Left it too late. For me, it's unfinished business.
话虽如此，我还是喜欢你做的每个碗，
Having said that, I like the fact that you've done individual bowls,
让我们尝一尝。
but let's taste it.
我们在糖里加了一点牛轧糖。
We've added a touch of nougatine to the sugar.
在你的浮岛中央
In the middle of your floating island
你应该吃点樱桃果冻。
you should have some cherry jelly.
我很喜欢你往蛋白派里塞的果冻，
I quite like your jelly that you pipe into the meringue,
因为人们没有预料到这一点，当你切过去的时候，会有一个很好的
because people don't expect that and when you cut through there's a nice
里面有惊喜。
surprise in there.
我相信你的蛋清很硬。
I believe your egg whites are firm.
甜度很棒。
The sweetness is great.
话虽如此，我个人还是更喜欢一些东西
Having said that, I would personally have preferred something
更奢侈一点。你知道吗，你可以去异国情调。
a little bit more extravagant. You know, you could have gone exotic.
你今天的创作不够原创。
It's not original enough, your creation today.
非常感谢。
Thank you very much.
是啊，别再发出哔哔声了。
Yeah, not to do this BLEEP thing again.
罗曼，琳恩，对今早的挑战不后悔吗?
Romain, Leanne, no regrets with this morning's challenge?
我想我也会这么做的。
Um, I would have done it I think.
这和我期待的剧情差远了。
Well, it's far from the drama I was expecting.
不是最有想象力的，对吧?
Not the most imaginative, I would say, yeah?
我们看到小蛋白派，
We see little meringues,
如果它们是附加的，我不介意
which I don't mind if they are an addition
去一个美丽的浮岛，
to a beautiful floating island,
我很难在底部看到。
which I struggle to see at the very bottom.
它只是一个立方体，一个小立方体。
It's only the cube, the little cube.
这是唯一的一座浮岛吗?
Oh, so this is the only floating island there is?
是的，它不是从模子里出来的，
Yes, it was not coming out of the mould,
所以我们只能把剩下的东西弄得可爱一点。
so we had to get cute with what was left, basically.
这是朗姆酒浆果果盘。
So you've got a rum and berry compote.
看起来有点像伊顿公学的烂摊子。
It looks a little bit like an Eton mess.
就味道而言，我喜欢配苹果汁。
Flavour wise I like the compote to go with it.
基本上就是蛋白霜和浆果。
It's meringue and berries, basically.
这只是两份的份量。
This is only two portions size.
我们要求6到8小时。
We asked for six to eight.
你没有完成简报。
You did not meet the brief.
我们要求一个浮岛，你没有满足的简要。
We asked for a floating island, you did not meet the brief.
明天我真的很想去看看。
Tomorrow I really want to see.
谢谢你！谢谢你！谢谢大家。
Thank you. Thank you. Thank you, guys.
事情就是这样。很好。明天就是一场噩梦。
It is what it is. Fair enough. Tomorrow, it's a nightmare.
不结束就不算结束。完全正确。
It's not over until it's over. Exactly.
好吧，让我们忘记它，让我们明天更强大地回来。
OK, let's forget it and let's come back tomorrow stronger.
我们不会退居二线然后说，哦，是的，
We're not going to take the back seat and say, oh, yeah,
我们已经搞定了。是啊，我们明天肯定有比赛。
we've nailed this one. Yeah, we've definitely got a fight tomorrow.
明天的现场电镀盛典需要更多的个性元素
Tomorrow's live plating extravaganza requires more individual elements
比之前的任何展览都好
than any showpiece that's come before it,
所以今晚的黄金时段是取得成功的重要机会。
so tonight's golden hour is a vital chance to get ahead.
所以今天的秘方挑战很难，
So today's secret recipe challenge was a tough one,
我想可以这么说。
I think it's fair to say.
希尔顿公园巷，他们做得怎么样?
Hilton Park Lane, how did they do?
我真的很享受父子关系。
I really enjoyed the father and son partnership.
他们俩合作得很好。
They both worked together so well.
正如我们所知，伊曼纽尔用蛋糕造出了山姆，然后他变成了一个
As we know Emanuel built Sam out of cake and then he came to life as a
魔法学徒，所以说得通。
magic apprentice, so it makes sense.
Darryl和Bharat，他们是从最底层开始的
Darryl and Bharat, they've been going from the bottom
敬一个进入决赛的有力竞争者。
to a very strong contender to go to the final.
皇家酒店咖啡厅和甜蜜艺术实验室，
Both Hotel Cafe Royal and Sweet Art Lab,
目前它们几乎没有浮动。
they are barely floating at the moment.
压力很大，因为他们正在为决赛而战。
Pressure is on because they are fighting for the final.
早....
Morning.
早上好，厨师们。
Good morning, chefs.
我们希望你从昨天的不可能任务中恢复过来，
We hope you've recovered from yesterday's mission impossible,
因为今天，评委们决定重新设计表演挑战
because today, the judges have decided to reinvent the showpiece challenge -
剧透警告-他们并没有让它变得更容易。
and spoiler alert - they've not made it any easier.
我是说，我试着对他们说，学期快结束了，我们不能都看个视频吗?
I mean, I've tried to say to them, it's nearly the end of term, can't we all just watch a video?
但那就像铅蛋奶酥一样。
But that went down like a lead souffle.
那么，法官们，你们能解释一下今天的考验吗?
So, judges, would you be kind enough to explain today's ordeal?
我是说——表演挑战?
I mean - showpiece challenge?
厨师们，今天，我们要为你制作最壮观的蛋糕
Chefs, today, we would like you to make the most spectacular cake you
至少做过三层。
have ever made, at least three tier.
今天挑战的主题是冒险。
The theme for today's challenge is adventure.
所以你还必须创建一个
So you must also create a further
12个组件，然后在我们面前直播。
12 components which you will then plate up in front of us live.
你的表演必须非常精彩。
Your performance needs to be spectacular.
厨师们，你们有四个小时。
So chefs, you have four hours.
时间从现在开始。
The time starts now.
好，好，好。
OK, OK, OK.
这个三层蛋糕是他们做过的最大的蛋糕
The three tiered cake is the largest cake they've ever been asked to make
为了比赛。
for the competition.
它必须足够大，能喂饱40个人。
It must be big enough to feed 40 people.
如果有人对我说，
If someone normally said to me,
你得去做一个三层蛋糕，
you had to go and do a three-tiered cake,
你不可能在四小时内做好。
you wouldn't have it ready in four hours.
但这还不是全部。
But that's not all.
也会有现场电镀，
There will be live plating as well,
既令人兴奋又令人畏惧。
so exciting and daunting at the same time.
这道美味的甜点就是在这里制作出来的
Live plating is where a spectacular dessert is created
就在你眼前。
in front of your eyes.
这是表演时间，现场电镀，三层蛋糕，
This is showtime, live plating, three tiered cake,
他们要准备什么才能让这一切一起工作和创造
which they will have to prepare to make it all work together and create
一个伟大的爱冒险的观众。
a great adventurous spectator.
这是最颓废和最具戏剧性的美食表演艺术。
This is gastronomic performance art at its most decadent and dramatic.
我想要惊喜。
I want to be surprised.
我想看到运动。
I want to see movement.
我希望他们与我接触。
I want them to engage with me.
我想在桌子上看到爆炸和烟火。
I want to see explosion and firework on the table.
我所期望的不会比这少。
I expect nothing less than that.
哇。他们想要更健康的，就给他们更健康的。
Wow. They want it fitter, give them fitter.
这是一个演示，也许是Benoit。
This is a presentation, maybe Benoit.
早上好。
Good morning to you.
早....事情进展如何?
Morning. How did it go?
我们对你将要想出的东西很感兴趣。
We are so intrigued with what you're going to come up with.
你现在的设计是怎样的?
What's the story of your designs today?
这个故事就像生存，生存到侏罗纪世界，
The story is like surviving, surviving into a Jurassic world,
像恐龙。
like dinosaurs.
对于我们这样的幸存者来说，这是一个非常危险的挑战。
This is a very risky challenge for survivors like us.
所以你带着你的生存本能。
So you bring your survival instinct.
是的，每一个挑战，几乎死了但还活着。
Yes, every single challenge, almost dead but still alive.
在令人失望的第一天之后，
After a disappointing first day,
Sweet Art Lab的Hideko和Theo
Sweet Art Lab's Hideko and Theo
希望它们的侏罗纪经历能拯救它们免于灭绝。
hope their Jurassic experience will save them from extinction.
它的特色是貂色饼干骨头、恐龙蛋和香草，
It will feature sable biscuit bones, dinosaur eggs and vanilla,
抹茶巧克力雪纺海绵火山蛋糕，
matcha and chocolate chiffon sponge volcano cakes,
会喷出覆盆子熔岩和液氮烟。
which will spew molten raspberry lava and liquid nitrogen smoke.
这可能很危险。
That could be dangerous.
我们不会吃掉任何液氮。
We're not going to be eating any of this liquid nitrogen.
老实说，我们得挺过这一关。
We're going to have to survive this one, to be honest with you.
对这个超级兴奋。你兴奋吗，珍爱?
Super excited for this one. Are you excited, Cherish?
我超级兴奋。
I am super excited.
你们会有移动的恐龙吗?它不会动。
Are you going to have moving dinosaurs? It won't be moving.
你要打扮成幸存者吗?
Are you going to be dressed as a survivor?
你可能会感到惊讶。你可能会感到惊讶!
You might be surprised. You might be surprised!
在半决赛中幸存下来也是头等大事
Surviving this semifinal is also a top priority
皇家咖啡厅的Leanne and Romain。
for Hotel Cafe Royal's Leanne and Romain.
所以他们从无畏精神中汲取灵感
So they've taken inspiration from the fearless spirit
印第安纳·琼斯。
of Indiana Jones.
你知道，你总是看冒险电影，
You know, you always see an adventure movie,
有座摇摇晃晃的桥，有点像丛林桥。
there's a wonky bridge, kind of jungle bridge.
我们要砸碎一些会掉下来的巨石。
We're going to smash, like, some boulders that are going to come running down.
我们要用干冰
We're gonna use dry ice
在旅程结束时制造烟雾效果。
to make a smoky effect at the end of the journey.
为了避免糕点店末日之殿，
In a bid to avoid the Temple of Patisserie Doom,
它们正在寻找结晶巧克力草的藏宝图，
they're navigating a treasure map of crystallised chocolate grass,
巧克力土和焦糖布丁。
chocolate soil and creme brulees.
最后是三层芒果巧克力蛋糕，
Culminating in a three tier chocolate cake filled with mango,
青柠香草果汁，百香果和芒果甘纳许。
lime and vanilla compote and passion fruit and mango ganache.
在第四个蛋糕上平衡的是他们摇摇晃晃的桥，他们的
Balanced on the fourth cake is their wonky bridge, from which their
巨石会下降。
boulders will descend.
这就是你在黄金时段做的事吗?
Is that what you've done during the golden hour?
这就是我们今天要做的。
This is what we've got to do today.
黄金时间也差不多。
Golden hour is about the same.
哦，我的天啊。我们要讲一个故事。
Oh, my gosh. We're going to tell a story.
好的。用我们的盘子。
OK. With our plating.
就像一张藏宝图。
It's like a treasure map.
宝藏地图。哇。
Treasure map. Wow.
你今天有什么计划?
What kind of strategy do you have for today?
每个人都在跑步，这就是策略。
Everybody is running, that's the strategy.
运行。我们要推它。
Running. We're going to push it.
在希尔顿公园巷，他们正在计划一些更多的东西
Over at Hilton Park Lane they are planning something a little more
他们要感谢山姆的未婚妻妮可。
relaxing and they have Sam's fiancee Nicole to thank for it.
我们要去加勒比海风格的地方，
We're going sort of Caribbean-esque,
让我有心情去巴巴多斯。
get me in the mood for when I go to Barbados.
当我告诉她我要参加比赛时，我说，
When I told her I was gonna do the competition, I said,
之后我带你走。要让她保持甜蜜
I'll take you away afterwards. Got to keep her sweet,
否则我不确定我还有什么可回去的。
otherwise I'm not sure I'll have anything to go back to.
他们的热带雨林之旅将以酸橙鱼子酱岛为特色，
Their tropical rainforest adventure will feature lime caviar islands,
芙蓉蛋白霜和巧克力椰子。
hibiscus meringue rocks and chocolate coconuts.
他们的三层蛋糕会放在一个巨大的巧克力架子上
And their three tiered cake will sit on a giant chocolate stand
像瀑布一样倾泻而下。
and cascade like a waterfall.
里面会有椰子汁，椰子，朗姆酒，果冻，
It will be filled with pina colada flavours, coconut, rum, jelly,
菠萝果冻和椰子芝士蛋糕。
pineapple jelly and coconut cheesecake.
他们还提供了合适的椰林酒。
And they are serving up proper pina coladas.
会点鸡尾酒。
Got a bit of cocktail making.
你基本上是在策划贿赂。
You are planning a bribery, basically.
有人听我说过这个词吗?
Has anybody heard that word coming from me?
这是演出的一部分，是娱乐。
It's part of the show, it's entertainment.
我当然是在逗你。
I was teasing you, of course.
那么这就足够让你进入决赛了吗?我当然希望如此。
So is that going to be enough to take you through to the final? I certainly hope so.
它将。是的。信念。
It will. Yeah. Conviction.
是的,当然!
Yes, definitely!
是的,当然有。
Yes, definitely.
说到冒险，
When it comes to adventures,
度假村世界的Darryl和Bharat的乐趣理念就没那么新奇了。
Resort World's Darryl and Bharat's idea of fun is a lot less exotic.
主题是什么?我们称它为伟大的户外，
What's the theme? Call it the great outdoors,
因为我经常出去露营，冬天不带帐篷。
because I quite often go out camping, without tents in the winter.
哇。你就带着睡袋去吗?
Wow. You just go with a sleeping bag?
是啊，我们可以搭个庇护所或者就在星空下睡觉。
Yeah, we'll make a shelter or we'll just sleep under the stars.
我去露营。你呢?
I go camping. Do you?
哦,哈哈。
Oh, ha-ha.
他们粗糙的伪装蛋糕将用木槿花装饰
Their rugged camouflage cake will be decorated with hibiscus flowers
以榛子海绵为特色，
and feature layers of hazelnut sponge,
黑加仑果冻和黑巧克力慕斯。
blackcurrant jelly and dark chocolate mousse.
他们的罗勒凝胶和黑莓布丁应该
Their live plating elements of basil gel and blackberry brulees should
唤起对英国荒野的探险。
evoke an expedition to the wilds of Britain.
这能让你进入决赛吗?我希望如此。
Is it going to get you through to the final? I hope so.
我觉得味道和外观完全不同，
Flavours and the look are completely different, I think,
它有…烤豆，培根?这主意不错。
it has... Baked beans, bacon? That's not a bad idea.
香肠。是的,是的。
Sausages. Yeah, yeah.
在阁楼上放了太久的睡袋的味道。
The smell of a sleeping bag that's been in a loft for too long.
是的。我看过国家电视台。
Yeah. I've watched Countryfile.
蛋糕准备好了。
The cake is ready.
我可以建造它。但由于时间限制，
I can build it. But with the time limit on it,
这真的不那么令人欣慰。
it's not really that comforting.
三个蛋糕要做。
Three cakes to do.
所以很忙，很忙，很忙。
So it's busy, busy, busy.
一定要用力。
Definitely have to push.
希望不要花太长时间定型。
Hopefully it won't take too long to set.
但制作三层蛋糕只是战斗的一部分。
But making the three tiered cake is just part of the battle.
大厨们，你们已经完成一半了。
Chefs, you are halfway through.
还剩两个小时。
So that's two hours left.
这些团队还有另一项艰巨的任务。
The teams have another mammoth task.
创建12个带电电镀元素。
Creating the 12 live plating elements.
这是芒果泥，看起来像生鸡蛋。
This is mango puree, it looks like a raw egg.
他们越有野心……
The more ambitious they are...
我们要敲开其中一个椰子。
We'll crack one of these coconuts.
他们进入决赛的机会就越大。
The more chance they'll have of making it through to the final.
时间总是不够用，这就是问题所在。
Never have enough time here, that is the problem.
这座桥差不多完工了。
The bridge is pretty much done.
哦,哦。
Oh, oh.
但Leanne和Romain的冒险却止步不前。
But Leanne and Romain's adventure has been stopped in its tracks.
哔哔声。
BLEEP.
重建桥梁，如果我可以的话。
Rebuild the bridge, if I can.
来吧!
Come on!
哔哔声。
BLEEP.
没有桥，他们的轰动性表演
Without a bridge, their blockbusting performance
没有大结局。
has no grand finale.
这将是一座断桥。
It will be a broken bridge.
大厨们，你们还有一个小时。
Chefs, you have one hour left.
那是一个小时!
That's one hour!
小心点。
Be careful with that.
虽然大多数团队可以继续建造他们巨大的
While most of the teams can push on constructing their gigantic
分层蛋糕……我得说，感觉很紧张。
tiered cakes... I must say, it feels quite tense.
不幸的是，由于时间不够，我们承受了很大的压力。
A lot of pressure on us, unfortunately, due to a lack of time.
. .琳恩和罗曼正在努力挽救他们摇摇欲坠的桥，
..Leanne and Romain are battling to save their rickety bridge,
他们的盛典中最引人注目的明星。
the star attraction of their extravaganza.
哔哔的声音
BEEP
它在我手里融化了。所以罗曼和琳恩，
It's melting in my hand. So Romain and Leanne,
我注意到已经有几处裂缝了。
have noticed there was already a couple of cracks.
但是，嘿，他们非常专注。
But, hey, they are very focused.
在希尔顿公园巷，他们正在做一个巨大的巧克力摊。
And Hilton Park Lane, they are making a huge chocolate stand.
展台会像电镀一样被赋予生命吗?
Is the stand going to be brought to life as well as the live plating?
因为他把全部精力都放在证人席上了。
Because he's focusing all his energy on the stand.
伯努瓦，那名胜世界呢?
But Benoit, what about the Resorts World?
他们要去乡下某个地方露营。我喜欢露营!
They are going camping somewhere in the countryside. I love camping!
我有点担心。
I've got a little concern.
你用它做了什么让它变得特别?
What is it that you do with it to make it special?
他们会不会太过安全?
Will they go a little too safe?
还有Hideko和Theo
And we've got Hideko and Theo -
侏罗纪世界。
the Jurassic World.
在过去，这总是一个好概念。
In the past, it's always good a concept.
然而，糟糕的交付。
However, poor delivery.
我希望他们今天能来。
I hope they're going to make it today.
我要用力。
I need to push.
来吧!希尔顿公园巷，你好!
Come on! Hilton Park Lane, hi!
这足以让你进入决赛吗?这是你进入决赛的门票吗?
Is this going to be good enough to get you to the final? Is this your ticket to the final?
因为我们有期末考试。这就是我们现在得到的。
Cos we've got the final. That's what we've got now.
我真的希望如此。在规定的时间内，我们会尽可能多地去。
I really do hope so. We're going as much as we possibly can do in the time frame.
它是热带。你最喜欢的鸡尾酒是什么?
It's tropical. What's your favourite cocktail?
色情明星马提尼。色情明星马提尼?
Porn Star Martini. A Porn Star Martini?
山姆，我完全没想到你会这么说!
Sam, that's not what I expected you to say at all!
大厨们，你们还有半小时。
Chefs, you have half an hour left.
有很多……
There's a lot...
有很多事情要做。天气很热，不是吗?
There's a lot to do. It's very heated, isn't it?
今天天气很紧张。
It's got very tense today.
不过这是决赛的一个名额。我们希望看到你做得好。
It's a place in the finals, though. We want to see you do well.
所以我现在就得做。对不起，如果你不介意的话。
So I need to do it now. Sorry, if you don't mind.
我必须这么做。哦!我必须这么做。
I have to. Oh! I have to.
我很抱歉。我必须这么做。
I'm sorry. I have to.
蛋糕，放进去。
The cakes, get in there.
即使他们的蛋糕活过来了……
Even if their cakes are coming to life...
.除非他们把所有的电镀道具都准备好了，准备好了，
.unless they have all their live plating props stood by, ready for action,
他们的表演仍有可能失败。
their performance could still be a flop.
在压力下。这些还没弄好。
Under pressure. Still got these to ball up.
有冰淇淋，热巧克力慕斯，黑加仑豆腐。
There's ice cream, warm chocolate mousse, blackcurrant curd.
用于带电电镀。
For the live plating.
芒果格兰尼塔丸子。
Mango granita balls.
芙蓉酥皮。我们想让它们看起来有点像石头，
Hibiscus meringue. We wanted them to look a bit like rocks,
所以他们……
so they're...
他们了。有很多事要做。
They're cracked. A lot to do.
机不可失，时不再来。
It's now or never.
大厨们，你们还有十分钟。
Chefs, you have ten minutes left.
哔哔的声音
BEEP
这些花瓣用来装饰我们的蛋糕。
These petals to decorate our cake.
哔哔的声音
BEEP
从那里面拿不出一个。他们都被卡住了。
Can't get one out of that. They're all stuck.
快!加油，加油，加油，加油!
Quick! Come on, come on, come on, come on!
以马内利!
Emmanuel!
以马内利!我需要一些帮助。
Emmanuel! I need some help.
底座不是平的。
The base wasn't flat.
它在疯狂地摇晃。
It's wobbling like crazy.
我要你拿着那个。
I need you to hold that.
我选了一个合适的角度。
Went for a proper angle on that one.
我只需要它能粘住……停!
I just need it to stick... Stop!
停止移动顶部!这不是粘……
Stop moving the top! It's not stick...
注意你在蛋糕上的位置，因为我不想让你毁了整个…
Watch where you put it on the cake cos I don't want you to ruin the whole...
大厨们，你们还有一分钟。
Chefs, you have one minute left.
哔哔的声音
BEEP
有时间，伙计!
Got a minute, mate!
当然是在压力之下。
Under pressure, of course.
哔哔的声音
BEEP
真是一场噩梦!
What a nightmare!
推动!以马内利!
Push! Emmanuel!
大厨们，你们的时间到了!你的时间到了!
Chefs, your time is up! Your time is up!
天Moley !
Holy Moley!
我迫不及待地想看到它的实际应用。
I can't wait to see it in action.
四个令人惊叹的三层蛋糕和几十个活电镀元素，
Four stunning three-tiered cakes and dozens of live plating elements,
全部在五小时内完成。
all produced in five hours.
现在决赛的席位岌岌可危，
And now with a place in the final at stake,
舞台已经搭建好了。
the stage is set.
好了，伙计们，让我们开始吧。好戏上演。
Well, guys, let's get this show on the road. Showtime.
这是我们的椰子。我们代表小岛。
This is our coconut. We're kind of representing little islands.
一些酸橙和鱼子酱。
Some lime and caviar.
黄色来自芒果。
Yellow from the mango.
西瓜果冻。
Watermelon jellies.
白巧克力和香草。
White chocolate and vanilla.
龙的水果。
Dragon fruit.
我用冰镇果汁朗姆酒来助兴。
I help all of this with some pina colada...drinks.
哇!
Woo!
哦，天哪，天哪。
Oh, my, my, my.
我爱它，爱它，爱它。
I love it, love it, love it.
向你鞠躬。
And my bows to you.
谢谢你！哇。你让我觉得我现在真的在晒太阳，
Thank you. Wow. You make me feel like I am actually suntanning now,
喝着我的果汁朗姆酒。
having my pina colada.
你为我们送上了一道美丽的，充满异国情调的甜点。
You've delivered a beautiful, exotic display of dessert.
欢呼。
Cheers.
你能给我们一块蛋糕吗?
If you could serve us perhaps a slice of your cake?
这是菠萝馅饼。
Got pineapple confit.
有椰子慕斯。
Got a coconut mousse.
我不太确定。
I'm not too sure.
让我有点失望的是你的蛋糕，
What is perhaps a bit disappointing for me is in your cake,
我希望那是真正的椰林果汁朗姆酒
which I was hoping to be truly pina colada,
椰子比其他任何东西都多。
was more coconut than anything else.
但是，您引入的所有元素实际上都绑定在一起。
However, all the elements that you bring in really bind together.
我看不出盘子上的错误。
I can't spot a mistake on the plate.
谢谢你！桑特。
Thank you. Sante.
欢呼。
Cheers.
我们要带大家经历一场地图上的冒险
Well, we're gonna take us through an adventure to the map
去真正找到宝藏。把它拿走。
to actually find the treasure. Take it away.
音乐:柴可夫斯基的《糖梅仙女之舞》
MUSIC: Dance Of The Sugar Plum Fairy by Tchaikovsky
巧克力屑。
Chocolate crumbs.
芒果凝胶。
Mango gel.
没关系。
That's OK.
哦吼!
Woohoo!
我认为这很有趣。我们玩得很开心，不是吗?
I think it's good fun. We had fun, didn't we?
是的。好的。
Yes. OK.
我可以继续，就像…
I can continue, just like...
这部分很有趣。
That part is fun.
但我敢说，这有点笨拙，
But it's a little bit, should I dare say, clumsy,
比如，当我们看到你在焦糖焦糖焦糖布丁时。
i.e. when we saw you caramelising your creme brulee.
烧得太猛了，桌子都要熔化了。
So much firing that you could potentially melt the table down.
这种蛋糕很过时。
The cake is quite old-fashioned.
我希望你能带来一些很禅意的东西，
I was hoping that you'd bring in something that is quite Zen,
一些很前卫的东西，因为我知道你们俩能做什么。
something that is quite avant-garde, because I know what you two can do.
请给我们来一片。
Please, serve us a slice.
我怎么看蛋糕就是我现在怎么吃。
How I look at the cake is how I'm eating now.
没有烟花。
There's no firework.
只有来自百香果的活力。
There is only the zing that is from the passion fruit.
没有小爆炸。
There's no chitty bang.
我能说"大爆炸"吗?奇蒂砰砰。
Can I say chitty bang? Chitty bang bang.
没有“小砰砰”。
There's no chitty bang bang.
但泡沫，凝胶和格兰尼塔让你的调色板焕然一新。
But the foam, the gels and the granita refresh your palette.
我认为这个想法和意图很好。
The idea, intention, I think, is great.
谢谢你！谢谢你的努力。谢谢你！
Thank you. Thank you for all your effort. Thank you.
都是关于恐龙的。
All about dinosaur.
所以，是的，这是在侏罗纪冒险中生存。
So, yeah, it's surviving in a Jurassic adventure.
音乐:约翰·施特劳斯二世的蓝色多瑙河圆舞曲
MUSIC: The Blue Danube Waltz by Johann Strauss II
舞蹈的编排，袅袅的烟雾。
The choreography, the smoke that is bubbling away.
今天是你们的舞台。
You own the stage today.
侏罗纪世界与分子天文学相遇。
The Jurassic world meets molecular astronomy.
哇!伙计们，你们把我困在这里了。
Wow! You know, guys, you've got me here.
我都笑掉裤子了。裤子了吗?
I'm laughing my pants off. Pants off?
但它们仍然开着。还开着，还开着。
But they are still on. They're still on, they're still on.
我只希望你的味道能传达出来。
I just hope your flavour profile delivers.
我感觉自己像在吃鸡蛋。
I felt like I was eating egg.
然而，里面有一种水果的味道。
However, it was a fruity element that's inside there.
真的很喜欢吃。
Really enjoyed eating it.
我们有三种口味的雪纺蛋糕。
We've got the chiffon cake with three flavours.
香草，巧克力和抹茶。
Vanilla, chocolate and the matcha.
真的把我带回了童年
Really take me back to my childhood
就像我妈妈给我做雪纺一样。
as how my mum make the chiffon for me.
非常感谢。
Thank you very much.
我现在真的很想念我妈妈。
And I now really miss my mum.
我感觉不到雪纺蛋糕的味道，
The flavour combination within the chiffon cake, I don't sense,
因为你所有的成分都含有太多的酸度。
because there is so much acidity on all your components.
话虽如此，我还是喜欢你的巧克力。
Having said that, I love your chocolate.
我最喜欢的部分是，
And the part I really enjoy,
实际上，是覆盆子醋酱。
actually, the raspberry vinegar coulis.
干得好。谢谢你！谢谢你！谢谢你！
So well done. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you.
谢谢。
Arigato.
这是关于户外的故事。
It's the story of the outdoors.
请给我们一个惊喜。
Please, surprise us.
音乐:Leo Delibes的Flower Duet (Lakme)
MUSIC: Flower Duet (Lakme) by Leo Delibes
红醋栗和罗勒凝胶。
Redcurrant and basil gel.
巧克力奶油。
Chocolate creme.
热巧克力慕斯。
Warm chocolate mousse.
巧克力球。
Chocolate spheres.
黑莓火烧后。
Blackberry brulees.
大厨，你跟我说露营的事时，
Chef, when you were telling me about your camping,
我非常兴奋。
I got all excited.
我梦到烧烤了。
I was dreaming about barbecuing.
我梦见马在四处小跑。
I was dreaming about horse trotting around.
然而，当我看到你怎么装盘的时候，我有点泄气了。
However, when I started to see how you plate it, I get a bit deflated.
这有点令人失望。你们都很安全。
It's a bit disappointing. You guys have been safe.
蛋糕里可能还会有更多。
There might be more to come in the cake.
我们有巧克力慕斯，黑加仑果冻，榛子海绵。
We have a chocolate mousse, a blackcurrant jelly, hazelnut sponge.
我喜欢吃你的蛋糕，
I enjoy eating your cake,
有了巧克力，还有你放进去的慕斯，
you know, with the chocolate, the mousse that you put in,
但没有什么能点亮你的蛋糕，让它充满活力。
but there's nothing to lit up your cake and bring it alive.
你拿的罗勒凝胶很好吃。
The basil gel that you've got there is on the money.
但你选的味道很精致。
But you've chosen flavours which are pretty delicate.
我对你所做的事感到不满意。
I'm not feeling wow by what you've done.
如果你想晋级总决赛，
If you are to move up to the Grand Final,
你现在必须发泄出来。再也不安全了。
you have to let it all out now. Safe no more.
非常感谢。谢谢你！干杯,家伙。
Thank you very much. Thank you. Cheers, guys.
欢呼。
Cheers.
能给我一杯果汁朗姆酒吗?
Can I have a pina colada?
在那之后我需要它。
I need it after that.
基于这两个挑战，
Based on both challenges,
Benoit和珍惜现在将对球队进行排名，
Benoit and Cherish will now rank the teams,
只有前三名才能进入总决赛。
and only the top three will take their place in the Grand Final.
毫无疑问，我们为自己感到骄傲。
We've done ourselves proud, there's no doubt about it.
我们把所有…所有的一切。几乎是所有的东西。
We've put all...everything into that. Like, literally everything.
你当然想通过决赛了，绝对想。
You wanna go through final, of course, big-time.
压力是存在的。我觉得我们有危险。
The pressure is there. And I think we are in danger.
我很乐意接通。这意味着一切，你知道的。
I would love to get through. It would mean everything, you know.
我们很努力才走到这一步。这是最后一步。
We've worked really hard to get here. And it's the last step.
我们只能自豪地说:“是的，我们进入了决赛。”
We could be only proud to say, "Yeah, we made it to the final".
这绝对是件很棒的事。
Like, definitely, it would be something great.
Benoit和珍惜已经做出了决定。
Benoit and Cherish have made their decision.
第一名的队伍在整个比赛中表现最好。
The team in first place had the best day of their entire competition.
恭喜你……
Congratulations...
甜蜜艺术实验室的Hideko和Theo，你们进入决赛了。
Hideko and Theo from Sweet Art Lab, you are through to the final.
第二名是评委的排名
In second place, the judges ranked
希尔顿公园巷的伊曼纽尔和山姆。
Emmanuel and Sam from the Hilton Park Lane.
恭喜你，你也进入决赛了。
Congratulations, you're also through to the final.
那就只剩皇家咖啡馆酒店的琳恩和罗曼了
Which leaves Leanne and Romain from Hotel Cafe Royal
还有来自名胜世界的Darryl和Bharat。
and Darryl and Bharat from Resorts World.
你们帮我回忆了一下
You guys just sort of helped me to remember
为什么我一开始会选择烘焙，
why I got into baking in the first place,
所以不管今天发生什么，你们都很棒。
so whatever happens today, you guys are awesome.
伯努瓦和珍爱同意了
Benoit and Cherish agreed
这是将要退出比赛的队伍
that the team who'll be leaving the competition
今晚是……
tonight are...
琳恩和罗曼。
Leanne and Romain.
我会想你的。我也会想你的!
Gonna miss you. Gonna miss you, too!
当你离开这样的比赛时，你总是很伤心，
You're always sad when you are leaving this kind of competition,
尤其是现在，我们离决赛只有一步之遥。
especially now, when we are just at the door to the final.
祝贺你。我知道你今天要走了
Congratulations. I know you're leaving today,
但还是恭喜你。你一路来到了半决赛。
but it's congratulations. You came all the way to the semifinal.
我只是为……感到骄傲。是啊，你应该。
I'm just proud of... Yeah, you should be.
我认为它从总体上改变了我们。
I think it's changed us as people in general.
我们从这个过程中学到了很多。
Like, we've learnt so much from doing it.
这是一次很棒的经历。
It's been a great experience.
我认为最好的部分是……
I think the best bit...
我度过了最美好的一天!
The best day ever had!
最后。
Finally.
你做到了。你做到了。你做到了。
You did it. You did it. You did it.
哔哔声。
BLEEP.
我们可以用这个吗?是的,邪恶。绝对的。
Are we allowed to use that? Yeah, wicked. Absolutely.
感觉很棒。是的。
Feel great. Yeah.
很神奇的。像羔羊拉里一样快乐。
Amazing. Happy as Larry the lamb.
喂?我们进入决赛了!
Hello? We're in the final!
电话里的尖叫
SCREAMING FROM PHONE
下次……经过深思熟虑……
Next time... After much deliberation...
这件事昨天就该做了。
This should have been done yesterday.
评委们已经决定…
The judges have decided...
2018年《烘焙大赛:专业选手》的获胜者……
That the winners of Bake Off: The Professionals 2018...
我们的时间不多了。
We're now running out of time.
是……
Are...
你能不能别这么用力敲桌子?
Can you please not bang that table so hard?
哔哔声。
BLEEP.
你有什么能打动伯努瓦和珍爱吗?
Do you have what it takes to impress Benoit and Cherish?
如果你想申请的话
If you would like to apply
想了解下一期《烘焙大赛:专业人士》，请访问:
for the next series of Bake Off: The Professionals, visit:
音乐:在山王的大厅里，格里格
MUSIC: In The Hall Of The Mountain King by Grieg
字幕由红蜂传媒制作
Subtitles by Red Bee Media
大家好，欢迎来到专业烘焙大赛。
Hello and welcome to Bake Off: The Professionals.
我简直不敢相信这是总决赛。是的，在十周之后
I can hardly believe it's the grand final. Yes, after 10 weeks of
激烈的竞争，坚硬的山峰和镜子般的光泽，
fierce competition, stiff peaks and mirror glazes,
最终会有一支队伍加冕
finally one team will be crowned
英国最好的专业糕点师
the best professional pastry chefs in Britain.
会是名胜世界吗?
Will it be Resorts World?
是希尔顿公园巷吗?
Will it be Hilton Park Lane?
会是甜蜜艺术实验室吗?
Will it be Sweet Art Lab?
只有一个巨大的挑战挡在胜利者的路上
Only one mammoth challenge stands in the way of the winner
在苏塞克斯菲尔广场的大厅里宣布
being announced here in the Great Hall of Firle Place in Sussex.
哦，我太兴奋了。哦，我好紧张。
Oh, I'm so excited. Oh, I'm so nervous.
当我紧张的时候，
Oh, when I'm nervous,
为了释放我所有的能量，我总是做一些体力活动。像什么?
to let out all my energy I always do something physical. Like what?
哦。
Oh.
最后一次……
Last time...
. .一场壮观的现场电镀对决…
..a spectacular live plating showdown...
跳伞、高空滑索……
Parachuting, zip wiring...
. .甜蜜艺术实验室的Hideko和Theo成功了。
..saw Hideko and Theo of Sweet Art Lab triumph.
伙计们，你们让我来了。
You know, guys, you got me here.
但那是皇家咖啡馆的琳恩和罗曼……
But it was Leanne and Romain of the Hotel Cafe Royale...
没有厚颜无耻的刘海。厚颜无耻的砰砰的枪声。
There is no cheeky bang. Cheeky bang-bang.
. .刚刚错过了决赛的机会。
..who just missed out on a place in the grand final.
我会想你的。我也会想你的!
I'm going to miss you. I'm going to miss you too!
现在整个比赛归结为一个史诗般的挑战…
Now the entire competition comes down to one epic challenge...
没时间了。回来了!
Running out of time. Back!
. .来决定获胜者……
..to decide the winners...
我不太确定。
I'm not really sure.
. .《烘焙大赛:专业人士》
..of Bake Off: The Professionals...
我们对你的想法很感兴趣。
We are blown away with your concept.
这是哇!
This is wow!
. . 2018。
..2018.
你能不能别撞那张桌子?
Can you please not bang that table?
我现在要去旅行了。
I'm going to trip now.
啊!
Ah!
灾难!
Disaster!
这之后我能接受心理咨询吗?
Can I have counselling after this?
经过九周的艰苦训练，一切都归结为接下来的两天。
After nine gruelling weeks, it all comes down to the next two days.
等等，等等，等等。
Wait, wait, wait.
代表伯明翰高端酒店名胜世界，
Representing the high-end Birmingham hotel Resorts World,
达瑞尔和巴拉特在感情激动的第一周差点分手。
Darryl and Bharat nearly went out in an emotional first week.
那里的一切都不对。
Everything is just not right in there.
哦，伙计，没事的。
DARRYL CRIES Oh, man, it's all right.
但他们表现出顽强的战斗精神……
But they have since shown a dogged fighting spirit...
我们会做到的。我们能做到!
We will do it. We can do it!
. .为了调味，要放平。
..and flat for flavour.
我要开始跳恰恰了!
I'll start doing a cha-cha-cha!
哦，真漂亮。
Ooh, it's beautiful.
这是关键时刻，明天我可能会喜极而泣……
This is crunch time, there might be tears of joy tomorrow from me...
从他。
From him.
我已经振作起来了。
I've manned up.
草莓在里面。
Strawberries in there.
它是直的吗?是的。
Is it straight? Yes.
从伦敦五星级酒店希尔顿公园巷，
From London's five-star Hilton Park Lane,
伊曼纽尔和山姆带来了视觉盛宴……
Emmanuel and Sam have delivered feasts for the eyes...
这就是我所说的展示品。
That is what I call a showpiece.
. .如果不总是为了味觉。
..if not always for the palate.
我不喜欢这样。
I'm not enjoying this.
但他们有一种不可否认的惊人本领。
But they have an undeniable knack for the spectacular.
椰子，冰镇果汁朗姆酒。
Coconut, pina colada.
珍爱:我爱它，爱它，爱它。
CHERISH: I love it, love it, love it.
我穿着我的幸运袜，我让他出去了
I'm wearing my lucky socks and I've made him go out
再买一些粉色和黄色的袜子。
and buy some pink and yellow socks as well.
他的袜子上有西瓜，太疯狂了。
He's got watermelons on his socks, which is just madness.
定制糕点业务甜艺术实验室已达到
Bespoke patisserie business Sweet Art Lab have reached
最后以一种创造性的方式登上顶峰。
the final on the crest of a creative way.
这个故事就像侏罗纪世界。
The story is like Jurassic World.
但Hideko和Theo无限的想象力…
But Hideko and Theo's limitless imagination...
哇!
Wow!
. .并非没有风险。
..is not without risk.
现在，等待结束了。
Now, the wait is over.
欢迎回来，决赛选手们。
Welcome back, finalists.
明天结束前，你们三支队伍中的一支将获得冠军
By the end of tomorrow, one of you three teams will be crowned
2018年专业烘焙大赛的获胜者。
winners of Bake Off: The Professionals 2018.
阻挡你的只有厄运的挑战。
All that stands in your way is the challenge of doom.
你很可能会陷入糕点炉的崩溃。
You may well go into patisserie meltdown.
法官们，前方是什么?
Judges, what lies ahead?
我们想让你办一场奢华的宴会
We want you to produce a lavish banquet
为了招待至少80位客人，
to serve at least 80 guests,
以大型雕塑为特色的
featuring a large sculptural showpiece
还有四种不同的甜点。
and four different types of desserts.
然后你将不得不在聚会上提供你的甜点
You will then have to serve your desserts at a party
由盖奇勋爵和夫人在大会堂主持。
hosted by Lord and Lady Gage in the Great Hall.
有趣的是，盖奇勋爵其实是个子爵，
Fun fact, Lord Gage is actually a Viscount,
你知道这意味着什么吗?
and you know what that means?
他实际上是巧克力饼干的后代。
He's literally descended from a chocolate biscuit.
珍惜。
Cherish.
它必须讲述一个故事，反映你的激情和个性。
It must tell a story and reflects your passion and personality.
各位队员，你们今天有四个半小时的时间
So, teams, you have four and a half hours today
明天还有四个半小时，现在开始计时。
and a further four and a half hours tomorrow and your time starts now.
好吧。我们开始吧。
All right. Let's start.
就是它了，总决赛。
This is it, the grand final.
他们必须倾尽全力迎接挑战。
They have to throw everything they've got at this challenge.
他们必须想出他们认为定义他们的东西
They've got to come up with what they feel defines them
作为糕点师。
as pastry chefs.
厨师们必须拿出一个展示品
The chefs have to come up with a showpiece
这就引出了甜点。
that leads down beautifully to the dessert.
它需要彼此结合。
It needs to marry with each other.
明天的奢华宴会并不是团队唯一的截止日期。
Tomorrow's lavish banquet isn't the team's only deadline.
蛋黄，奶油芝士，鲜奶油。
Yolk, cream cheese, whipping cream.
再过四个半小时，他们就要面对评委了。
In just four and a half hours, they'll be facing the judges.
今天结束的时候，他们要做出两道漂亮的甜点。
At the end of today, they have to produce two beautiful desserts.
我们希望看到各种各样的味道和质地
We want to see a range of flavour and textures
什么最能代表他们的风格。
and what represents their style the best.
在准备元素的同时提供精致的甜点
Delivering exquisite desserts while preparing elements
为了明天令人敬畏的中心装饰
for tomorrow's awe-inspiring centrepieces
将需要令人头晕目眩的团队合作和时间管理能力。
will require a head-spinning feat of teamwork and time management.
第一天非常关键。
The first day is so crucial.
他们需要提前准备，否则第二天就会遭殃。
They need to be ahead of time or on the second day they will suffer.
早上好,伙计。就是这里。就是这里。这是最后一轮。
Morning, guys. This is it. This is it. This is the final round.
这对你们来说意味着什么?
What does it mean to you guys?
这意味着很多，巨大的。
It means a lot, massive.
你能相信第一轮吗?
Can you believe the first round?
他假装哭
HE PRETENDS TO CRY
他们笑了别让我难受!
THEY LAUGH Don't make me feel bad!
你开始的时候有点小问题
You had that little hiccup at the beginning
然后，一致性。
and then since, consistency.
那么，你能描述一下你的宴会吗?
So, will you be able to describe your banquet?
它叫做“结束派对”。
It's called End Party.
我们要向万物致敬来庆祝
We're going to celebrate with homages to things
就像我们在比赛中做的那样。
that we've done in the contest.
在那里结束派对将看到一个单独的巨型巧克力
There End Party will see a separate giant chocolate
还有高耸入云的糖衣，包括闪光球，
and sky-scraping sugar centrepiece, including glitter ball,
气球，四叶草
balloons, a four-leaf clover
以及其他对之前作品的致敬。
and other nods to previous showpieces.
巴拉特希望派对开始
And Bharat's hoping to get the party started
再来一份加了柚子奶油的千层浓汤
with a reinvented millefeuille with yuzu cremeux
涂满凝胶的覆盆子放在金黄色的底座上。
and gel-filled raspberries sat on a blondie base.
金发女郎是什么?它就像布朗尼的表亲。
What's a blondie? It's like cousin to a brownie.
一个表弟。啊。是用白巧克力做的。
A cousin. Ah. It's done with white chocolate.
啊，一个金发女郎和一个布朗尼……
Ah, a blondie and a brownie are...
好吧，你总能学到新东西。
OK, you always learn something new.
当Darryl和Bharat庆祝他们的总决赛之旅时…
While Darryl and Bharat celebrate their journey to the grand final...
你称那个果冻有500磅吗?是的。
Did you weigh that jelly as 500, 500? Yeah.
. .希尔顿公园巷的Emmanuel and Sam，
..for Hilton's Park Lane Emmanuel and Sam,
这都是因为他们之间的关系。
it's all about the relationship that has got them here.
主题是协约。
The theme is Entente Cordiale.
协约是英国人和法国人之间的协议
Entente Cordiale was an agreement between English and French
说他们会互相支持。
to say they would support each other.
我们的想法是作为一个团队，英国人和法国人，
The idea is as a team together, English and French,
我们要一起努力。
we're going to work together.
很明显，这将是非常法式和英式的。
It's going to be obviously very French and English.
汤姆打算做些制糖的工作来提高自己。
Tom's going to excel himself with some sugar work.
我想做我做过的最棒的糖果秀。
I want to do the best sugar showcase I've ever done.
啊。这是一大步。
Ah. That's a big step.
这就是野心和伟大的宣言。
That's called ambition and a big statement.
山姆壮观的糖雕塑将以埃菲尔铁塔为特色
Sam's spectacular sugar sculpture will feature the Eiffel Tower
还有大本钟，两侧是巧克力色的女王卫队
and Big Ben, flanked by a chocolate Queen's Guard
还有一瓶香槟。
and a champagne bottle.
他们的第一份法英甜点是巧克力慕斯手指
Their first Franco-English dessert will see a chocolate mousse finger
装满了血橙果冻，
filled with blood orange jelly,
在山姆的前卫基础上保持平衡
balanced on Sam's avant-garde base.
这是布朗尼海绵蛋糕，在上面撒上少许蛋糕粉。
This is a brownie sponge, just spreading some feuilletine on top.
这一层很脆。
It's a nice crunchy layer.
这是你的基地。
You'll have this as your base.
当谈到Hideko和Theo的主题时，一切都不是看起来的那样。
When it comes to Hideko and Theo's theme, all is not what it seems.
所有的甜点和所有的展示都会看起来像什么
All the dessert and all the display is going to look like something
事实并非如此，或多或少。不是它的东西?
which it's not, more or less. Something which it's not?
是的，所以你不确定它是不是一种食物。
Yes, so you're not sure, like, if it's a food.
所以评委们会不会有吃桌子的危险
Oh, so is there a risk that the judges will start eating the table
因为他们觉得这可能是甜点?这是……这是令人担忧的。
cos they think it might be a dessert? That's... That's a worry.
所以，人们会问:“这是手提包还是甜点?”
So, people go, "Is it a handbag or is it a dessert?"
大约是对的?就是这样。是的,没错。就是这样。
Is about right? That's it. Yeah, exactly. That's it.
好的。是西奥还是甜点?
OK. Is it Theo or is it a dessert?
英子和西奥令人费解的表演
Hideko and Theo's mind-bending display
将以一个巨大的巧克力S为中心，代表甜蜜艺术实验室，
will centre around a giant chocolate S, for Sweet Art Lab,
一个糖心和一个华丽的可食用相框。
a sugar work heart and an ornate edible picture frame.
他们的第一道甜点是柑橘芝士蛋糕
And their first dessert is a citrus cheesecake
被设计成冰淇淋，
designed as an ice cream,
里面装满了藏红花慕斯和一个惊喜的水果中心。
filled with saffron mousse and a surprise fruit centre.
这是用来做柑橘果盘的。
It's going to be for the citrus compote.
粉红葡萄柚，血橙和柠檬。
Pink grapefruit, blood orange and a lemon.
但是这些队伍明天无法组装一个展示品……
But the teams won't be able to assemble a showpiece tomorrow...
我要尽我所能来演。
I'm going to cast everything I can.
. .除非他们有时间开始准备大糖
..unless they find time to begin preparing their large sugar
今天还有巧克力元素。
and chocolate elements today.
现在，这是你的黄金时刻。
So, now, this is essentially, like, your golden hour.
是的。
It is, yeah.
这将是我们的展示桌。哦，我明白了。
It's going to be our presentation table. Oh, I see.
在你说之前，它们不是芸豆。
Before you say it, they're not kidney beans.
它们不是芸豆。我还以为是果冻宝宝呢。
They're not kidney beans. I thought they were jelly babies.
我们对此有一些评论。利亚姆笑
We've had a few comments about that. LIAM LAUGHS
说到按时把事情做好，
When it comes to getting things set in time,
山姆给了自己更多的担心。
Sam has given himself even more to worry about.
这是我们要放进去的血橙果冻
This is a blood orange jelly that we're going to be putting inside
牛奶巧克力和血橙手指。
the milk chocolate and blood orange finger.
这是一种血橙泥，我把它浓缩了
It's a blood orange puree, I've reduced it down
所以它就固定了，保持它的形状，
so it's just set, like, just holds its shape,
这正是我想要的
which is what I wanted.
我想我今天可能需要幸运的袜子，这是肯定的。
I think I might need the luck of the socks today, that's for sure.
显然，我被迫去买了一双新袜子。
I was forced, obviously, to go and buy a new pair of socks.
三个孩子的父亲伊曼纽尔做出了更多的牺牲
Father of three Emmanuel has sacrificed more
比他平时穿的袜子更能进入决赛。
than his normal socks to get to the grand final.
我提到的竞争太多了?只会一点点。只是…
I mention the competition too much? Only a bit. Just...
只会一点点。只会一点点。
Only a bit. Only a bit.
不得不说，我的家人一直很支持我。
My family's been very supportive, I have to say.
我妻子取代了我和她在家庭中的角色，
My wife's taken over my role as much as hers in the family,
照顾我的女儿们。
looking after my daughters.
在整个比赛中我们花了很多时间在一起，
We've spent so much time together throughout this whole competition,
我觉得我们见面的次数比错过的次数还多。
I think we've seen more of each other than we have our misses.
我不只是把他当成老板，而是把他当成朋友，感觉很好。
It's been nice not see him as just the boss and to see him as a friend.
我们是朋友吗?我想是的。
Are we friends? Yeah, I suppose.
他们的友谊将在第二道甜点中得到巩固，
Their friendship will be cemented in their second dessert,
经典的热带风情
a tropical take on a classic,
山姆最喜欢的百香果巧克力会在哪里
where Sam's favourite passion fruit chocolate will coat
一个非常法国的金融海绵。
a very French financier sponge.
这是一个金融组合。
This is a financier mix.
杏仁，糖粉，面粉和焦黄油。
Almonds, icing sugar, flour and a burnt butter.
Beurre noisette的发音是这样的。
Beurre noisette is how it's pronounced.
我们已经习惯了在大质量中工作。
Working in big qualities is something we're used to.
但准备宴会并不是所有团队都熟悉的任务。
But preparing a banquet isn't it a familiar task for all the teams.
这绝对是一个巨大的挑战，所以一切都必须完美。
It's definitely a big challenge so everything has to be perfect.
西奥和英子更习惯于满足小的，
Theo and Hideko are more used to satisfying smaller,
的定制要求。
bespoke requests.
在这样一家小公司工作，西奥很难相信这一点
Working for such a small company has seen Theo struggle to believe that
他们可以与来自高端酒店和餐厅的团队竞争。
they could compete with teams from high-end hotels and restaurants.
对我来说，西奥一直都是赢家，但他自己并不知道。
Theo, for me, he always has been a winner but he doesn't know it.
他每周都给我打电话，告诉我，
Every week, he was calling me and telling me,
“我不确定，我不确定。”
"I'm not sure, I'm not sure."
最后，已经是决赛了，我真的很自豪。
And finally, it's already the final, so I'm really proud.
我真的为他感到骄傲。
I'm really proud of him.
西奥的未婚夫启发了他们的第二道甜点，
And Theo's fiance has inspired their second dessert,
改造gianduja慕斯，
transforming gianduja mousse,
芒果和佛手柑果汁
mango and bergamot compote
还有巧克力和榛子黑貂
and chocolate and hazelnut sable
戴在无名指上。
into a ring finger.
对于他的第二道甜点，Darryl冒着巨大的风险。
For his second dessert, Darryl is taking a huge risk.
我不能吃任何坚果，
I'm not allowed to eat any nuts,
所以我要做一个可爱的榛子焦糖。
so I'm going to make a lovely hazelnut caramel.
只是个寻求危险的人。
Just a danger seeker.
生活在边缘。
Life on the edge.
在达里尔成为厨师之前，危险从未远离。
Before Darryl became a chef, danger was never far away.
这是一个相当困难的青年。
It was quite a difficult youth.
直到11岁我妈妈去世的时候我都还好，不幸的是，
I was OK up to about 11 when my mum passed away and, unfortunately,
我16岁离开家，从那以后就开始走下坡路了。
I left home at 16 and it kind of went downhill from there.
和警察纠缠不清，极度黑暗，
In and out of trouble with the police, extremely dark time,
直到我遇到了我的妻子汉娜，后来成为厨师。
until I met my wife Hannah and then cheffing.
他不停地工作，然后用自己的方式冷静下来
He worked and worked and worked, then calmed down with his ways
搬到这里来感觉很好
and it was nice to move down here
远离那些废话。
and get away from all the nonsense.
我为他感到骄傲，队友们都认为他很棒。
Really proud of him and the boys think he's fantastic.
Darryl的旅程在他的第二道甜点中得到了庆祝，
Darryl's journey is celebrated in his second dessert,
用…制成的旅行棒
a travel bar made with
巧克力甘纳许慕斯
chocolate ganache mousseline
淡盐榛子焦糖让我们
and a lightly salted hazelnut caramel that takes us
回到他进入总决赛之旅的起点。
right back to the start of his trip to the grand final.
这是我为了参加比赛所做的努力。
It's the bar that I did to get into this competition.
我把它从伯明翰带到伦敦，没有坏掉
I took it from Birmingham to London without them breaking
他们旅行得很好。
and they travelled really well.
巴拉特，你想快点尝一下吗?
Bharat, do you want to just taste this quick?
是的。快，快，快。
Yeah. Quick, quick, quick.
Salt-wise。
Salt-wise.
是的，很好。好吗?是的。
Yeah, it's good. Good? Yeah.
大厨们，你们还有一个小时。
Chefs, you have one hour left.
那是一个小时。他说了什么?一个小时，好吗?是的。
That's one hour. What did he say? One hour, OK? Yep.
一小时，Hideko。谢谢你！
One hour, Hideko. Thank you.
有多少?一个小时。有我们吗?哔哔声。
How many? An hour. Have we? BLEEP.
我可能需要帮手来做这些。确定。
I might need a hand just to build these. Sure.
需要凝固的甜点…
Desserts that need to set...
爆炸中有果冻吗?是的。
Jelly in the blast? Yeah.
. .必须尽快放到冰箱里。
..have to be in the freezer as soon as possible.
这是做手指用的，我把慕斯放进模具里。
This is for the finger, I'm piping the mousse into the mould.
现在的任何拖延都将意味着更少的时间
Any delay now will mean less time to glaze
在第一次评判前添加细节。
and add detail before the first judging.
这些是旅行酒吧。
These are the travel bars.
我需要把它们封起来，然后放进冰箱。
I need to seal these off and then put them in the freezer.
时间不等人。
Time waits for no man.
这里越来越热了。＃
# It's getting hot in here. #
但是西奥已经落后了。
But Theo is already falling behind.
我在做。好的。
I'm making them. OK.
还有很多事要做。
Still quite a lot of to do.
他的手指可能在冰箱里…
His fingers might be in the freezer...
. .但他甚至还没有开始他的冰淇淋幻想。
..but he's yet to even start his ice cream illusions.
下一个是芝士蛋糕。好的。
The cheesecake next, please. OK.
是的。
Yeah.
半小时，大厨们。你还有半个小时。
Half an hour, chefs. You've got half an hour left.
这是白巧克力加覆盆子的金发蛋糕。
This is a white chocolate and raspberry blondie.
最重要的是准确性，否则图层看起来就不对了。
It's all about accuracy, otherwise the layers won't look right.
它们是固定的，这是主要的。
They're set, that's the main thing.
只要切掉其中一个末端，因为它们真的很大。
Just cutting one of the ends off because they're really big.
每种甜点只有一个样品会被仔细审查
Just a single example of each dessert will be scrutinised
评委们…
by the judges...
这是焦糖巧克力和泡米。
It's a caramel chocolate with puffed rice.
它只是提供了另一种质感。
It just gives another texture.
. .这意味着细节比以往任何时候都重要。
..meaning detail is more important than ever.
我在给手指上光泽釉。
I'm doing the shiny glaze for the finger.
我要在中间放一些柚子豆腐
I'm going to put some of the yuzu curd just between there
每一层都得到了一些东西。继续前进。
so every sort of layer's getting something. Pushing on now.
我看到一个甜点了，另一个怎么样?
I can see one dessert there, how's the other one going?
它会。
It's going.
山姆!
Sam!
你不会从萨姆那里得到什么。它在走，但是在走……
You're not going to get a lot from Sam. It's going, but going...
. .正确?呃…
..correctly? Er...
10分钟后我们就知道了。
We'll see in about 10 minutes' time.
我要给酒吧装饰一下，
Going to do a little decoration for the bar,
刷上一些金色的闪光。
brush some gold shimmer on.
24-BHARAT黄金。
24-BHARAT gold.
大厨们，你们还有15分钟。
Chefs, you have 15 minutes left.
对，把这个加到演员名单上。
Right, add that to the cast.
所以我们明天还要做釉料。
So, we've still got glaze to make for tomorrow.
甜点就在上面。
The desserts are going to be up there.
我至少在努力完成一点装饰工作。
I'm trying to at least push to get a little bit of decoration done.
非常激烈。四个半小时过得太快了。
Very intense. Four and a half hours have just gone so fast.
正在煮的糖对我明天的生活有很大的影响，
The sugar being cooked makes a world of difference for me tomorrow,
否则我就会战斗一整天了。
otherwise I would've been fighting the whole day.
我希望我今天能多做些事情。
I wish I have more done today.
你觉得你能及时完成吗?我必须这么做。
You think you can get that done in time? I have to.
我没有时间。
I don't have time.
大厨们，你们有一分钟时间。
Chefs, you have one minute.
我的天啊。
My goodness.
盘子里。你抓住他们了。
Plate. You got 'em.
更多?
More?
厨师们，请离开你们的工作台。
Chefs, please step away from your workbenches.
你今天的时间到了。
Your time today is up.
这很艰难。
That was tough.
所以你明天要上，一定要上。
So you're going to be on it tomorrow, have to be on it.
明天会很艰难。是吗?
Tomorrow will be tough. Yeah?
每队四道甜点的前两道将进入明天的决赛
The first two of each team's four desserts for tomorrow's final
宴会现在由珍爱和伯努瓦来评判。
banquet will now be judged by Cherish and Benoit.
西奥和英子，请把你们的甜点端上来。
Theo and Hideko, please bring your desserts to the table.
老实说，它看起来就像一个小花盆，
It looks like a little flowerpot, to be honest with you,
而不是冰淇淋蛋筒，但我明白你的意思。
as opposed to an ice cream cone, but I see the idea.
圆锥体可以吃吗?
Is the cone edible?
它可以食用，但不是甜点的一部分。
It's edible but it's not part of the dessert.
外面是柑橘芝士蛋糕
Citrus cheesecake outside
还有藏红花慕斯和柑橘果盘。
and saffron mousse and a citrus compote.
我很喜欢慕斯，我觉得它很清淡。
I really like the mousse, I think, it's really light.
然而，我渴望更有质感的来刺激我的味觉。
However, I was craving for more textured to excite my palate.
因为这已经不是我想的那样了，
Because this is no longer what I thought it was,
然后这个就变软了。
then this becomes soft.
藏红花会污染周围的一切。
And the saffron contaminates everything around.
所有的味道都是一样的。
The whole lot tastes of one thing.
再提醒我一次，这应该是个手指吗?
And remind me again, this is supposed to be a finger?
做得很整齐。釉，做得很好。
It's very neatly done. The glaze, it was nicely finished.
这是巧克力和榛子，佛手柑和芒果的混合果汁
So this is a chocolate and hazelnut sable, bergamot and mango compote
然后是牛奶巧克力慕斯，上面有牛奶巧克力釉。
and then a milk chocolate mousse with a milk chocolate glaze.
哔哔声。对不起!
BLEEP great. Sorry!
我真的，真的，真的，真的，真的，真的，真的很喜欢。
I really, really, really, really, really, really, really love this.
芒果和佛手柑的味道，我非常喜欢。
Mango and bergamot, the flavour, I really loved.
吃的时候不会太甜。
When you eat it, it's not over-sweet.
就口感而言，这比你的芝士蛋糕更让我兴奋。
In terms of texture, this excites me more than your cheesecake.
这是一块不错的糕点。
It's a nice piece of pastry.
谢谢你！非常感谢。
Thank you. Thank you very much.
干得好，伙计们!
Well done, guys!
这是榛子味的高音棒。看起来很开胃。
It's a hazelnut treble bar. It looks very appetising.
它是光滑的。我喜欢你加了
It's sleek. I like the fact that you've added
部分喷涂的顶部
a partly sprayed top
底部是一层美味的釉。
and a gourmand glaze at the bottom.
这是一种淡巧克力，
It's a light chocolate panache,
榛子焦糖加一点盐，
a hazelnut caramel with a touch of salt,
配上焦糖泡米。
with caramelised puff rice.
你用的是我不喜欢的味道。
You are working here with flavour I don't like.
但我爱。
But I love.
:哦!
ALL: Oh!
一小撮盐可以提升焦糖的味道。
That little pinch of salt is lifting the caramel flavour.
这是哇。
This is wow.
我真的很喜欢它，因为它有泡米。
I really like it because of the puffed rice.
我吃的时候有一种酥脆的感觉。
There is a crispy sensation that I'm eating.
巧克力的咸味能很好地平衡吗
Can taste the saltiness of the chocolate balanced very well
有慕斯和脆脆的口感。
with the mousse and the crunch.
好了，我们找到下一个了。
Okay, we've got the next one.
从视觉上看，它是一块切好的金发女郎。
Visually, it's a cut piece of blondie.
像这样切一些覆盆子。
Just sliced like this, some raspberries.
他叹了口气
HE SIGHS
这已经做过太多次了，这是最后一次，伙计们。
It's been done too many times - this is the final, guys.
这是一种千面杂烩。
It's a take on a mille-feuille.
是白巧克力加覆盆子的金发蛋糕，
It's a white chocolate and raspberry blondie,
配覆盆子，白巧克力和柚子奶油。
with raspberries and white chocolate and yuzu cremeux.
说到味道，那一点柚子奶油，很酸。
In terms of flavour profile, that little yuzu cream, very acidic.
唯一漂亮的地方就是下面那个金发美女。
The only nice part here is your blondie at the bottom.
口感很好，很甜，很好吃。
It was beautiful texture, sweet and this was nice.
我对你的期望远不止这些。
I expect more than what you have displayed for us.
然而，这一块是我们真正喜欢吃的。
However, this one piece that we really enjoy eating.
我很喜欢。
I loved it.
做得很好。谢谢你！谢谢你！
Well done. Thank you. Thank you.
乍一看，它看起来不错。
From the first glance, it looks alright.
但当我仔细观察时，我希望它更干净。
But when I look closer, I expect it to be cleaner.
当我看到你把另一块切下来的时候，
And then when I saw you chop off the other piece over here,
这让我觉得它是不完整的。
it just let me feel that it was incomplete.
这是最后的润色，很匆忙。
It's the finishing touches, it's been rushed.
我们有佛罗伦萨底座，牛奶巧克力慕斯
We have a Florentine base, a milk chocolate mousse
中间是血橙果冻。
with a blood orange jelly in the middle.
底部的纹理很漂亮。脆脆的口感很美。
Lovely textures at the bottom. The crunchiness there is beautiful.
我不喜欢的部分是血橙。
The part I don't love is the blood orange.
它就是那种液体吗?我们预计它会有点流动，当……
Is it meant to be that liquid? We expected it to kind of be runny when...
但它没有跑，它飞走了。
Ah, but it's not running, it's flown away.
好的，还有一种甜点。
Okay, there is another dessert.
我要说的是，这是一种有点仓促的糕点。
Again, I would say this is a pastry which is a little bit rushed.
这是一个非常简单的设计，所以它需要非常圆滑
It's a very simple design, so for that it needs to be very sleek
这里的精确度对我来说还不够。
and the precision here is not quite there yet for me.
这位杏仁金融家被浸在了百香巧克力中。
The almond financier has been dipped in passion chocolate.
在里面，你有一个激情和芒果拼盘，然后在上面
Inside, you've got a passion and mango compote, and then on top
是马斯卡彭奶酪，用橘子和香草果冻调味。
is the mascarpone cream piped in a Mandarin and vanilla jelly.
当我单独吃它的时候，我喜欢它。
When I eat it as individual components, I like it.
但是当我把它作为一个整体吃的时候，它很干。
But when I eat it as a whole, it's quite dry.
你有七个不同的元素。我想你喝得太多了。
You've got seven different elements. I think you've got too many.
这是百香果的味道，很有味道。
I've got a passion fruit, dominant flavour.
但这很无趣。谢谢你们的努力，团队。
But it's uninteresting. Thanks for your effort, team.
谢谢你！谢谢你！明天又是新的一天。
Thank you. Thank you. Tomorrow is another day.
是啊!在那之后。
Yeah! After that.
我们度过了一个艰难的早晨。
We had a tough morning.
我不知道是缺乏计划还是希望做得太多。
I don't know if it's lack of planning or hoping to do too much.
今天的评论不错，感觉很好。
Good comment today, feel really good.
4.5小时刚刚过去!
4.5 hours just gone!
所有的事情都要在明天完成，所有的事情。
Still everything has to be done tomorrow, everything.
奖杯现在已经触手可及了
The trophy is in reach of our hands now
但我们明天真的很忙。
but we've really got a push tomorrow.
今天是比赛的最后一天。
It's the last day of the competition.
几个小时后，其中一支队伍将加冕
In just a few hours, one of these teams will be crowned
《烘焙大赛:2018》的优胜者。
the winners of Bake Off: The Professionals 2018.
在这个时刻，说两支球队是平衡的，公平吗?
Is it fair to say that the teams are evenly balanced at this moment in time?
我不得不说，它非常非常接近。
I have to say that it is very, very close.
Darryl和Bharat，他们的高音棒很好吃。
Darryl and Bharat, their treble bar was delicious.
毫无疑问，这是目前为止最好的甜点。
Without a shadow of a doubt, the best dessert so far.
甜蜜艺术实验室的情侣们。
The sweethearts of Sweet Art Lab.
在半决赛中看到英子能为她做些什么之后
After seeing in the semi-final what Hideko can do for her
活电镀，我现在期待更多。
live plating, I am expecting even more now.
山姆和伊曼纽尔，他没有达到他想达到的目标。
Sam and Emmanuel, he did not achieve as much as he wanted to.
好像少了点什么。
There was something missing.
但他们总是会反弹，这些家伙，所以一切都是为了比赛。
But they always bounce back, those guys, so everything is to play for.
我想知道谁会赢得现金奖。
I wonder who's going to win that cash prize.
他们会很享受花这些钱。兄弟，没有现金奖励。
They can really enjoy spending that money. Bruv, there's no cash prize.
没有钱?!不。
There's no money?! No.
他们为什么要这么做?
Why are they doing it?
白痴。
Idiots.
我在开玩笑。
I'm joking.
这些队伍现在只有4.5小时的时间来完成任务
The teams now have just 4.5 hours to complete
他们的前两款甜点的批次在昨天进行了评判，
the batches of their first two desserts judged yesterday,
制作两款新甜点。
and create batches of two new desserts.
还要建造他们的大型宴席
Plus construct their giant showpiece banquets
评委们和盖奇勋爵夫妇的派对
for the judges and Lord and Lady Gage's party.
紧张,紧张。
Tense, nervous.
希望它能落实到位。或者不会。
Hopefully it will fall into place. Or it won't.
今天是重要的一天。最后的机会……时间太少了。是啊!
It's a massive day. Last chance to... So little time. Yeah!
这是期末考试，一定很紧张!
It's the final - it has to be stressful!
名胜世界，今天是最后一天!
Resorts World, it's the last day!
你好吗?
How are you doing?
我觉得我们有点落后了。
I think we're a little bit behind.
就因为我昨天没去铸这些。对着它。
Simply because I didn't get these casted yesterday. Up against it.
请给我们介绍一下你们的甜点好吗?
Could you please take us through your dessert?
是的，是巧克力小蛋糕。
Yes, it will be a chocolate petit gateau.
在巧克力黑貂饼干上，
On top of chocolate sable biscuit,
Darryl会放一个带凹槽的巧克力慕斯
Darryl will place a fluted dome of chocolate mousse
用一个橙色的维多利亚海绵蛋糕，里面装满了一种配料
with an orange Victoria sponge filled with an ingredient
这是他们在比赛中取胜的关键。
that has been key to their journey through the competition.
加一点香精和一些橘子胶。
A bit of added flavour and some mandarin gel.
你喜欢你的普通话，是吗?是的。
You like your mandarin, don't you? Yeah.
你以前用过，对吧?我们所做的。
You've used that before, have you? We did.
珍惜，普通话对普通话来说是什么?
Cherish, what is Mandarin for mandarin?
Hwa-yu。Hwhy-you吗?
Hwa-yu. Hwhy-you?
华……华。
Hwa... Hwa.
余。余。
Yu. Yu.
那是它!Hwa-yu。
Tha's it! Hwa-yu.
伯努瓦:我不知道你在说什么。
BENOIT: I've got no clue what your talking about.
普通话用法语怎么说?普通话。看,无聊。
What is Mandarin in French? Mandarin. See, boring.
简单。
Straightforward.
在令人失望的第一天之后……
After a disappointing first day...
我在准备蛋白派。
I'm getting the meringues ready.
. .伊曼纽尔和萨姆现在都寄希望于获胜
..Emmanuel and Sam are now pinning their hopes of winning
他们最喜欢的口味的比赛。
the competition on some of their favourite flavours.
我想我已经说得很清楚了，我是你的忠实粉丝
I think I've made it quite clear that I'm a great fan
开心果和覆盆子。
of pistachio and raspberry.
伊曼纽尔的球体将看到开心果奶油和
Emmanuel's spheres will see pistachio buttercream combined with
脆脆的柑橘蛋白酥皮和覆盆子和卡拉曼斯焗。
crisp citrus meringue and a raspberry and calamansi confit.
都涂上了一层红色的饼干粉。
All coated in a red layer of powdered biscuit.
覆盆子油酥饼放在中间。
Raspberry confit is going in the middle.
蛋白派看起来不错。
Meringues looking good.
嗯…
Uh...
我们将会看到。再多一点。
We'll see. A bit more.
能在一小时或一个半小时内告诉你。
Capable of telling you in about an hour, 1.5 hours.
而希尔顿公园巷和名胜世界
While Hilton Park Lane and Resorts World
赶紧完成圆顶甜点…
rush to complete dome desserts...
很好，对吧?
It's good, yah?
. .在Sweet艺术实验室，他们正在花时间改造
..Over at Sweet Art Lab, they are spending time transforming
他们把甜点变成了一道主菜。
their dome dessert into a main course.
Hideko的诡计继续在汉堡面包形状上
Hideko's trickery continues with burger bun-shaped
圆形的西番莲巧克力慕斯，里面充满了夏威夷果
domes of passionfruit chocolate mousse filled with macadamia
坚果汉堡布朗尼，上面撒上白巧克力甘纳许奶酪
nut burger brownies, topped with white chocolate ganache cheese
还有一份苹果草莓沙拉。
and an apple and strawberry salad.
那么，我们是应该这样吃呢，还是应该…
So, are we supposed to eat like that, or are we supposed to...
嗯…这取决于你。在这里，你从来没有刀叉，你会…
Um... It's up to you. Over here, you never have a knife and fork, you go...
吃面包的意义就在于把它撑起来，不是吗?
That's the whole point of having the buns is to hold it up, no?
是的，如果你愿意的话!
Yes, if you want to!
显然洛德和盖奇夫人喜欢汉堡。嗯,是的。和烤肉串。
Apparently Lord and Lady Gage love burgers. Uh, yeah. And kebabs.
是的,我……他们喜欢去烤肉店。
Yeah, I... They love going to kebabs shops.
以及完成大量的生产
As well as finishing huge batches
在他们宴会上的四种甜点中…
of all four of their banquets' desserts...
我想把他们赶走
I want to get them out of the way
然后我可以花尽可能多的时间在糖的工作。
and then I can spend as much time as possible on the sugar work.
在他们之间，这些团队现在有超过200个个人展示作品
Between them, the teams now have over 200 individual showpiece
组件完成。
components to complete.
所以要选角和拉绳。
So there's casting and all the pulling to be done.
吹，然后是巧克力。
Blowing and then there's chocolate work.
你有香槟酒瓶，你有……哦，那是狮子吗?
So you've got the champagne bottle, you've got... Oh, is that a lion?
那是一头狮子。做得很好。是的,是的。是啊，两选一。
That is a lion. Well done. Yeah, yeah. Yeah, that's two out of two.
第三个是什么?然后你就会，
What's the third one? And then you've got, like,
那些站在女王房子外面包厢里的人。
the people that stand in the boxes outside the Queen's house.
对，就是这个。它们叫什么?警卫。
Yeah, that's the one. What are they called? Guards.
我以为他们的名字很时髦呢。
I thought they had a posher name.
他们很可能会，我不确定。
They might well do, I'm not sure.
我对糖不是很有信心，所以…
I'm not really confident with sugar, so...
西奥的第二次尝试将会是一个浪漫的中心
Theo's second attempt at a romantic centrepiece will feature
心是用糖做的。
hearts made from poured sugar.
现在开始铸造。
Casting it now.
还有一颗巨大的钻石镶嵌在金铸糖上。
And the giant diamond set in a display of gold cast sugar.
我试着把管子做成一个心形。
I tried to make a heart-shape out of the pipe.
巴拉特在做巧克力圈。
Bharat is doing the chocolate ring.
陈列品将坐在糖陈列品的后面，
The showpiece will be sitting behind the sugar showpiece,
有球，有花。定型大约需要45分钟到1个小时。
with balls, flowers. It will take about 45 minutes to an hour to set.
大厨们，你们有一个小时的时间。你现在还剩下3.5小时。
Chefs, you've had an hour. You now have 3.5 hours left.
已经过去一个小时了。我知道。哔哔声。
That's an hour's gone already. I know. BLEEP.
这件事昨天就该做了。
This should have been done yesterday.
如果提供80种甜点和所有元素的壮观
If delivering 80 desserts and all the elements for a spectacular
《Showpiece》要求不够高……
showpiece wasn't demanding enough...
. .Hideko试图同时做到这两点。
..Hideko is attempting to do both at the same time.
她的最后一道甜点将伪装成她的展示品的一部分。
Her final dessert will be disguised as part of her showpiece.
她华丽的牛奶巧克力相框里会有巧克力慕斯，
Her ornate milk chocolate picture frame will contain chocolate mousse,
榛子黑貂饼干，跳跳糖和百香果
hazelnut sable biscuit, popping candy and a passionfruit
还有柚子盐焦糖。
and yuzu salted caramel.
在争夺冠军的最后一搏中，
In the final push for the title,
英子不是唯一一个愿意欺骗的人。
Hideko isn't the only one willing to deceive.
我把果冻和英吉利酱一起放进蛋糕里。
I've got the jelly with the anglaise to go inside the cake.
和主菜一模一样。
Exactly like an entremet.
伊曼纽尔做的层层野草莓果冻和英式奶油
Emmanuel's layers of wild strawberry jelly and creme anglaise will be
周围是法式蓝莓草莓青柠慕斯，
surrounded by a French Mara des Bois strawberry and lime mousse,
镶嵌成一个垫子的形状，上面放着皇冠上的珠宝，
set in the shape of a cushion to bear the crown jewels,
最后一道主菜陈列室甜点
for a final entremet showroom dessert
这将他们的主题结合在一起。
that brings their showpiece theme together.
它离心脏很近。我们有一个草莓奶油蛋糕，
It's quite close to heart. We have a strawberries and cream cake,
我年轻时在温布尔登当过球童。
and I was a ballboy at Wimbledon when I was younger.
还有，皇家坐垫，我爸爸在白金汉宫工作，
Also, the royal cushion, my dad works in Buckingham Palace,
这是另一个联系。
so another connection there.
而希尔顿公园巷和
While the banquets and themes for both Hilton Park Lane and
Sweet Art Lab开始联合起来，为Darryl和Bharat…
Sweet Art Lab are starting to come together, for Darryl and Bharat...
它是什么样的?还是有点软。
What's it like? Still a bit soft.
. .到达终点的旅程似乎越来越长了。
..The journey to their end party seems to be getting longer.
我不想搬家，那是因为……
I don't want to move that's because...
巴拉特的巧克力戒指还没有凝固，
Bharat's chocolate ring still hasn't set,
完成最后一道甜点也是他的工作。
and it is also his job to complete their final dessert.
我要把我的柠檬酥饼压平。
So I'm just stamping out my lemon shortbread.
这是芒果巴瓦鲁的底料。
Which is going to be the base for the mango bavarois.
巴拉特的每一块柠檬酥饼都要放在上面
On each of Bharat's lemon shortbreads will sit
白巧克力上釉的芒果巴瓦鲁球，
white chocolate glazed spheres of mango bavarois,
里面有西番莲果冻
filled with a passionfruit jelly
还有芒果和西番莲果盘。
and a mango and passionfruit compote.
我想这个会有更多的纹理
I think this will have a few more textures
以及他们可能喜欢的味道。
and flavours that they might enjoy.
球，碗，球。
It's balls, bowls, balls.
大厨们，你们的最终挑战已经进行了一半!
Chefs, you are halfway through your final challenge!
哎呦。对不起,男人。
Whoops. Sorry, man.
有很多很多事情要做。没时间了。这里有很多事情要做。
A lot, a lot to do. Running out of time. Plenty, plenty to do here.
我得停止巧克力装饰了
I'm going to have to stop chocolate decoration to get on with
蛋糕马上就做好了。
cake finishing in a minute.
我只是在选大本钟和埃菲尔铁塔
I'm just casting the Big Ben and the Eiffel Tower
这样他们就能及时冷却下来，以便使用。
so they can get cooling down in time to be able to use.
感觉名单越来越长了。
Feels like the list is getting longer.
我在做一些气球，一些丝带。
I'm doing some balloons, some ribbons.
希望是一只戴着帽子飞来的天鹅
Hopefully a swan that will come round with a hat
还有一点三叶草。
and a little shamrock.
Darryl给自己设定了一个挑战，使用五种不同的
Darryl set himself the challenge of using five different
不同种类的糖来制造30多种不同的元素。
types of sugar to create over 30 separate elements.
还是没定。是吗?还是没定。
Still not set. Eh? Still not set.
但如此大量的熔融物放出的热量
But the heat given off by such a large quantity of molten
糖可能对巴拉特的巧克力没有帮助。
sugar may not be helping Bharat's chocolate.
你看，它只是在加热房间。这是我们不想要的。
It's just heating up the room, you see. Which we don't want.
可能把我们推迟了半小时。
Pushed us back about half an hour, probably.
我是说，一分钟是很长的时间。
I mean, an minute's a long time.
他们并不是唯一一支开始失去宝贵时间的球队。
And they're not the only team beginning to lose precious minutes.
西奥的浪漫中心装饰的组成部分有
The components for Theo's romantic centrepiece have
冷却时开裂。
cracked during cooling.
我真的不喜欢吃糖。
Sugar is really not my thing.
在这次比赛中做了一次，两次。
Done once, twice in this competition.
现在没有时间重新塑造他们了。
And now there is no time to recast them.
应该做心脏手术但我不确定我们现在是否要做心脏手术。
Supposed to do a heart but I'm not sure we're going to do a heart now.
灾难。
Disaster.
还剩90分钟，我们将赢得职业烘焙大赛。
90 minutes left to win Bake Off - The Professionals.
你还好吗?是的。看起来不应该是这样的。
You OK? Yeah. Doesn't look how it should be.
当西奥被迫简化他的浪漫糖果展示时……
While Theo has been forced to simplify his romantic sugar showpiece...
是的，我很生气。
I'm annoyed, yes.
. .对山姆来说，简单不是他的菜单。
..for Sam, simplicity is not on the menu.
我正在尝试做我做过的最复杂的滴注。
I'm attempting to do one the most complicated drips I've ever done.
在比赛中第一次，
For the first time in the competition,
他正试图吹细糖管并把它们折起来
he is attempting to blow thin sugar tubes and fold them
一起形成三维的缎带。
together to form three-dimensional ribbons.
我觉得我们每一轮都要加倍努力。
I think we're trying to go the extra mile with every round.
到现在为止，我们已经走了好几英里了。
By now, we've done quite a few miles.
但是Darryl和Bharat的野心……好带。
But Darryl and Bharat's ambitions... Good ribbon.
. .将他们有史以来最大的制糖量结合起来哦,是的!
..to combine their largest-ever volume of sugar work... Oh, yes!
. .带着一个巨大的巧克力陈列品……你有粉丝吗?
..with a huge chocolate showpiece... Do you have any fans?
. .似乎没有任何进展
..doesn't appear to be getting any closer
他们的时间不多了。
and they're running out of time.
球队的朋友和家人已经开始陆续抵达洛德
The team's friends and families have began arriving at Lord
还有盖奇夫人的派对，还有一些熟悉的面孔。
and Lady Gage's party, along with a few familiar faces.
回来的感觉真好。
It feels really great to be back.
是啊，感觉很好
Yeah, it feels really good,
因为你没有压力什么的。
cos you're not under pressure or nothing.
我现在觉得有点暴露了
I feel a little exposed now,
人们可以看到我的时尚品味有多差!
and people can see how bad my fashion sense is!
他们笑了
THEY LAUGH
对山姆来说，这太艰难了。他从不在家。
For Sam, it's been so hard for him. He's never at home.
他总是在练习。
He's always practising.
我们希望能再多见到他一点，
We'd love to see him a bit more than we have done,
但我们为他感到无比骄傲。
but we're amazingly proud of him.
西奥非常喜欢。
Theo is so into it.
就像，他奉献了，他完全奉献了自己。
Like, he gave, he gave himself, like, totally.
他只是在练习。
He's just practising and everything.
当他回到家，他是如此的累。他太累了。
When he comes home, he's so tired. He's so, so tired.
他只想睡觉。
He just wants to go to sleep.
是的，他说，“我想睡觉。我想睡觉!
Yes, he says, "I want to go to sleep. I want to sleep!
我觉得我爸很有可能赢。
I think my dad's got a good chance of winning.
厨师们，你们还有一个小时来完成你们的宴会。
Chefs, you have one hour left to complete your banquets.
你还好吗，劳伦?还有几件事要做。
Do you feel all right, Lauren? Er, still a few things to do.
不过你的时间不多了。你的……怎么样?
Your time's ticking, though. What about your...?
好的，我现在就查一下。
Yeah, I'll check it now.
在这最后的时刻，
In this final hour,
这些团队必须建造他们设计过的最大的展示品…
the teams must construct the largest showpieces they've ever designed...
彩带做好了。管子完成了。
The ribbons are done. The tubes are done.
一切都是模式化的。气球是下一个。
Everything's been moulded. The balloons is the next one.
. .为240个甜点做最后的修饰。
..and put the finishing touches to 240 deserts.
这就够了。
This is enough.
这是芒果巴瓦罗。
This is the mango bavarois.
Hideko吗?是吗?我要的洋葱是你做的吗?对不起,没有。
Hideko? Yes? Did you make the onions that I asked for? Sorry, no.
他叹了口气
HE SIGHS
我只是想给它们多一点颜色。
I just wanted to give them a bit more colour.
我去过英国。现在我想做一个法国气球。
I've done England. Now I want to do a France balloon.
希望这能让我们从伯努瓦那里得到加分。
Hopefully, this will get us some bonus points from Benoit.
我现在还得把我的花组装在这里。
I've got to still assemble my flowers on here now.
我在做一只小鸟。
I'm making a wee bird.
那是埃菲尔铁塔。
That's the Eiffel Tower.
这是大本钟。
This is the Big Ben.
这是我最不喜欢的部分。公平地说，这就像兽医一样。
This is the bit I dislike most. It is like being a vet, to be fair.
如果我造得太晚，它就不会凝固。
If I build too late, it's not going to set.
如果我一块一块慢慢地组装，就像我做花一样，
If I build piece by piece slowly, as I'm making the flowers,
因为匆忙建造总是有风险的。
cos rushing a build is always a risk.
一旦我完成了所有这些，我就可以继续建造了。
Once I've pulled all of these, I can get on with building.
不过我需要两个。
I need two of these, though.
我正忙着把香槟酒灌完。
I'm working on the finish of the champagne bottle.
好吧，希望我们不用喝这个，
Well, hopefully, we won't be drinking from this one,
但我们会再喝一杯的!
but we'll be drinking another one!
不管发生什么，我都要喝酒!我们还剩多久?
Whatever happens, I'll be drinking! How long have we got left?
大厨们，最后的挑战只剩下半个小时了!
Chefs, that's just half an hour left on your final challenge!
30分钟。我们现在没法用这个了。
30 minutes. No way we can use this now.
没有时间。
No time.
巴拉特已经没有时间完成他的巧克力中心了。
Bharat has run out of time to complete his chocolate centrepiece.
他们最后一次宴会的成功与否取决于达里尔的制糖工作。
The success of their final banquet now rests on Darryl's sugar work.
最近怎么样?
How's it going?
你必须在不破坏石膏本身的情况下这样做，
You have to do this without breaking the actual cast itself,
因为那将是一场灾难。
cos that would be a calamity.
一场灾难!我喜欢这个词。
A calamity! I like that word.
糖，代表冰块。
The sugar, representing the ice cubes.
它必须保持平衡。
It's got to balance.
15分钟。啊!
15 minutes. Ah!
口干!
Dry mouth!
法国完蛋了。
Here goes France.
我无能为力，只能再试一次。
Nothing I can do about it, except try and do another one.
如果这个气球保持原样，它至少比第一个要好。
If this balloon stays like it is, it was better than the first one, anyway.
这让我很紧张。整件事让我很紧张。
It's making me nervous. The whole thing's make me nervous.
这是移动。
That's moving.
It's moving.
你能不能别那么用力敲桌子?
BANGING Can you please not bang that table so hard?
毫米吗?你能不能别再敲桌子了?
Mm? Can you stop banging the table?
对不起。留下来。
Sorry. Stay.
爆炸
BANG
发出哔哔声
BLEEP
他叹了口气
HE SIGHS
继续，继续。
Carry on, carry on.
模糊
INDISTINCT
就是这样。
That's that.
哦,不!达瑞尔和巴拉特的好戏刚刚落下。
Oh, no! Darryl and Bharat's showpiece has just dropped.
不管你有多想赢，这都很残酷。
However much you want to win this, it's gutting.
达雷尔，发生什么事了?
Darrell, what just happened?
只是还没来得及定型。
It's just not had the time to set.
但你知道吗?你们还在继续做这些事，
But do you know what, though? You guys are still continuing with these lot,
我觉得这是最主要的。继续。
and I feel like that's the main thing. Keep going.
别担心。是的。
Don't worry about it. Yep.
发出哔哔声
BLEEP
大厨们，你们还有五分钟。
Chefs, you have five minutes left now.
这个和这个，它们就像钻石。
This and this, they're like diamonds.
我想在上面放一些叶子。
I want to get some leaves on there.
这个展示品真的需要一点绿色。
The showpiece really needs a little bit of green.
脚下真的很脆。这不是很好的糖。
It's really crunchy underfoot. It's not very nice sugar.
她喘着气
SHE GASPS
她吹
SHE BLOWS
哇!我把它剪掉了。
Wow! I cut it off.
这之后我能接受心理咨询吗?我想我们需要它。
Can I have counselling after this? I think we're going to need it.
你还有一分钟。
You have one minute left.
不,山姆。忘了这个吧。好吧。我认为它增加了很多。
No, Sam. Forget this one. All right. I think it adds to it a lot.
队员们，该你们上场了。
Teams, that's your time up.
祝贺你,每一个人。
Congratulations, everyone.
你已经完成了最后的挑战。
You've completed your final challenge.
做得很好。对不起，伙计。
Well done. I'm sorry, man.
哦，好吧，你知道…没有足够的时间。
Oh, well, you know... Not enough time.
对不起，伙计。
I'm sorry, mate.
# Una furtiva lagrima…＃
# Una furtiva lagrima... #
三场80人的盛宴
Three showpiece banquets for 80 people
在短短9个小时内。
in just nine hours.
你看到什么了吗?不，我没看到。
Did you see what...? No, I didn't see it.
只是听到了声音，让我想起了我们的房子倒塌的时候。嗯嗯。
Just heard the noise, it reminded me of when ours fell down. Mm-hm.
我相信它也很美。哦，是的，毫无疑问。
I'm sure it was beautiful, as well. Oh, yeah, no doubt about it.
我知道他要去…他飞得很高。
I know he was going...he was going very high.
我要搬回孟加拉国。
I'm moving back to Bangladesh.
现在将由珍爱和伯努瓦来评判每队的最后一场比赛
Cherish and Benoit will now judge each team's final showpieces
品尝剩下的两种甜点。
and taste their remaining two desserts.
你所有优雅的结构，所有的努力，
You rested all your elegant structure, all that effort,
所有的工作都很漂亮，很优雅，
all that work, it was beautiful, it was elegant,
在最底部涂一点胶，不要比这个大。
on a little glueing, no bigger than this, at the very base.
我们可以看到它断裂的地方。
We can see where it broke.
你需要确保你知道你的压力点在哪里。
You need to make sure you understand where your pressure points are.
所以这很不幸。
So it's unfortunate.
你还好吗?
Are you all right?
你还好吗?你还好吗?是的。她抽噎
You OK? You OK? Yeah. SHE SNIFFLES
我只是为他们感到难过。
I just feel so sad for them.
对不起。
Sorry.
他呼出
HE EXHALES
你没事吧?是的。是的。好吗?
You all right? Yeah. Yeah. Bon?
这不仅仅是为了展示。现在，是关于甜点的。
It's not just about the showpiece. Now, it's about the dessert.
这是一个中式小蛋糕。
It's a Mandarin petit gateau.
它有一个橘子凝胶，一个橙色海绵
It has a Mandarin gel, an orange sponge
还有一块巧克力色的黑貂饼干，上面裹着香橙慕斯。
and a chocolate Sable biscuit, surrounded by scented orange mousse.
就设计而言，
Well, in terms of the design,
釉面有点薄。
the glaze was a little bit on the thin side.
很多这样的甜点
Quite a few of those desserts
釉还没完全涂好。是的。
haven't got the glaze all the way. Yeah.
就像巧克力配橘子一样。
Quite like the chocolate profile with the orange.
他们很般配。
They marry together very well.
黑貂太厚，又不够短，
The Sable is far too thick, and not short enough,
这使得它很难切割。
which makes it very difficult to cut.
这是芒果巴瓦罗加百香果果冻和新鲜芒果
It's a mango bavarois with a passion fruit jelly and fresh mango
还有百香果，最后是柠檬酥饼。
and passion fruit, finished with a lemon shortbread at the bottom.
从视觉上看，它很简单，但釉面很好。
Visually, it's pretty simple, but nicely glazed.
有时候，当它很简单的时候，它看起来真的很优雅。
Sometimes, when it is simple, it looks really elegant.
外观设计简单，内部设计简单。
Simple design on the outside, simple design on the inside.
但味道干净。摩丝的质地很漂亮。
But clean flavour. The mousse has a beautiful texture.
然后有了果盘，
And then with the compote,
酸度很快就会加入，它们之间的平衡非常好。
the acidity just kicks in straight away and they balance very nicely.
你做的每件事都很努力。
Very good effort in everything that you have done.
好吧，伙计们，这太激动人心了!它有。非常感谢。
Well, guys, it's been emotional! It has. Thank you very much.
两人:是的，谢谢。非常感谢。谢谢你！欢呼。
BOTH: Yes, thank you. Thanks very much. Thank you. Cheers.
开始和结束时都哭了。
Cried at the start and at the end.
他们笑了
THEY LAUGH
这看起来很疯狂!疯了。
This looks mad! Insane.
哇。
Wow.
你利用了每一秒。
You made use of every second.
看着你们俩工作真是太开心了。
It was such a joy to watch both of you work.
我真的很喜欢水晶球作为你的基础。
And I really like the crystal ball as your base.
真的很喜欢小狮子。它让我想起了特拉法加广场。
Really liked the little lion. It reminds me of Trafalgar Square.
它们都很好地结合在一起。
It all binds together really nicely.
我真的很喜欢这个配色方案。这是诚挚的协约。
I really like the colour scheme. It is the entente cordial.
吹糖丝带的小技巧
The little technique of the blown sugar ribbon
不是你经常看到的。
is not something you see often.
技术上很有挑战性。
Very technically challenging to do.
你能认出那些让你的故事生动起来的符号。
And you can recognise the symbols which bring your story to life.
但这不是甜点。
But it isn't the dessert.
我们想尝尝覆盆子和开心果球。
We would like to taste the raspberry and pistachio sphere.
你会看到一个红色的饼干层覆盖在开心果奶油上。
You will see a red biscuit cuillere to cover the pistachio buttercream.
里面是柑橘蛋白酥皮。
Inside, you've got citrus meringue.
最后，你会发现一些覆盆子酱。
To finish with, you will find some raspberry confit.
画龙点睛，
The finishing touch,
我想让它有更多的技巧和高完成度。
I'd like it to have a little bit more finesse and high finish.
我个人非常喜欢开心果和覆盆子。
Personally, I really like pistachio and raspberry.
我很喜欢你在蛋白派中加入皮屑。
I really like when you add in the zest into your meringue.
我尝了尝开心果。
I taste the pistachio.
我觉得奶油其实很清淡。
I think the buttercream is actually quite light.
但它仍然是奶油，所以这意味着有很多黄油。
But it's still a buttercream, so that means a lot of butter.
当你把它们一起吃的时候，你会有一种浓郁的感觉
When you eat it all together, you've got a sensation of richness
糖和脂肪。
in sugar and in fat.
这是一种老式的甜点。
So it's a little bit of an old-fashioned kind of dessert.
我很高兴你决定不拘泥于一种风格，
I like the fact that you've decided not to stick to one style,
所以在这种情况下，你有更多的分享甜点。
so you have more of a sharing dessert on this occasion.
草莓酸橙慕斯，
So you've got strawberry and lime mousse,
草莓果冻配新鲜草莓，
strawberry jelly with fresh strawberries,
香草奶油蛋糕，香草海绵蛋糕，底部是小蛋糕。
vanilla anglaise, vanilla sponge and the bottom is a feuilletine.
它很优雅。这层很均匀。
It's quite elegant. The layer is quite even.
我喜欢它的口感。这是可爱的海绵蛋糕
I like some of the texture. You've got the lovely sponge
下面是脆脆的布丁。
and then the crunchy feuilletine at the bottom.
我喜欢慕斯的口感，口感很柔滑
I like the mousse texture, quite creamy on my palate
而且对我来说很干净。
and it's quite clean for me.
至于果冻，它会完全融化，
And then, as for the jelly, it just melts completely,
我还能品尝到新鲜的草莓味。
and I can still taste the fresh strawberry.
它真的很好吃。两人:谢谢。
It's really pleasant to eat. BOTH: Thank you.
我期待着晚餐!
I'm looking forward to dinner!
他们笑了
THEY LAUGH
你真的在努力突破界限
You are trying really hard to push the boundaries
什么是可能的糕点。
of what is possible within patisserie.
那里有很多乐趣。
A lot of fun is there.
我们总是被你的理念所折服。
We are always blown away with your concept.
那是个奢华的宴会吗?
Is that a lavish banquet?
我不太确定。
I'm not too sure.
糖链有点过于简单了。
And the sugar strand is a little bit on the simplistic side.
你能端上你的甜点吗?是的。
Will you be able to serve your dessert? Yes.
你喜欢奶酪吗?这是要加到汉堡里的……
Would you like cheese? This is to add to the burger...
笑声
LAUGHTER
一些番茄酱吗?你喜欢奶酪吗?是的。哦，是的，请。
Some ketchup? Would you like cheese? Yes. Oh, yes, please.
汉堡外的面包是由百香果巧克力慕斯制成的
Outside the burger bun is made up of passion fruit chocolate mousse
还有夏威夷坚果巧克力布朗尼。
and macadamia nut chocolate brownies.
奶酪是白巧克力甘纳许。
And the cheese is white chocolate ganache.
我可以看到生菜，它是由苹果做成的，
And I can see the lettuce, which is made up of apple,
西红柿是由草莓做成的。
tomato that is made out of strawberry.
做得很好。我喜欢它的样子。
Well done. I like the look of it.
忘掉羞耻吧!
Forget being shameful!
哦!笑声
Oh! LAUGHTER
我的大脑让我喜欢它，因为它太有趣了。
My mind's asking me to like it, because it's so fun.
我真的很喜欢巧克力蛋糕
I really like the brownie with
里面的澳洲坚果的嘎吱声。
the crunch of the macadamia that is inside.
我喜欢中间的布朗尼，
The brownie in the middle I like,
但我觉得对我来说，风格重于内容。
but I think it's style over substance for me.
有太多的事情要做，你只剩下一个……
There's too many things going on and you're left with a...
. .奇怪的味道。
..weird flavour.
芯片……
The chips...
. .没关系!
..that's OK!
笑声
LAUGHTER
这是一种小酥饼，加了浓郁的覆盆子番茄酱。
It's a little shortbread with a quite intense raspberry ketchup.
这是我最喜欢的部分。
This is the part I could enjoy.
下一个。
Next one.
我很高兴你做出了这样的决定
I really enjoy the fact that you've decided that
你的一份甜点会是展示品的一部分。
one of your desserts would be part of the showpiece.
好主意。
Great idea.
这是我们第一次可以吃相框。
This is the first time that we can eat a picture frame.
我喜欢这个主意。
Love the idea.
我很喜欢焦糖的味道。
I quite like the caramel taste.
然而，我认为它已经与大妥协
However, I think it has been compromised with the big
我吃过的大块巧克力，它超越了这种感觉
chunk of chocolate that I've eaten, and it overtakes the sensation
我以为我在吃酥饼
that I'm thinking I'm eating a shortbread.
酥饼很好吃，百香果焦糖也很棒
The shortbread is beautiful, the passion fruit caramel is great
再加上牛奶巧克力，
and the combination with the milk chocolate,
我可以玩一整天。
I could have this all day.
谢谢你！非常感谢。谢谢你！
Thank you. Thank you very much. Thank you.
他呼出
HE EXHALES
猫头鹰咄
OWL HOOTS
另外两个队真的很强
The two other teams really strong
我们不能在同一个法庭上吵架，所以我们就…是的。
and we can't fight in the same court, so we just, you know... Yes.
. .我们的风格和…是的!
..did our style and... Yes!
. .法官尝了尝，他们喜欢一些，
..the judge tasted and they liked some pieces,
他们不喜欢别人。
they didn't like some other.
是的，那是不一样的。
Yes, that was different.
尤其是珍爱，用她的方式表达她的情感。
Especially Cherish showing her emotions the way she did.
当中心装饰物升起时，它看起来确实不错
When the centrepiece went up, it did look good
我为此感到非常自豪。
and I was quite proud of it.
是的。情感的全面。
Yeah. Emotional all-round.
我想我们都对结果感到焦虑和紧张。
I think we're both anxious and nervous about the result.
这将是非常不同的。
It's going to be very different.
通常我们会在厨房等待结果。
Normally we're waiting for result in the kitchen.
而现在，我们将在朋友和家人面前。
Whereas now, we are going to be in front of friends and family.
你的心跳会比平时快十倍。
Your heart's going to be going ten times faster than it normally is.
欢呼和掌声
CHEERING AND APPLAUSE
当决赛选手与他们的朋友和家人团聚时，
While the finalists join their friends and families,
珍爱和伯努瓦要做一个重大的决定。
Cherish and Benoit have a huge decision to make.
技术和努力都很好，
Techniques and effort were good,
但这部分让他们有点失望。
but this is the part which let them down a little bit.
他们尽了最大的努力。
They tried their very best.
这对我来说非常重要。
That is, for me, very important.
这是一种展示的元素。
There is that element of showpiece.
人物都在那里。
The characters are there.
当你看到塔的故事，或者整个概念?
When you look at the Tower story, or the whole concept?
你好!
Hello!
好主意，迷你汉堡，概念很好。
Good idea, the little, mini burger, the concept is good.
这张桌子可能会成为冠军。
Potentially, this table could be a champion.
这不是一个容易的决定。不，它不是。
It's not going to be an easy decision. No, it is not.
欢呼和掌声
CHEERING AND APPLAUSE
大家晚上好。
Good evening, everyone.
非常感谢你的到来。
Thank you so much for coming.
决赛中的三支球队绝对是不可思议的。
The three teams in the final have been absolutely incredible.
但只能有一个赢家。
But there can only be one winning team.
请往前走。
Please step forward.
欢呼和掌声
CHEERING AND APPLAUSE
经过深思熟虑，评委们做出了决定
After much deliberation, the judges have decided
2018年《烘焙大赛:专业选手》的获胜者是……
that the winners of Bake Off: The Professionals 2018 are...
. .伊曼纽尔和山姆。
..Emmanuel and Sam.
欢呼和掌声
CHEERING AND APPLAUSE
做得好!
Well done!
哦，我的天哪!
Oh, my goodness!
太神奇了!
That is amazing!
这太疯狂了。
That was insane.
做得好!
Well done!
我们的旅程越来越强大。
Our journey has gone from strength to strength.
我们是朋友，这是毫无疑问的。
We were friends, there's no doubt about it.
但他更像是我的老板和朋友，我想这已经改变了，
But he was more my boss and friend second, and I think that's changed,
现在我们是朋友，他还是我老板。
and now we're friends as much as he still is my boss.
阿莱兹，让我看看你的眼泪!Allez，加油!
Allez, show me a little tear! Allez, come on!
不是山姆就是别人。
It's Sam or nobody else.
我不可能和其他人一起做这件事。
There's no way I could have done it with anybody else.
做得好!
Well done!
辉煌!
Brilliant!
做得好!
Well done!
我认为这是他们应得的，所以我真的为他们感到高兴。
I think they deserve it big time, so I feel really happy for them.
在这次比赛中我们学到了很多
We learned a lot in this competition
这是我经历过的最好的经历之一。
and it's just one of the best experiences I've done.
我很高兴你们能走到这一步。
I was so happy you guys made it so far.
我很累，很累，很开心，很激动。
I've been tired, exhausted, happy, emotional.
虽然这段经历非常艰难，但我会想念它的。
Although it has been extremely tough, I'm going to miss it.
我会想念大家的。
I'll miss everyone.
我们遇到了一些很棒的人，度过了美好的时光，
We met some great guys, we had some amazing times,
和其他人竞争真的是一种乐趣。
it's been a real pleasure to compete with the other guys.
这是朋友……
It's friends for...
. .很可能是生命。
..very likely, life.
欢呼和掌声
CHEERING AND APPLAUSE
你有什么能打动伯努瓦和珍爱吗?
Do you have what it takes to impress Benoit and Cherish?
如果你想申请下一个系列
If you would like to apply for the next series
烘焙大赛:专业人士，访问…
of Bake Off: The Professionals, visit...
音乐:爱德华·格里格的《在山王的大厅里》
MUSIC: In the Hall of the Mountain King by Edvard Grieg